<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tiger:entry"  >Tiger, Bengal</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tiger:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
               <cell width="284">
                  <cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
                     <img src="entities/units/animals/TigerBengal/TigerBengal_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="96" width="96"/>
                  </cell>
                  <cell width="16">
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
                  </cell>
                  <cell width="16">
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
                  </cell>
                  <cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/endangered.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="204" b="51">
                     Endangered
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>   
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Tropical Rainforest</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_tropicalrainforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Southeast Asia</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Rainforest_Asia_SouthEast.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>               
               <cell width="284" pady="10">              
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:  	Carnivores                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Carnivora)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:	Cats                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Felidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>Panthera</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>tigris</i>
                     <br/>

							Subspecies:	                                                       
                     <i>
							tigris
                     </i>
                  </color>                                 
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tropicalrainforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">
Fun Bengal Tiger Facts
                  </font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
The Bengal tiger is the world's largest cat, weighing up to 400 to 570 lb (180 to 258 kg).
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
A tiger's roar can be heard up to 2 mi (3 km) away.
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
With the exception of white tigers, which have blue eyes, all tigers have yellow eyes.		
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  Studies suggest that tigers have very good hearing. They can turn their ears toward the source of a sound, enhancing their hearing sensitivity.		
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
Five soft pads on the bottom of tiger paws produce a distinctive paw print, or pug mark. 			The padding on the bottom of the paw enables tigers to move silently.
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  Only half of all tiger cubs in the wild survive to the age where they become independent of their mother. 		
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  Tigers hunt alone, using the protective covering of trees or tall grass to slowly sneak up on prey.
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  On average, a tiger in the wild must kill about once every eight days.
                  </color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
To unlock the Bengal tiger in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 3-1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>
The tiger is the largest member of the cat family and the only cat with striped fur. Perfectly designed       			predators, tigers possess beauty, grace, and awesome power. Their presence in the wild, revealed by a throaty       			roar or a track on a dusty trail, electrifies the forest and sends shivers down the spines of all who share its space. Humans admire tigers as much as they fear them and the animals figure prominently in Asian myths, religions, arts, and imagination. Tigers were once found throughout the forested regions of tropical and temperate Asia. Excessive hunting and destruction of tiger habitat have now narrowed the tiger's range to a few isolated patches throughout Asia. Many people have organized local and international conservation organizations to prevent tigers from becoming extinct.                 
            <p/>
Among the 36 cat species, tigers are most closely related to 
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_lion:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">lions, </color>
               </u>
            </a>
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_leopard:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">leopards</color>
               </u>
            </a>
, and  
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_jaguar:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">jaguars</color>
               </u>
            </a>            
. These cats evolved from a common ancestor that was probably similar to modern leopards or jaguars and lived more       			than 5 million years ago. The earliest fossils clearly identified as those of tigers are about 2 million years old.       			These fossils were found in central Asia, eastern and northern China, Siberia, Japan, Sumatra, and Java. Based on       			fossils dating from 300,000 to 10,000 years ago, some scientists think that tigers may have ranged into       			present-day Alaska via the Bering land bridge that once joined Alaska and Siberia during the last glaciation in       			the Pleistocene Epoch. Other scientists believe that the big cat fossils found in Alaska all belong to lions.                                    
            <p/>
Scientists use a variety of methods to study the behavior of tigers and track their movements. Radio tracking       			was first used to track tigers in Nepal in 1973. In this method, a collar with an attached radio transmitter is       			placed around the neck of a tiger. Scientists monitor the radio transmissions as the tiger travels, tracking the       			tiger's whereabouts to learn about its range, life history, and behaviors. More recently, scientists have set up       			camera traps that are triggered by an infrared beam. When a tiger crosses the infrared beam, the camera snaps a       			shot of the tiger, recording the date and time the photograph was taken. The tiger's unique stripes help identify       			the animal, and when the same animal triggers other camera traps, the photo archives enable scientists to gather       			information about the tiger's movements. This method helps scientists estimate tiger numbers in the wild.           
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">
Content provided courtesy of                         
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">
Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>
(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_elephant:entry"  >Elephant, African</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_elephant:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/ElephantAfrican/ElephantAfrican_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/ElephantAfrican/ElephantAfrican_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
                  <cell width="60"/>						
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/endangered.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="204" b="51">
Endangered
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>     

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Savannah</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_savannah.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Savannah_Africa.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:  Elephants                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Proboscidea)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:  Elephants                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Elephantidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:                                                         
                     
                     <i>Loxodonta</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:                                                         
                     
                     <i>africana</i>
                     <br/>
                  </color>

               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/savannah_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>                   
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun African Elephant Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The name "elephant" means "visible from afar."		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			African elephants eat up to 6 percent of their body weight each day. For a 10,000 lb bull, that translates to 600 lbs of feed per day.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the African elephant in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 4-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                   	The elephant is a huge mammal characterized by a long muscular snout and two long, curved tusks. Highly intelligent and strong, elephants are the largest land animals and are among the longest-lived, with life spans of 60 years or more. Healthy, full-grown elephants have no natural enemies other than humans.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Over the past 40 million years, more than 600 species of elephants have roamed the earth. Today only three species are alive - the African elephant, the Asian elephant, and the African forest elephant. Climate fluctuations over the millennia and resulting vegetation changes caused the extinction of many elephant species, but human impact has also taken its toll. At the turn of the 20th century, elephants numbered from 5 million to 10 million, but widespread hunting and habitat destruction reduced their numbers to an estimated 640,000 by the end of the century. Present-day efforts to save elephants may be inadequate, and biologists are unsure if elephants as a species will survive.                                    
            
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                African elephants live in grassy regions south of the Sahara Desert. Dark gray in color, bull (male) elephants stand about 11 ft (3.4 m) tall and weigh about 5.4 metric tons, while cow (female) elephants stand 2.8 m 9 ft (2.8 m) tall and weigh about 3.6 metric tons. They have no sweat glands, so they like to cool off by rolling in ponds and streams. The mud that dries on their skin protects it from the sun.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                          			Throughout history, people have prized elephants for their great size and strength. On the battlefield, soldiers astride elephants have trampled and terrified enemies. Elephants also have been trained to carry heavy supplies through jungles and to haul huge logs from the forests where they once lived.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Elephants have long been revered and honored, and in Thailand, India, and other Southeast Asian countries, beautifully decorated elephants still play a significant role in traditional religious ceremonies. According to Buddhist tradition, the Buddha chose the form of a white elephant as one of his many earthly incarnations, and the rare appearance of a white elephant is still heralded as a manifestation of the gods.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_beaver:entry"  >Beaver, American</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_beaver:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
         <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/BeaverAmerican/BeaverAmerican_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
                  <cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/vulnerable.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                        Conservation Status:
                        <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="255" b="0">
                        Vulnerable
                        </color>                     
                     </color>                     
                  </cell>
               </cell>            
 
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Wetlands</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_wetlands.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	North America</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Wetlands_America_North.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Rodents                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Rodentia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Beavers                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Castoridae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Castor  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>canadensis</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/wetlands_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun American Beaver Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Look out below! Beavers are sometimes dropped by parachute into remote areas to build dams and reduce erosion in rivers.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The secretion beavers produce to mark their territories contains acetylsalicylic acid, the main ingredient in aspirin.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A beaver can stay underwater for up to 15 minutes by storing extra oxygen in its lungs and body tissue.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the American beaver in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 3-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                The beaver is a semiaquatic rodent noted for the building of dams. There are only two kinds of beavers, the American beaver and the Eurasian beaver. The two species share similar behavior and anatomy, although they have some small physical differences, such as the shape of the nasal bones. They are large rodents; the average adult beaver weighs about 16 kg (about 35 lb), but specimens as heavy as 40 kg (90 lb) have been found, and some extinct beavers were almost bearlike in size.                                    
           

            <p/>

            
                                                The North American beaver is widely known for its habit of building dams and for its closely knit family units. The construction of the dam produces a small- to moderate-sized beaver pond that helps to increase the biological diversity of the surrounding area as well as conserve water and maintain water flow.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_rhino:entry"  >Rhinoceros, Black</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_rhino:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/RhinocerosBlack/RhinocerosBlack_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
						<br/>   
						<cell width="32" pady="0">               
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/critical.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
						</cell>                 
						<cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
							<color r="255" g="255" b="255">
							Conservation Status:
							<br/>
								<color r="255" g="0" b="0">
							Critically Endangered
								</color>
							</color>                  
						</cell>
					</cell>

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Savannah</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_savannah.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	East Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Savannah_Africa_East.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Odd-Toed Ungulates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Perissodactyla)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Rhinoceroses                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Rhinocerotidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Diceros  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>bicornis</i>
                     <br/>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/savannah_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Black Rhinoceros Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A rhinoceros's horn grows throughout its life.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Poachers kill rhinoceroses for their horns, which are ground and used in traditional Chinese medicine.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			When they are threatened, rhinoceroses sometimes charge toward a distressing scent or sound.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Rhinoceroses have extremely poor vision, but an acute sense of smell.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the black rhinoceros in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 3-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                Rhinoceros is the common name for five species of enormous mammals with one or two horns projecting from their snouts. Rhinos are among the biggest and heaviest land animals alive today, exceeded in size only by the 	                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_elephant:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">elephant </color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                 	and the 	                                    
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_hippo:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">hippopotamus</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                 	. They have thick, pillar-like legs, with three toes covered with broad, hooflike nails. Rhinos are legendary for their poor eyesight, but their senses of smell and hearing are acute. Although they look clumsy, rhinos can swivel around rapidly to face danger, and if threatened, can charge at speeds of up to 50 km/h (about 30 mph).                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Relatively fearless and unpredictable, the immense black rhinoceros will charge people or animals, usually stopping just before impact. The largest black rhinos weigh 1.3 metric tons and are 9.8 feet (3 meters) tall. They have two horns on their snouts, and in some black rhinos, the larger, front horn extends 32 inches (81 centimeters). Used to make dagger handles in Yemen and medicines and aphrodisiacs in East Asia, a single rhino horn can bring thousands of dollars on the black market. Consequently, the black rhinoceros and its close relative, the white rhinoceros, have been hunted nearly to extinction. Black rhinos once ranged throughout Africa south of the Sahara but are now restricted to parks scattered throughout the range. To prevent inbreeding and to ensure the survival of the species, park personnel truck rhinos between isolated reserves for mating.                         
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                To avoid the heat and biting flies, this armor-plated mammal spends hours each day wallowing in mud holes in the floodplains of the Ganges and other rivers of northeast India. With a single horn and wartlike bulges on its shoulders and upper legs, this primitive-looking, solitary animal feeds on grasses and aquatic plants. Fewer than 1,400 Indian rhinoceroses survive today.                         
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Rhinos live in warm climates, and are found only in Africa and Asia. The two African species are the white rhinoceros, a relatively placid animal that is the largest of all rhino species, reaching a weight of over 3 metric tons, and the black rhinoceros, which is about half as heavy as the white rhinoceros but much more aggressive. The Asian species include the Indian rhinoceros, which has skin that looks like a suit of armor, and two much rarer species, the Sumatran rhinoceros and the Javan rhinoceros. African rhinos have two horns, but depending on their species and sex, Asian rhinos have two horns, a single horn, or none at all. As a result of illegal trade in rhinoceros horn and habitat destruction, the populations of the black, Sumatran, and Javan rhinos have suffered a sharp decline in recent years, and are now close to extinction in the wild.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_cheetah:entry"  >Cheetah</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_cheetah:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Cheetah/Cheetah_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="96" width="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
                  <cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/vulnerable.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="255" b="0">
                     Vulnerable
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>            
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Savannah</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_savannah.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Savannah_Africa.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class: Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order: Carnivores                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Carnivora)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:	Cats                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Felidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>Acinonyx</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:                                                        
                     
                     <i>jubatus</i>
                     <br/>
                  </color>                 
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/savannah_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Cheetah Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The cheetah is one of the fastest land animals. It can reach a top speed of 58 mph 	(93 km/h) in 2 to 3 seconds, and maintain it for 1,000 ft (300 m).		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The cheetah's long tail acts as a balance and aids in high-speed turns.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A cheetah's footpads have grooves for better traction at high speeds.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			When communicating with one another, cheetahs do not roar; instead they make a 	variety of vocalizations, including purrs, bleats, barks, and chirps, that sound 	remarkably like those of a bird.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the cheetah in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 2-1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                     The cheetah is a member of the cat family and one of the fastest land animals in the world. A cheetah can accelerate to a running speed of 93 km/h (58 mph) in just two to three seconds, sustaining that speed for up to 300 m (1,000 ft). Until about 100 years ago cheetahs were found in open habitats throughout Africa, the Middle East, and southwest Asia as far as central India. Excessive hunting and habitat destruction have reduced the cheetah's range to isolated parts of Africa south of the Sahara, where around 10,000 cheetahs now live. Fewer than 100 cheetahs remain in remote areas of Iran.                                    
           

            <p/>

            
                                                Until recently this fastest of land mammals dashed after its prey across savannahs and semideserts throughout Africa and western and central Asia. Now the cheetah, Acinonyx jubatus, verges on extinction in Asia and is dwindling in much of Africa. Why? Some biologists believe today's cheetahs are simply too inbred to thrive, being descended from a few survivors of a crisis that almost wiped the species out some 10,000 years ago. But other scientists dispute this bottleneck theory and maintain that the genetic uniformity of the cheetah has not led to any constitutional weakness. The real agents behind the decline of the species, they say, are the ranchers and farmers who persecute cheetahs as vermin and encroach on their remaining habitat.                                    
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
           
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Scientists classify the cheetah in its own genus because of its physical distinctiveness from other cats, although genetic studies suggest that the cheetah may share a common ancestor with the North American puma. Fossil evidence shows that cheetahs may have originated in North America as early as 3 million years ago and then spread into Eurasia and Africa. Scientists theorize that around 12,000 years ago a significant climate change caused a rapid decline in the cheetah population, with only a small group of cheetahs surviving in Eurasia. Inbreeding (mating between close relatives) likely occurred as this tiny population slowly grew over generations. As a result of this inbreeding, today's cheetahs lack genetic variation, which may make them less able to adapt to changes in the environment, such as infectious disease or a climate change. Overhunting and habitat destruction place cheetahs at high risk for extinction. Farmers often kill cheetahs to prevent them from threatening their livestock. Scientists have developed breeding programs intended to provide insurance against their extinction in the wild, and they are working with local communities in Africa to reduce conflicts between people and cheetahs.                                     
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
           
            
           
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Scientists primarily study cheetahs in the wild by using radio tracking, in which a collar with a radio transmitter attached is placed around the neck of a cheetah. Scientists monitor the radio transmissions as the cheetah travels in order to track the cat's whereabouts and learn about its life history and behaviors. Some scientists also keep a photographic archive of individuals within a population. They are able to distinguish one cheetah from another by a distinctive pattern of rings on the tail. This photographic record helps scientists monitor individual cheetahs over the course of their lives.                                        
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
        
         
       
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                 	        Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_chimp:entry"  >Chimpanzee</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_chimp:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Chimpanzee/Chimpanzee_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
                  <cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/endangered.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="155" b="0">
                     Endangered
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Tropical Rainforest</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_tropicalrainforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Central Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Rainforest_Africa.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Primates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Primata)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Hominids                                                                            
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                    
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     <i>(Hominidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Pan</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>troglodytes</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tropicalrainforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Chimpanzee Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Chimpanzees do not swim.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Chimpanzees strip sticks and poke them into termite mounds to catch insects for food.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Chimpanzees usually travel on all fours on the ground, but they also swing from tree to tree.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The brain of a chimpanzee is about half the size of the human brain.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the chimpanzee in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 3-1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                      The chimpanzee is an ape of equatorial Africa that, physically and genetically, is the animal most closely related to humans. Two species of chimpanzee, or chimp, exist: the common chimpanzee and the bonobo, also known as the pygmy chimpanzee. The common chimp is found in dense jungle and more open wooded savannah from Sierra Leone and Guinea on the Atlantic Ocean to the lakes Tanganyika and Victoria in east central Africa. The bonobo is found only in a small region of thick jungle in the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC, formerly Zaire) in central Africa. Both species of chimpanzee are listed as endangered species in the wild by the World Conservation Union (also known as IUCN).                                    
           
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
           
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Chimpanzees, Pan troglodytes, are known as intelligent communicators and problem solvers. They prepare and use a wide variety of tools such as long, peeled digging sticks, grass stems, sponges (made of bark or leaves, chewed until soft), and rags (of leaves). They may use these tools for enlarging the holes of insect dens, pulling termites or ants out of their nest mounds, or smashing the harder-shelled of the 20 kinds of fruit they often eat in a day. Males also use sticks and rocks in their charging displays. Chimpanzees differ from human beings by only 1 percent of their genetic material, making them our closest relative.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                The highly intelligent and gregarious chimpanzee lives in the tropical rain forests of equatorial Africa. Although these primates spend much of their time in trees-where they forage for fruits, nuts, and leaves-they are also active on the ground. In their research, Jane Goodall and other scientists have discovered that chimpanzees use a complex system of communication and maintain an elaborate, hierarchical social structure. Like other apes, chimpanzees are in peril because of the ongoing destruction of tropical rain forests.                           
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            <p/>
         </cell>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
                               Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.	                                   
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_peafowl:entry"  >Peafowl, Common</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_peafowl:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/PeafowlCommon/PeafowlCommon_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/PeafowlCommon/PeafowlCommon_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="60"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>             

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Temperate Forest</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_temperateforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Southeast Asia</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/temperateforest_Asia.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Birds                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Aves)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Gamebirds                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Galliformes)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Quails, partridge, francolins, pheasants, 	                                                       
                     
                     <br/>

                     grouse, turkey                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Phasianidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Pavo  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>cristatus</i>
                  </color>   
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/temperateforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Common Peafowl Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Peacocks (males) and peahen (females) subsist on an omnivorous diet of worms, insects, small snakes, and seeds.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the common peafowl  in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                  Peafowl, or peacock, is a common name for three members of the pheasant family. Although these birds are more commonly called peacocks, that name is properly applied only to males; females are called peahens. Two species are Asian: the common or Indian peafowl, and the green peafowl. The third species, the Congo peafowl, is known only from the forests of the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC, formerly Zaire). The Asian peacocks are noted for their resplendent trains of long upper tail coverts, which conceal their relatively short tails, and are raised and spread in strutting displays. The feathers are generally iridescent green and gold and are ornamented with eyelike markings of a rich color, known as peacock blue. The same blue also appears on the head, neck, breast, and crest of the common peacock; in the green peacock the head, neck, and underparts are green. The peahens have no trains and are less colorful than the males. Peafowl build their nests on the ground or in the low branches of trees. The birds subsist on an omnivorous diet of worms, insects, small snakes, and seeds.                                    
           

            <p/>

            
                                                The common peafowl has been domesticated in many parts of the world, and there are feral populations in the Hawaiian Islands. A white variety has been produced by selective breeding.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                 Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_zebra:entry"  >Zebra, Common</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_zebra:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/ZebraCommon/ZebraCommon_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>              
   
               <cell width="128">   
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Savannah</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_savannah.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	East Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Savannah_Africa_East.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Odd-Toed Ungulates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Perissodactyla)</i>
                     <br/>
      Family: Horses / Asses / Zebra <i>(Equidae)</i><br/>

                           			Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Equus</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>burchelli</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Subspecies:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>boehmi</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/savannah_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Common Zebra Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Zebras may be able to recognize other zebras by the pattern of stripes on their bodies.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Although they are less cooperative than horses, zebras can be tamed and trained to pull carriages, but they are very difficult to ride.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Zebras signal to each other with body language and sounds in the same way that domesticated horses do. 			Lowered ears, for example, show that a zebra is likely to kick, while a snort shows that it is alarmed.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			During the course of a day, a zebra herd may wander 12 miles (20 km) or more in search of food, usually returning to the same resting place each evening.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the common zebra in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 1-1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                The zebra is a member of the horse family with an eye-catching coat of black and white stripes. Zebras are found only in Africa, but their remarkable markings make them among the most familiar mammals in the world. There are three species of zebras, each with a distinctive stripe pattern: Grevy's zebra, the mountain zebra, and the plains zebra (also known as Burchell's zebra).                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Zebras are members of the family Equidae, which also includes horses and asses. The earliest known ancestor of the animals in this family was a small animal called Hyracotherium, or more commonly, Eohippus, which lived 60 million years ago during the Pleistocene Epoch. Animals known to be the direct ancestors of the modern horse, ass, and zebra appeared in Europe, Africa, and Asia about 4 million years ago during the Pliocene Epoch.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                       		Like other members of the horse family, zebras are primarily grazing animals, feeding on coarse        		grass. Zebras face many predators, particularly          			                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_lion:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">lions </color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                 	              			 and hyenas, but over the last 200 years humans        		have posed a greater threat to their survival. The quagga, a zebra with stripes on its head and neck,        		but often none on its sides and hindquarters, lived in southern Africa until the 1870s, when it was        		hunted to extinction. Today, both Grevy's zebra and the mountain zebra are endangered by hunting and        		habitat loss.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.	                                                   
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_camel:entry"  >Camel, Dromedary</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_camel:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/CamelDromedary/CamelDromedary_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell> 

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Desert</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_desert.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	North Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Desert_Africa_North.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Even-Toed Ungulates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Artiodactyla)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Camels                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Camelidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Camelus  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>dromedarius</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/desert_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Dromedary Camel Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Camels can close their nostrils to keep out dirt and sand.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Camels can drink brackish or salt water without getting sick.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The camel stores fat, not water, in its hump. The hump becomes flaccid as the fat is metabolized.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the dromedary camel in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                The dromedary camel is one of two kinds of camels, which are large ruminants native to the desert regions of Asia and northern Africa. The dromedary, or Arabian camel, has one hump, and the Bactrian camel, the other kind of camel, has two humps. The humps are stores of flesh and fat, absorbed as nutrition when food is scarce. A camel can subsist without water for several days. The dromedary camel usually stands 2 m (7 ft) tall at the shoulders. The hump rises about 30 cm (about 12 in) above the back. The Bactrian camel has slightly shorter legs, is about 1.9 m (about 6.5 ft) in height at the shoulders, but usually has a heavier torso than the dromedary. Both types of camels have been domesticated since ancient times.                                    
           

            <p/>

            
                                                The dromedary camel, unknown in the wild state, is found from northwestern India and the lowlands of Afghanistan to the extremity of the Arabian Peninsula and Somalia to the south and westward across the African deserts. Attempts have been made to introduce the species into Spain, Zanzibar, and the southwestern United States, but without lasting success. In Australia a population of about 25,000 feral dromedary camels still remains from an introduction that took place from 1840 to 1907. The dromedary camel is adapted to subsistence in the desert by its structural qualities and by its ability to bite off and consume the thorny plants that grow there. Thick, broad sole pads and thick callosities on the joints of the legs and on the chest, upon which it rests in a kneeling position, enable it to withstand the heat of the desert sand. Moreover, its nostrils may be closed against flying dust, and its eyes are shielded by very long eyelashes.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                 The endurance and strength of the camel have made it a valuable beast of burden. The dromedary camel, generally used as a saddle animal, can cover more than 161 km (100 mi) in a day. The flesh and milk of the camel are used as food and the hide for leather. The long hair, shed every summer, is made into cordage, fine paint brushes, and a light, warm, long-napped cloth.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.	                                   
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_penguin:entry"  >Penguin, Emperor</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_penguin:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/PenguinEmperor/PenguinEmperor_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Tundra</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_tundra.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Antarctica</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Tundra_Antarctica.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:	Birds                                                       
                     
                     <i>(Aves)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Penguins                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Sphenisciformes)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Penguins                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Spheniscidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Aptenodytes  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>forsteri</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tundra_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Emperor Penguin Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Studies indicate that penguins are champion divers. 			The large emperor penguin can reach depths of over 1,600 ft (500 m).		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			While most birds shed their feathers and grow new ones during a relatively long period of the year, 			penguins renew their entire plumage over two to four weeks.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A molting penguin generally stands immobile during its molting period, and has a very swollen, disheveled appearance.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
         To unlock the emperor penguin in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 1-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
         </color>
            <p/>
            
            
            
            
			The emperor penguin is one of only two penguin species that live on the frozen Antarctic continent. Penguin is the common name for 17 species of 
			flightless seabirds widely distributed in cooler waters and along coastlines in the Southern Hemisphere. Skilled swimmers, penguins have streamlined, 
			barrel-like bodies that reduce drag in the water. Their wings, modified to form thin, stiff flippers, provide propulsion while swimming.        
         
            
            
            
            <p/>
            
            
            
            
         Unlike the bones of other birds, penguin bones are solid, not hollow, which helps them remain submerged underwater. On land, penguins have a 
         waddling gait due to their short, thick legs set far back on the body. Penguins come ashore to breed, but they are, in fact, true marine animals, 
         spending as much as 80 percent of their lives underwater.  
         
            
            
            
            <p/>
         </cell>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">
            
            
            
            
                                                Contributed By: Tony D. Williams                                    
            
            
            
            
            
            <br/>
            
            
            
            

                                                      Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_gemsbok:entry"  >Gemsbok</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_gemsbok:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Gemsbok/Gemsbok_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>         
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Scrub</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_scrub.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Southern Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Scrub_Africa_South.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Even-Toed Ungulates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Artiodactyla)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Bovids                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Bovidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Oryx  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>gazella</i>
                     <br/>

                     Subspecies:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>gazella</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/scrub_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Gemsbok Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The female gemsbok's horns are slightly longer and slimmer than the male's.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Lone gemsbok bulls have been known to kill attacking lions by impaling them with their strong horns.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			To help supplement their water intake, gemsboks eat tsama melons and dig up roots and tubers.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			With their long horns and striking facial markings, gemsboks make highly prized hunting trophies.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Due to its lethal horns, the gemsbok is sometimes called the "sabre antelope."		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the gemsbok in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 1-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                Gemsbok is the common name for the largest and best known of the three species of oryx, or straight-horned antelope. Herds of ten or more gemsbok are still seen in southwestern Africa, their sandy-gray flanks nearly invisible against the desert and brushland habitat. Both sexes have sharply pointed horns that extend up to about 1.5 m (about 4.9 ft). The gemsbok stands up to 140 cm (up to 55 in) high at the shoulder and has a horselike posture and gallop. The horns are lowered parallel to the ground and the animals lunge with great accuracy when holding off 	                                    
           

            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_lion:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">lions </color>
               </u>
            </a>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
             and other predators. They are also swift runners that can outpace a horse or a pack of African hunting dogs. Gemsbok can survive dry seasons by eating melons and plant bulbs. Their long horns and striking facial markings have made them prized hunting trophies.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_ibex:entry"  >Ibex</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_ibex:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Ibex/Ibex_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Ibex/Ibex_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="60"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/vulnerable.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>  						
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="255" b="0">
                     Vulnerable
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>                                
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Alpine</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_alpine.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">European Alps</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Alpine_Europe.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Even-Toed Ungulates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Artiodactyla)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Bovids                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Bovidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Capra  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>ibex</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/alpine_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Ibex Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The unique structure of the ibex's hoof makes it an excellent climber on steep rocks.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Climbing to great heights is the ibex's best defense -- few predators can follow them into the steepest regions of their habitat.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			If an ibex senses danger, it will rise up on its very strong hind legs and point its horns towards its predator.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The ibex gets help with its grooming tasks from the grackle, a bird that pecks parasites from its coat.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			An ancient Egyptian recipe for a baldness cure includes ibex fat among its ingredients.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Like most goats, the male ibex sprays itself with its own urine, resulting in a strong body odor.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
         To unlock the ibex in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 1-1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
         </color>
            <p/>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
         Ibex is the common name for three species of wild goats characterized by enormous, back-curving horns, which in the male measure from 70 to 140 cm (28 to 55 in); the horns of the female are shorter. The representative Alpine ibex stands 65 to 105 cm (26 to 41 in) high, varies seasonally from reddish-brown to brownish-gray, and associates in bachelor groups and in herds of 10 to 20 females. It is found in craggy terrain between the timber and snow lines of the Alps. Male and female herds join only during the mating season. The Alpine Ibex is remarkably surefooted and is known for its agility in leaping about rocky ledges. Alpine ibexes have been severely hunted and are now protected. Other ibexes that are threatened with extinction are the Ethiopian ibex and the Spanish ibex of the Iberian Peninsula.
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_panda:entry"  >Bear, Giant Panda</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_panda:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/PandaGiant/PandaGiant_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/endangered.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="155" b="0">
                     Endangered
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Temperate Forest</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_temperateforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	China</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Temperateforest_china.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Carnivores                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Carnivora)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Bears                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Ursidae)  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Ailuropoda</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>melanoleuca</i>  
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/temperateforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Giant Panda Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Giant pandas are herbivores, and they eat about 40 lbs (18 kgs) of bamboo each day.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Giant panda paws have a long wrist bone that works like a thumb to grasp bamboo stems.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Giant pandas spend 12-14 hours eating each day.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Only about 1,000 giant pandas remain in the wild.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the giant panda in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 5-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                 Giant panda is the common name for a bear found in provinces of western China. The giant panda resembles other 	                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_grizzly:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">bears </color>
               </u>
            </a>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
             in general appearance, with the exception of the black patches over its eyes, ears, and legs and the black band across its shoulders. Giant pandas live in bamboo forests at high elevations and feed primarily on bamboo. Unlike other bears, they vocalize by bleating rather than roaring.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Females weigh about 80 kg (about 180 lb), and males weigh about 100 kg (about 220 lb). The giant panda's so-called sixth front toe is not a digit or claw but an enlarged wrist bone that functions as a thumb in grasping food. Giant pandas feed almost exclusively on bamboo, which is not highly nutritious. Furthermore, some bamboo species flower simultaneously and die shortly afterward, occasionally leading to starvation among giant panda populations. If their usual food supply is threatened, giant pandas may feed on gardens, crops, and even chickens, but they are little threat to people except in close encounters. The habitats of family groups and the survival of juvenile giant pandas are still poorly understood. Giant pandas seem to have no permanent den and do not hibernate, although they shelter in the winter in dens or hollow trees. Giant pandas are fairly solitary most of the year. Females may live in loose groups within the range of a dominant male.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Breeding takes place from March to May, and the young are born three to six months later weighing only 85 to 140 g (3 to 5 oz). Two cubs may be born, but only one survives. The young cry loudly for help and require great care from the mothers, and losses of young are a serious problem in the recovery and management of giant-panda populations. The giant panda's broken range has created six isolated populations. The total number of giant pandas in the wild is now about 1,000. Because giant pandas are restricted to a small area of western China, their status may be the most precarious of all the species of bears. World interest and research funds from many nations have improved the giant panda's status, but the species remains vulnerable to humans.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Contributed By: Charles Joseph Jonkel                         
            
            
            <br/>

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_flamingo:entry"  >Flamingo, Greater</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_flamingo:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/FlamingoGreater/FlamingoGreater_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell> 

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Wetlands</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_wetlands.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Central Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Rainforest_Africa.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  Birds		                                                       
                     
                     <i>(Aves)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Flamingos                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Phoenicopteriformes)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Flamingos                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Phoenicopteridae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Phoenicopterus  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>ruber</i>
                     <br/>

                     Subspecies:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>ruber</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/wetlands_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Greater Flamingo Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Young flamingos turn from gray to pink when they start eating shrimp and plankton.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The legs of the flamingo bend backwards and it eats upside down.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			"Flamingo" is the Latin word for "flame."		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A group of flamingos is called a "pat."		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			In ancient Rome, flamingo tongues were considered a great delicacy.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Flamingos feed in large numbers, making them less vulnerable to predators.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			In order to fly, flamingos need to run a few paces to gather speed. 		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			In many zoos, flamingos are fed a special pellet diet that helps them maintain their distinctive coloring.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the greater flamingo in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 1-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            The greater flamingo is the largest species of flamingo. Flamingo is the common name for the four species of a family of birds having exceptionally long legs and long, highly flexible necks. Their relationship to other birds is uncertain; some evidence allies them with the herons and ibises, some with the ducks and geese; and there is fossil evidence suggesting a relationship to shorebirds. Their bills bend abruptly downward about midway; the upper mandible is narrow, and fits into the lower like the lid of a box. When they feed, flamingos dip the head under water and scoop backward with the head upside down. The edges of the bill have tiny narrow transverse plates called lamellae. The large fleshy tongue pressing against the inside of the bill strains the water out through the lamellae, leaving behind the small invertebrates and the vegetable matter upon which the bird feeds.                                    
           

            <p/>

            
                                                The greater flamingo has two rather different subspecies, one vivid red and the other paler. The first of these breeds in the Caribbean area, from Yucatan and the West Indies to the coast of northeastern South America. It breeds well in captivity, and the occasional flamingo seen north of Florida probably escaped from a zoo. The paler flamingo inhabits Eurasia, in the Mediterranean area and Africa, east to India. Males of both subspecies may reach 155 cm (61 in) in height. The greater flamingo breeds in standing water or on low islands in shallow ponds, salt pans, and lagoons, building a conical mound of mud topped by a slight depression in which the one egg (rarely two) is laid. The young are fed on regurgitated food for as long as 75 days, although they can feed for themselves after about 30 days.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_grizzly:entry"  >Bear, Grizzly</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_grizzly:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/BearGrizzly/BearGrizzly_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/endangered.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="155" b="0">
                     Endangered
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Boreal Forest</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_borealforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	North America</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Boreal_America_North.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Carnivores                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Carnivora)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Bears                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Ursidae)  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Ursus</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>arctos</i>
                     <br/>

                     Subspecies:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>horribilis</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/borealforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Grizzly Bear Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			There are many subspecies of brown bear, including the grizzly and the Kodiak.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Unlike animals that hibernate, brown bears awaken easily during winter sleep and sometimes walk about.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Coastal populations of brown bears that feed on fatty salmon may be three times larger than inland brown bear populations that subsist on plants, insects, and some meat.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Brown bears are not always brown - they may have black, red, or gray coats.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the grizzly bear in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 3-1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                 The grizzly bear is one of several subspecies of the brown bear, the widest ranging of all bear species. Although the name grizzly bear is sometimes used to refer to all brown bears, grizzly actually refers to one subspecies in the northwestern interior of North America. Members of the subspecies that range throughout coastal Alaska and western Canada are known as Alaskan bears; those on Alaska's Kodiak Archipelago are called Kodiak bears. On the Eurasian land mass, brown bears extend from Norway to the Siberian peninsula and as far south as Greece and Iraq.                                    
           

            <p/>

            
                                                Brown bears have large, plantigrade feet (heel and sole touching the ground) and five long claws on their front paws to aid in digging. They may be almost black or very light beige; a few brown bears are pure white. The grizzly bear has deep chocolate brown fur with silver tips. The Kodiak bear is uniformly brown and usually has a ruff of longer hair that makes the head look larger.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                 Brown bears, along with                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_polarbear:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">polar bears</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                    , are the largest of the bear species. Brown bears range in weight from 90 to 800 kg (200 to 1760 lb), and adult males generally weigh more than adult females. Kodiak bears, which often feed on salmon, can weigh more than 700 kg (1700 lb). Grizzly bears, with a diet of berries, vegetation, and small mammals, are smaller than Kodiak bears. Depending on habitat, the average weight of grizzlies varies from 150 to 360 kg (330 to 794 lb) in Alaska and British Columbia, 95 to 139 kg (209 to 306 lb) in the Yukon Territory, and 102 to 324 kg (224 to 714 lb) in Yellowstone National Park.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                  Males and females are together only during the breeding season (May to June), but family groups may stay together for two to three years. Brown bears generally inhabit open areas, including the plains and the tundra. They may remain dormant without eating for up to seven months, usually at high elevations in dens or caves. During this dormant period, they are lethargic and less sensitive to danger. Their temperature declines only slightly, but their respiration and heart rate drop dramatically. When active, they eat enormous amounts of fish, berries, and succulent plants, sometimes consuming 40 kg (90 lb) of food per day.                                    
            
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Females have their first young at five to seven years old. They normally give birth to two cubs, skipping three to four years between litters. They can reproduce until almost 30 years of age, but few survive beyond the age of 20.                        
            
            
            <p/>
Brown bears make a loud roar when injured, but normally warn other bears and people by huffing, or making chomping or clacking sounds with their teeth. They almost always avoid confrontations with people. In most of their range, brown bears are relatively secure, although habitat losses pose a threat.	                                  
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">  
Contributed By: Charles Joseph Jonkel                           
            <br/>
Content provided courtesy of                         
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>
(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_hippo:entry"  >Hippopotamus</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_hippo:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Hippopotamus/Hippopotamus_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/vulnerable.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="255" b="0">
                     Vulnerable
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>            

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Wetlands</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_wetlands.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Central Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Wetlands_Africa.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Even-Toed Ungulates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Artiodactyla)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Hippopotamuses                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Hippopotamidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Hippopotamus</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>amphibius</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/wetlands_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Hippopotamus Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Hippopotamuses can close their nostrils and ears while underwater.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Before they can walk hippopotamuses can swim.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			When a mother hippo floats in the water, the young calf sometimes rides on the mother's back - behavior that helps protect the young from crocodile attack.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Female hippos take on all the responsibility of looking after their young and are fiercely protective parents.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the hippopotamus in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 2-1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                 The hippopotamus is an African mammal that lives partly in water and partly on land. There are two species of hippopotamuses. The smaller species, called the pygmy hippo, stands barely waist-high to an adult human. Its bigger relative - known as the river or common hippopotamus or, simply, hippopotamus - is one of the world's largest and heaviest land animals, weighing up to about 4,000 kg (about 8,800 lb). Although strictly a plant eater, the hippopotamus has massive jaws with formidable tusks. The animal has an unpredictable temperament and is capable of biting through small boats and slicing 	                                    
           

            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_croc:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">crocodiles </color>
               </u>
            </a>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
                      in two.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                The word hippopotamus comes from two Greek words that mean "river horse". While hippos do live in rivers, they differ from horses in being artiodactyls, mammals with an even number of hoofed toes on each foot. There is also very little about their shape that is horselike. Both species of hippos have barrel-shaped bodies, stocky legs, and smooth, almost hairless skin. Their heads appear outsized and their mouths look unusually broad.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Hippopotamuses are not as numerous as they once were, but they can still have a major impact on the landscape of the areas they inhabit. In some parts of Africa, river hippos trample riverbanks and lakeshores, creating a maze of waterside paths and wallows that they use to get access to the plants they eat. Hippos spend their days lazing in or near water, emerging after dark to feed.                                    
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Contributed By: David Burnie                        
            
            
            <br/>

            
                                                 				Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_jaguar:entry"  >Jaguar</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_jaguar:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Jaguar/Jaguar_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Tropical Rainforest</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_tropicalrainforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	South America</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/rainforest_america_south.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Carnivores                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Carnivora)  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Cats                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Felidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Panthera</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>onca</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tropicalrainforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Jaguar Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A jaguar sleeps an average of 10 hours per day.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Early South American cultures worshiped the jaguar as a god.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The jaguar's diet includes otters, turtles, frogs, alligators, and fish.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			With their short, sturdy legs, jaguars prefer to ambush rather than outrun their prey.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Jaguars are good climbers who like to hunt in trees, with mostly monkeys as their prey.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The word jaguar comes from a Native American word meaning "killer that takes its prey in a single bound."		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Jaguars are strong swimmers, and will follow their prey into water during a pursuit.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			While most big cats kill by biting the neck or throat, the jaguar often bites through the skull.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Some Amazon Indians claim that the jaguar uses its tail as bait when catching fish.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the jaguar in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                The jaguar is largest and most powerful of the American members of the cat family. The jaguar is found from the southern United States to northern Argentina, but it is especially abundant in the dense forests of Central America and Brazil. A mature jaguar is 112 to 185 cm (44 to 73 in) long, not including the tail, which is 45 to 75 cm (18 to 30 in) in length, and stands 60 cm (2 ft) high at the shoulder. Its coat is a rich yellow to rusty-red, and occasionally black, spotted with large black rosettes, each consisting of a circle of spots surrounding a central spot. The head and body are massive, and the legs are relatively short and thick. An adept climber and an excellent swimmer, the animal feeds on a wide range of arboreal, terrestrial, and aquatic animals. Although feared, the jaguar rarely attacks humans. In the pre-Columbian civilizations of Peru and Central America, it was worshiped as a god. Today the jaguar is extensively hunted because of ranchers' claims that it attacks cattle, although studies indicate that such attacks are infrequent.                                    
          

            <p/>

            
                                                    		Jaguars appear to mate in any season, although in some areas they may mate seasonally. After a gestation     		period of 93 to 105 days, the female bears one to four cubs, which remain with the mother until about the age     		of two. Jaguars have lived up to 22 years in captivity.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="280"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_lion:entry"  >Lion</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_lion:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Lion/Lion_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Lion/Lion_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="60"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/vulnerable.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="255" b="0">
                     Vulnerable
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255"> 	  				Savannah 	  			</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_savannah.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255"> 	  				Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/savannah_africa.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <font name="arial" size="8" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                        
                    	Class:  	Mammals                                                 
                        
                        
                        <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                        <br/>

                        
                          				Order:		Carnivores                                                 
                        
                        
                        <i>(Carnivora)  </i>
                        <br/>

                        
                          				Family:		Cats                                                 
                        
                        
                        <i>(Felidae)</i>
                        <br/>

                        
                          				Genus:		                                                
                        
                        
                        <i>Panthera</i>
                        <br/>

                        
                          				Species:	                                                
                        
                        
                        <i>leo</i>
                     </color>
                  </font>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/savannah_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Lion Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Lions are unusual among cats for their habit of living in groups. 			A pride consists of 2 to 12 adult females and their cubs. 			All of the females are related: sisters, mothers, aunts, and cousins.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A lion's roar can be heard from a distance of 5 miles (8 km).		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Despite their immense strength, lions do not have an easy life in the wild. 			They suffer from parasites and disease, they get injured or even killed while hunting or fighting with each other, and they may starve when food is scarce.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Lions spend about 20 hours a day just lying around.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the lion in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 2-1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                 The lion is one of the largest members of the cat family. The lion's size and strength have captured human imagination since ancient times, giving these animals the nickname king of beasts. Lions are also known for their mighty roar, a fearsome sound that can be heard by humans more than 8 km (5 mi) away.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                       Lions once ranged over vast areas on many continents. Fossil evidence shows that until about 10,000 years ago, lions lived throughout Africa, Europe, the Middle East, and into Asia as far as southern India and the island of Sri Lanka. They also lived in North America and northern South America. Since then, however, the lion's range has been shrinking steadily. Human hunters have killed countless        			numbers of lions as well as the hoofed mammals that lions eat. In many places, people have taken over the        			lion's habitats, which often are good places to farm and raise cattle. These habitats include grassy        			plains, savannahs, and dry woodlands but never thick forests or jungle. Today, lions are found in the wild        			in only two places on earth. About 100,000 lions survive in Africa south of the Sahara Desert. Another 300        			lions, called Asian lions, live in a reserve called the Gir National Park and Lion Sanctuary in northwest        			India. In both places, lions continue to be threatened by human activities. Thousands of lions also live in zoos and circuses around the world.                           
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
        
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="280"/>
         <cell width="600">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_moose:entry"  >Moose</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_moose:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
               <cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
                  <img src="entities/units/animals/Moose/Moose_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="16">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
                  <img src="entities/units/animals/Moose/Moose_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="16">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="60"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>             
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Boreal Forest</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_borealforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">North America</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Boreal_America_North.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
Class: Mammals                                                                            
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>
Order: Even-Toed Ungulates                                                        
                     <i>(Artiodactyla)</i>
                     <br/>
Family: Deer                                                        
                     <i>(Cervidae)</i>
                     <br/>
Genus:		                                                       
                     <i>Alces  </i>
                     <br/>
Species:	                                                       
                     <i>alces</i>
                     <br/>
Subspecies:	                                                       
                     <i>americana</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tropicalrainforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Moose Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A mother moose may protect her calf from wolves by shepherding it to shallow water, and then standing between it and the wolves, who usually give up.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			To escape wolves, moose often retreat to lakes and marshes, where they are safe until the water freezes over and the wolves can follow them.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Moose can dive up to 18 ft and stay underwater up to 30 seconds as they forage for water plants and roots.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A moose stands up to 7 ft (2 m) tall at the shoulder.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the moose in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
Moose is a common name for the largest member of the deer family. The name moose, given by the Algonquin, a native North American tribe, means "eater of twigs", reflecting the animal's primary diet of leaves and twigs. Moose are referred to as elk in Europe and Asia, where they inhabit the forests of northern Asia and Europe from Siberia in the east to Norway in the west, the Baltic region, and northern China. In North America moose are found in wooded areas of Canada and the northern United States. The deer known in North America as elk is also called wapiti. Moose are huge animals, with males, known as bulls, standing up to 2 m (6.5 ft) at the shoulder. Some bulls weigh more than 726 kg (1600 lb). Their characteristically long legs enable them to both browse on low bushes and small trees and wade in lakes and ponds to feed on aquatic plants. Once in the water, moose move easily and are powerful swimmers.                                    
            <p/>

            
                                                    		The head of the moose is large with an overhanging upper lip, or muzzle. A drooping growth of hair and     		skin, called a bell, hangs from the throat. The large, constantly moving ears of the moose act like radar,     		providing excellent hearing. A large shoulder hump is formed by the upward projections from neck vertebrae.     		Strong ligaments, which are necessary to hold the large head erect, are attached to these upward projections.     		The body color of the moose is generally brownish-black, with the face lightening to a brown color in the summer.     		The face of bulls darkens to a dark brown or black color as the breeding season approaches.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                    		Prominent features of bulls are the enormous antlers with marginal prongs, or tines, which can exceed 1.5 m     		(60 in) in width and 22.7 kg (50 lb) in weight. Antlers are covered with a soft, nutrient-rich skin called     		velvet, which is shed in early September and often eaten by bulls. Antlers themselves are shed each year     		after the mating season, which generally is in late September. Older bulls shed their antlers in December,     		and by the end of January most bulls have shed their antlers. Occasionally, some young ones will carry     		antlers into February. New antlers begin to grow in early April.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                    		Moose generally are solitary animals, although they may band in small groups of up to a dozen or more during     		the breeding season, especially in Canada's Yukon territory and Alaska. Both females and males are capable     		of mating in their second year of life. During mating, bulls battle for the female moose, or cows, engaging     		in antler fights with other males. After mating, gestation is around 230 days, with most calves born near     		the end of May. Cows usually bear one offspring, although twins are common and births of three or four calves     		have also been observed. Calves have reddish-brown coats and weigh 11 to 16 kg (24 to 35 lb) at birth.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                    		The average life span of moose is about 5 to 6 years, although some moose can live as long as 20 years. The     		age of a moose is determined by examining the root portion of the middle incisor teeth, which show a pattern     		of rings. Just as a tree's growth rings reveal its age, the dark ring in a moose's middle incisor combined     		with a light ring accounts for each year of age.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                    		Moose feeding habits vary with the seasons. During the fall, winter, and spring, they feed on the previous     		summer's growth of aspen, black poplar, willow, birch, hazel, dogwood, and balsam fir. In late spring and     		early summer, moose lick natural salt deposits, found in salt springs or roadside runoff to replenish their     		mineral reserves used up over winter. In summer, moose prefer vegetation that grows in water, and they can     		submerge for up to 40 seconds to reach plants beneath the water's surface.    		Despite their size and ability to attain running speeds of up to 58 km/h (36 mph) for short distances,     		moose fall prey to wolves and black and 	                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_grizzly:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135"> 				grizzly bears.  			</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                   	        		Some studies have shown that bears can kill up to     		75 percent of newborns in their first eight weeks of life. Another threat to moose is the winter tick.     		Tick infestations irritate the moose's skin, causing the moose to rub off portions of the hair they depend     		on for protection from the extreme winter cold, which typifies much of their habitat. Severe winters     		combined with heavy tick infestations can reduce moose populations as much as 50 percent.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                    		Contributed By: Vince Crichton   			                        
            
            
            <br/>

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_gorilla:entry"  >Gorilla, Mountain</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_gorilla:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/GorillaMountain/GorillaMountain_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/endangered.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="155" b="0">
                     Endangered
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>            

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Tropical Rainforest</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_tropicalrainforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Rainforest_Africa.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                                                                                                 Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                         		Order:		Primates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Primata)</i>
                     <br/>
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                      
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                         		Family:		Hominids                                                                             
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                  
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     
                     <i>(Hominidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                         		Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Gorilla</i>
                     <br/>

                                                                                                 Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>gorilla</i>
                     <br/>

                         		Subspecies:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>beringei</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tropicalrainforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Mountain Gorilla Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Fights between gorillas are rare and are usually resolved through threatening gestures.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Gorillas build a new sleeping nest every night.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Gorilla young develop physical skills twice as fast as human babies.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the mountain gorilla in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 4-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                 The mountain gorilla is one of three recognized geographically distinct gorillas, the largest, rarest, and most powerful anthropoid ape. Gorillas inhabit the forests of equatorial Africa from the western lowlands near the Cameroon coast to an altitude of about 3000 m (about 10,000 ft) in the central highlands of Democratic Republic of the Congo and Uganda. Three geographically distinct types are recognized: the western lowland gorilla, the eastern lowland gorilla, and the more densely coated mountain gorilla.                        
            
            
            <p/>
         </cell>
         <br/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_croc:entry"  >Crocodile, Nile</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_croc:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/CrocodileNile/CrocodileNile_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>              
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Wetlands</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_wetlands.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Central Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/wetlands_Africa.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                                                                                                 Class:  	Reptiles                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Reptilia)</i>
                     <br/>

                           		Order:		Crocodiles, Alligators and Gavials                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Crocodylia)</i>
                     <br/>

                           		Family:		Crocodiles                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Crocodylidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                           		Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Crocodylus</i>
                     <br/>

                           		Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>niloticus</i>
                     <br/>

                           		Subspecies:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>niloticus</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/wetlands_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Nile Crocodile Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			When crocodiles relax with their mouths open, a small bird, the spur-winged plover, plays dental hygienist and picks food from between their teeth.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Crocodiles constantly shed and replace their teeth throughout their lifetimes.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Crocodiles have no sweat glands. They lose heat through their mouths, and sometimes pant like dogs to keep cool.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A baby crocodile breaks out of its egg using a special hard tip on its snout.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Crocodiles can close off their nasal passages in the water, allowing them to seize food without drowning.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the Nile crocodile in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 1-1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                         Crocodile is the common name for any of a number of reptiles in a family of the crocodilian order. The term crocodilian refers to all members of the order, which includes alligators, caimans, and gavials as well as crocodiles.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                          		One of the largest reptiles on the earth today, the crocodile is also one of the most ferocious. It swallows many small animals whole but will also attack humans and other large animals, often batting them with its tail into a nearby pool of water to make them easier to capture.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Crocodiles can close off their nasal passages in the water, allowing them to seize food without drowning. They are immensely strong and may dismember larger prey by simply twisting it to death in the water. The Nile crocodile, Crocodilus niloticus, is one of the best known of the 12 species of crocodile.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                The Nile crocodile is the largest predator in Africa, growing up to 20 ft (6 m) in length and weighing up to a metric ton. It lurks around water holes and prowls rivers and canals in search of game, taking nearly any animal it can grasp, drown, and swallow, including humans. Found throughout subtropical and tropical Africa and Madagascar, adults are uniformly colored; juveniles are speckled. This crocodile was once numerous in the Nile and elsewhere, but its numbers have declined since World War II because of loss of habitat, hunting, and nesting-site disturbance by humans.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                The Nile crocodile was revered by certain ancient Egyptian sects, and mummies of crocodiles have been discovered in Egyptian tombs. In modern times this species has been hunted so extensively that few individuals remain in the lower Nile, but they are still abundant in the upper Nile and southward in Africa to the Cape of Good Hope.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Crocodiles are physiologically the most advanced reptiles; their internal anatomy resembles that of birds. They have a four-chambered heart and well-developed senses. Cold-blooded like all reptiles - their body temperature depends on the environment - crocodilians bury themselves in mud to estivate or hibernate. In warm regions they are dormant during droughts; in colder regions, during winter.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                Crocodile eggs are used for food in some parts of the world. The skin is highly valued for leather, and the extract from the musk glands is used in the manufacture of perfumes.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of 	                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_okapi:entry"  >Okapi</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_okapi:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Okapi/Okapi_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>               
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Tropical Rainforest</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_tropicalrainforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Central Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Rainforest_Africa_central.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Even-Toed Ungulates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Artiodactyla)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Giraffes                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Giraffidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Okapia</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>johnstoni</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tropicalrainforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Okapi Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Although much shorter than the giraffe, the okapi also has a long neck and eats leaves, and both animals have long tongues and skin-covered horns. 		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the okapi in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                    	The okapi, or forest giraffe, is a member of the 		                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_giraffe:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">giraffe </color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                                        			family found in the inaccessible rain forests of 	northeastern Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC, formerly Zaire) and western Uganda. The okapi lives a 	secluded life and it was not discovered until 1900. It is considered rare, but too little information 	exists about the okapi to classify it as threatened or endangered.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                      			The short, stout body of the okapi ranges from 150 to 170 cm (5 to 5.5 ft) high at the shoulders and 200 to     			213 cm (6.5 to 7 ft) in length, with a tail 30 to 42 cm (12 to 17 in) long that ends in a tuft. It weighs     			210 to 250 kg (460 to 550 lb). The male has two small, skin-covered bony knobs on its forehead. The okapi     			has a long, flexible blue-black tongue that it uses to rip leaves from branches. It has large, dark eyes     			and large, wide ears. The short, soft hair is reddish brown to black with large, white stripes on the front     			legs and flanks.                        
            
            
            <p/>
Little is known about the okapi in the wild. The animal visually blends into its surroundings. It feeds     			during the day, as well as just before dawn and after sunset. Each male generally inhabits a territory of     			about 6 sq km (about 2.3 sq mi). Although the okapi may travel in small family groups, this reclusive     			animal usually lives alone, except when mating. After mating, the female lives in isolation until she gives     			birth to one calf 14 to 15 months later. 
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="280"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                		Content provided courtesy of             		                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                                          			(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_ostrich:entry"  >Ostrich</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_ostrich:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Ostrich/ostrich_adult_m_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>            

               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Savannah</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_savannah.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Savannah_Africa.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Birds                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Aves)</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Order:		Ratites                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Struthioniformes)</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Family:		Ostriches                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Struthionidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Struthio  </i>
                     <br/>

                           			Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>camelius</i>
                     <br/>

                     Subspecies:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>australus</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/savannah_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Ostrich Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Although flightless, the ostrich can run at speeds as high as 40 mph (65 km/hr).		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Native to Africa, the ostrich is the largest living species of bird, growing to a height of 8 ft (2.4 m) and a weight of 330 lb (150 kg).		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the ostrich in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
           Ostrich is the common name for a large, flightless bird. Now found only in Africa, fossils indicate that the ostrich          		once also lived throughout Europe and Asia. Ostriches are the largest and strongest of living birds, attaining          		a height from crown to foot of about 2.4 m (about 8 ft) and a weight of up to 136 kg (300 lb). They have long          		necks and small heads, with large eyes and short, broad beaks. They spread their small wings when running and          		have long, powerful legs that are used for defense. The feet have only two toes. Male ostriches are black,          		with white wings and tail. The white feathers of the male, which are large and soft, are the ostrich plumes of          		commercial value. The female is a dull grayish brown.
           

            <p/>

            
                                                 			Ostriches are rapid runners and can attain about 65 km/h (about 40 mph). The males are polygamous and travel  			about in hot, sandy areas with three or four females, or in groups of four or five males accompanied by mates  			and young. The females lay their yellowish-white eggs together in a single large depression in the sand. The  			eggs weigh about 1.4 kg (about 3 lb) each and have a volume of about 1.4 liters (about 3 pt). The male sits on  			them at night, and the female incubates them by day.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                 			In the last half of the 19th century ostrich farming, or the breeding of domesticated ostriches for their  			plumes, was carried on extensively in South Africa, Algeria, Australia, France, and the United States. Ostrich  			plumes were used in hatmaking and dressmaking. Farming declined as the demand for ostrich plumes became almost  			negligible; however, the introduction of ostrich hide as a luxury leather has renewed interest in ostrich  			farming. The so-called American ostrich is actually a rhea.                           
         
         
         
        </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_kangaroo:entry"  >Kangaroo, Red</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_kangaroo:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
            
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/KangarooRed/Kangaroo_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/KangarooRed/Kangaroo_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="60"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>
                        
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Scrub</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_scrub.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Australia</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Scrub_Australia.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>
Order: Diprotodonts <i>(Diprotodontia)</i><br/>
      
                     Family:		Kangaroos                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Macropodidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Macropus  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>rufus</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/scrub_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Red Kangaroo Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A large kangaroo can travel up to 16 ft (5 m) in a single leap.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			When fighting, a larger kangaroo balances on its tail, grabs its rival with its forearms, and kicks with its hind legs.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			When in danger, kangaroos beat the ground with their back feet.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the red kangaroo in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            The red kangaroo is among the largest members of the kangaroo family. Kangaroo is the common name for a group of mammals found in Australia and neighboring islands. Kangaroos are marsupials, a type of mammal that gives birth to undeveloped young. In kangaroos and many other marsupials, the young are carried and nurtured in a special pouch on the mother's body.                                     
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
          
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                    		In Australia, the red kangaroo, Macropus rufus, has increased in numbers in response to people. Sheep     		ranchers favor this largest of the continent's native mammals by converting woodlands to grassland,     		providing sources of permanent water, and fencing out or killing the dingo. Even though it may be persecuted     		by these same ranchers as a competitor of their livestock, the red kangaroo has benefited overall, and its     		population stands in the millions.                           
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
       
         
         
         
         
         
       
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                    		Contributed By: Miles Roberts     		                        
            
            
            <br/>

            
                                                	Content provided courtesy of 	                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              		(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_redpanda:entry"  >Bear, Red Panda</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_redpanda:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
               <cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
                  <img src="entities/units/animals/PandaRed/PandaRed_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="16">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="16">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/endangered.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="155" b="0">
                     Endangered
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Temperate Forest</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_temperateforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	China</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Temperateforest_China.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Carnivores                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Carnivora)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Bears                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Ursidae)  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Ailurus</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>fulgens</i>
                     <br/>

                     Subspecies:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>fulgens</i>

                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/temperateforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Red Panda Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The red panda spends its days high among the tree branches of mountain bamboo forests, but spends its nights foraging for food on the ground.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Red pandas have long whiskers on their snouts, which help them navigate when foraging for food at night.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the red panda in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 4-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                            		Red Panda is the common name for a raccoonlike animal, similar in size to a large cat, with thick,             		reddish-brown fur. The red panda has pointed ears, stout limbs, and plantigrade feet (heel and toe touching             		the ground) with partly retractile claws and woolly soles. Like the          		                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_panda:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">giant panda</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                             	            		, the red panda has a sixth             		digit near the wrist that aids the animal in eating. The long, bushy tail has rings of red and yellow. Red             		pandas are found on steep mountains in western China and in the Tibetan Himalayas. They live in pairs and             		small groups in bamboo forests, on which they feed. They are nocturnal, sleeping in trees during the day.             		Breeding takes place from January to March, and the young are born three to five months later. The litter             		may include one to four, but most commonly two, offspring. In the past the red panda has been classified in             		the raccoon family and the bear family. More recently some scientists place the red panda in the family             		Ailuridae, which is separate from both the raccoon and bear families.                            
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of 	                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_giraffe:entry"  >Giraffe, Reticulated</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_giraffe:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/Giraffe/Giraffe_adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>            
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Savannah</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_savannah.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	East Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Savannah_Africa_East.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Even-Toed Ungulates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Artiodactyla)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Giraffes                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Giraffidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Giraffa  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>camelopardalis</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/savannah_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Reticulated Giraffe Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			A giraffe's neck can be over 1.5 m (5 ft) in length, but it contains only seven vertebrae.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     		Adult giraffes have no enemies other than 		                                                       
                     
                     <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_lion:entry">
                        <u>
                           <color r="255" g="231" b="135">lions </color>
                        </u>
                     </a>

                     and humans, as their huge hooves are very effective in defending against predators.		                                                      
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Giraffes are not great travelers, despite their long legs. 			They cannot walk over swampy ground because their hooves quickly sink, and they very rarely wade across rivers.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the reticulated giraffe in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 2-1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>

            
                                                The reticulated giraffe is one of the most striking subspecies of the giraffe, the tallest living animal, which is instantly recognizable by its exceptionally long neck. Male giraffes average about 5.3 m (17 ft) high, but some grow to a height of almost 6 m (20 ft)- tall enough to span two floors of a typical office building. Giraffes live in tree-scattered terrain in Africa.                        
           
            
            <p/>
            
            Female giraffes give birth in one of several specific "calving areas" in their home ranges, returning to these grounds to bear subsequent calves even if the larger home range has drifted geographically. Strong and well-developed at birth, calves nonetheless frequently fall to predators in their first year of life.
            
            <p/>
            
            After weaning, females stay within their mothers' territories, while males leave the range in all-male groups. Once a dominance hierarchy has been established among them, they wander alone in their own small ranges in search of females in heat. The sex of a grazing giraffe can be determined at a great distance with considerable accuracy. Almost invariably, males feed with their necks and often their tongues completely outstretched to reach the foliage of very tall trees. In contrast, females bend their heads over the tops of smaller trees.
            
            <p/>

            
                                                    		The giraffe is the better known of two species in the giraffe family. The other species is the     		                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_okapi:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">okapi </color>
               </u>
            </a>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
             an animal that was not even discovered by scientists until about 1900. Although much shorter than the     		giraffe, the okapi also has a long neck and eats leaves, and both animals have long tongues and     		skin-covered horns. The giraffe's ancestors first appeared in central Asia about 15 million years     		ago, but the earliest fossil records of the giraffe itself, from Israel and Africa, date back about     		1.5 million years.                           
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
        
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_lemur:entry"  >Lemur, Ring Tailed</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_lemur:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/LemurRingtailed/LemurRingtailed_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/vulnerable.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="255" b="0">
                     Vulnerable
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>            
           
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Tropical Rainforest                                                       
                     
                     <br/>
                  </color>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_tropicalrainforest.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Madagascar                                                       
                     
                     <br/>
                  </color>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Rainforest_Madagascar.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Order:		Primates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Primata)</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Family:		Lemurs                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Lemuridae)</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Lemur  </i>
                     <br/>

                           			Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>catta</i>

                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tropicalrainforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Ring Tailed Lemur Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			In the early morning, ring tailed lemurs like to warm themselves by sunbathing with arms outstretched.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Groups of ring tailed lemurs use their upright tails to keep track of each other when foraging for food in the open.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Male ring tailed lemurs sometimes engage in territorial "stink battles," in which they wipe their tails with smelly scent from their arms and then wave their tails at rival groups.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the ring tailed lemur in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 3-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            The ring tailed lemur, Lemur catta, is found only on the island of Madagascar and the nearby islands of Comoros. Adults of this species grow to 38 to 43 cm (15 to 17 in) in length and can reach weights of nearly 4 kg (9 lb). Their habitat ranges from tropical deciduous forest to semi-desert, and they are comfortable both on the ground and climbing trees.

            
            <p/>

            
                                                    		This fox-faced primate lives in a group of 10 to 20 or more of its fellows. In contrast to other more     		arboreal lemurs, the ring-tail, Lemur catta, spends much of its time on the ground. It inhabits the     		woodlands and forests of southwest Madagascar, where it subsists largely on wild figs and other fruits.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_leopard:entry"  >Leopard, Snow</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_leopard:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">

               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/LeopardSnow/LeopardSnow_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="96" width="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/endangered.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="255" g="155" b="0">
                     Endangered
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Alpine                                                       
                     
                     <br/>
                  </color>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_alpine.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Asia                                                       
                     
                     <br/>
                  </color>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Alpine_Asia.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:  	Carnivores                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Carnivora)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:	Cats                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Felidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>Uncia  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>uncia</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/alpine_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Snow Leopard Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The snow leopard has wide, furry paws that serve as snowshoes, preventing it from sinking into the snow.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The snow leopard is capable of making huge leaps over ravines and climbing bare rock faces in pursuit of prey.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Snow leopards have never been known to roar.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The snow leopard, native to the Himalayan mountains of Central Asia, has been known to range as high as 18,000 ft.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The snow leopard is considered to be a nocturnal animal, but it is most active at dawn and dusk.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The camouflage-like coat of the snow leopard renders it almost invisible in the rocky regions of its native habitat.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Although trading in snow leopard furs is illegal, it continues, threatening the snow leopard's existence.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			The snow leopard's diet consists mainly of wild sheep, goats and hares.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
         To unlock the snow leopard in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 4-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
         </color>
            <p/>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
         The snow leopard, also known as ounce, is a large mammal of the cat family which is found in the mountains of Central Asia. The animal's range extends from 2700 to 6000 m (8860 to 19,700 ft) in the summer, when the animals it eats migrate upward to graze on new grass. It has a thick layer of soft underfur covered by thick, long hair. The beautiful coat is pale gray, with black rosettes and small spots and a black streak along the spine; the underparts are whitish. The body length is about 1 to 1.3 m (about 3.3 to 4.3 ft) and the tail length is 0.8 to 1 m (2.6 to 3.3 ft). The animal is mainly nocturnal, and there are usually two to three cubs in a litter. Snow leopards have been overhunted for their fur and are now endangered.
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_gazelle:entry"  >Gazelle, Thomson's</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_gazelle:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/GazelleThomsons/GazelleThomsons_Adult_M_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
							<img src="entities/units/animals/GazelleThomsons/GazelleThomsons_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="16">
							<img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
						</cell>
						<cell width="60"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>               
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Savannah</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_savannah.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	East Africa</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Savannah_Africa_East.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                              		Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Order:		Even-Toed Ungulates                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Artiodactyla)</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Family:		Bovids                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Bovidae)</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Gazella  </i>
                     <br/>

                           			Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>thomsonii</i>
                     <br/>

                           			Subspecies:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>thomsonii</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/savannah_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Thomson's Gazelle Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			To confuse their enemies and to warn other gazelles, Thomson's gazelles bounce high into the air with their legs stretched down stiffly when alarmed. This behavior is called "stotting" or "pronking."		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Unlike deer, who shed their antlers, Thomson's gazelles retain their horns, which continue to grow throughout their lifetimes.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
         To unlock the Thomson's gazelle in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 1/2-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
         </color>
            <p/>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
         The Thomson's gazelle, which is 61 cm (24 in) tall, migrates between the African forests and the             		steppe. After the rains, it feeds on the fresh green grasses of the Serengeti Plain. Though usually             		found in herds of 20 or so, the gazelle will mass in the thousands for up to a few days. Its 30-cm (12-in),             		S-shaped horns offer some protection from predators, but its real defense is to flee.
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <cell width="280"/>
         <cell width="620">

            
                                                Content provided courtesy of                         
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_polarbear:entry"  >Bear, Polar</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_polarbear:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
            
               <cell width="284">
               <cell width="96" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/littleBox-128.tga">
                  <img src="entities/units/animals/BearPolar/BearPolar_Adult_F_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="16">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_male.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="16">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/icon_female.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="156"/>
                  <br/>   
                  <cell width="32" pady="0">               
                     <img src="ui/zoopedia/lowrisk.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="32" height="32"/>
                  </cell>                 
                  <cell width="224" padx="10" pady="0">
                     <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                     Conservation Status:
                     <br/>
                        <color r="170" g="255" b="0">
                     Lower Risk
                        </color>
                     </color>                  
                  </cell>
               </cell>             
            
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Tundra</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_biomes/icon_tundra.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="128" sh="128" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="128">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">	Arctic</color>
                  <br/>
                  <img src="ui/icon_maplocations/Tundra_Arctic.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="256" width="96" height="96"/>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="284" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">

                     Class:  	Mammals                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Mammalia)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Order:		Carnivores                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Carnivora)</i>
                     <br/>

                     Family:		Bears                                                        
                     
                     <i>(Ursidae)  </i>
                     <br/>

                     Genus:		                                                       
                     
                     <i>Ursus</i>
                     <br/>

                     Species:	                                                       
                     
                     <i>maritimus</i>
                  </color>
               </cell>
               <cell width="256" pady="10">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tundra_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <p/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="300">
            <cell width="64">
               <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-icon64.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
            </cell>
            <cell width="176">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <font name="arial" size="12" shadowx="2" shadowy="1" shadowa="50">      						Fun Polar Bear Facts      					</font>
               </color>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="280" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/factBG.tga" padx="10">
               <p/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Polar bears have black skin.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			For camouflage when hunting on ice, many polar bears hide their black noses with their paws.		</color>
               </cell>
               <br/>
               <cell width="32" pady="10">
                  <img src="ui/zoopedia/fact-bullet.tga" sx="0" sy="0" sw="32" sh="32"/>
               </cell>
               <cell width="202" pady="10">
                  <color r="255" g="255" b="255">			Female polar bears give birth while in a state similar to hibernation.		</color>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </cell>
         <cell width="340">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178">
            To unlock the polar bear in challenge or campaign games, you must earn a 3-star zoo fame rating for your zoo.
            </color>
            <p/>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            Polar bear is the common name for a white bear found on the sea ice of the Arctic throughout the North Polar             		basin. The only marine bear, it is longer than other 		                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_grizzly:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">bears </color>
               </u>
            </a>
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
             and streamlined for aquatic life. It has the             		plantigrade feet (heel and sole touching the ground) typical of bears, with five sharp, curved claws on each             		foot for grasping the ice and holding its prey. Long hair between the pads protects the bear's feet from the             		cold and provides traction on the ice. Stiff hairs on the forelegs, and very broad front feet, help the bear             		swim. All polar bears are white, although their fur may yellow in the summer. 		                                    
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
           
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                    		The largest wild bears ever weighed - more than 800 kg (1760 lb) - have been polar bears. However, most male     		polar bears weigh an average of about 350 kg (about 880 lb), and most females weigh about 250 kg (550 lb).     		Polar bears have a strong navigational sense, an extremely good sense of smell, and they are unusually     		clever at solving problems in order to obtain food. They eat primarily ringed seals, and occasionally     		bearded seals, walruses, or white whales. They also feed on berries, sedges, mussels, and kelp.  		                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                    		As with other true bears, polar-bear mothers and young form strong bonds. The young are very small when     		born: about 1 kg (about 2 lb). Their eyes remain closed for about 40 days and they must nurse every few     		hours. The mother holds them close to keep them warm. Except during the breeding season, male polar bears     		are solitary and roam over vast expanses of sea ice while hunting. During the breeding season (May to June),     		the males fight furiously over females. Both the male and female may mate with other individuals as well.                        
            
            
            <p/>

            
                                                      		Polar bears have little interest in other Arctic species, and they often ignore people entirely. Polar bears     		are hunted extensively in Canada and Greenland, and less so in Russia and Alaska. They are protected in     		Svalbard, Norway. Polar-bear populations are relatively secure because few people share their habitat, but     		shipping and offshore drilling for oil threaten their status.                                    
         
         
         
         </cell>
         <cell width="280"/>
         <cell width="620">
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
                               		Contributed By: Charles Joseph Jonkel    		                        
            
            
            <br/>

            
                                                	Content provided courtesy of 	                        
            
            
            <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
               <u>
                  <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
               </u>
            </a>

            
                                                              	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.                           
         
         
         
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>


      
</ZT2Strings>
