<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tropicalrainforest:entry"  >Tropical Rainforest Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tropicalrainforest:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tropicalrainforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  The tropical rainforest biome consists of woodland characterized by lush vegetation and comparatively high temperature and rainfall throughout the year. Rainforests are the world's most biologically diverse ecosystems. Although they account for less than 7 percent of the land surface on Earth, they contain more than 50 percent - some scientists estimate as high as 90 percent - of its plant and animal species. One hectare (about 2.5 acres) of tropical rainforest may contain more than 600 species of trees. By comparison, the forests of the United States and Canada combined contain only around 700 tree species. Even more impressive are the number and diversity of animal species that call rainforests their home. One study found more species of ants living on a single rainforest stump than exist in all of the British Isles.			
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  Rainforests also play a critical role in global climate regulation by absorbing carbon dioxide, a gas believed to be partially responsible for global warming. Plants naturally absorb carbon dioxide and give off oxygen gas in the process of photosynthesis, and tropical rainforests absorb more carbon dioxide than any other terrestrial ecosystem on earth.
				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                 
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
				There is general agreement among the scientific community that by absorbing some of the gas, rainforests play a vital role in lessening its impact.
				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
				To be classified as a rainforest, a forest must have a closed canopy, in which the treetops, or crowns, touch each other, creating a shaded forest interior. In addition, temperature and rainfall must be high and relatively even throughout the year. Forests that meet these criteria are found flanking the equator in South and Central America, Asia, Africa, and Australia. In South America, a vast, forested area of the Amazon River basin in Brazil and neighboring countries is by far the largest rainforest in the world. It encompasses more than 3.5 million sq km (about 1.4 million sq mi) - about half of the total global rainforest cover. The larger of two large rainforests in Asia is centered along the Malay Archipelago, including the islands of Borneo and Sumatra, the Malay Peninsula, and the Republic of the Philippines. The other main rainforest in Asia is found primarily on the island of New Guinea and in northern Australia. In Africa, most of the rainforest is concentrated along the Atlantic coast and the Congo River
 basin.			
               
               
               
              
               
               
                  
                 
                  
                  <p/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                   Content provided courtesy of
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135"> Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                   (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.

               
               
               
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_savannah:entry"  >Savannah Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_savannah:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/savannah_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					The Savannah 
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_biomedef:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">biome </color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                   is a tropical grassland with a scattering of shrubs and small and large trees. Savannahs may result from soil conditions, 
						from periodic fires caused by lightning or set by humans, or from climatic influences.
						
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
						Climatically determined savannahs, as found in western and southwestern Africa, develop in regions with marked wet and dry 
						seasons, where rainfall ranges between 100 and 400 mm (4 and 16 in) a year. These savannahs vary from open-canopied forests 
						with a grassy understory to true savannahs in which grasses are dominant. When the rainfall is 100 to 200 mm (4 to 8 in), 
						generally only grasses can survive the dry season. When rainfall reaches 300 mm (12 in), the soil holds enough water to 
						sustain shrubs through the dry season as well. When rainfall exceeds 300 mm, enough water is left to support solitary trees; 
						and when rainfall exceeds 400 mm, enough moisture remains during the dry season to allow trees to grow more densely and to 
						form a canopy, shading out the grasses
						
                  
                  
                 
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
						In regions of higher rainfall, such as eastern Africa, savannahs vegetation is maintained by periodic fires. Consuming dry 
						grass at the end of the rainy season, the fires burn back the forest vegetation, check the invasion of trees and shrubs, 
						and stimulate new grass growth. These savannahs are also influenced by large grazing mammals such as wildebeest and zebra. 
						When abundant, the animals can so reduce the vegetation that the grassy cover cannot carry a fire. Woody vegetation then 
						increases, changing savannahs to woodland. Such woody growth can be reduced, in turn, by large browsers such as elephants
						
                  
                  
                 
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
						Soil-determined savannahs include the llanos of Venezuela and the campos cerrados of Brazil. 
						The latter are characterized by a hard crust in the soil, formed by ferric oxides. Grasses grow in the soil above the crust; 
						trees grow where roots, following cracks in the crust, can reach deeper groundwater.
				
               
               
               
               
               
               
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                    Content provided courtesy of 
 
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004. </color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.

               
               
               
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_alpine:entry"  >Alpine Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_alpine:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/alpine_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					The Alpine biome, similar to the tundra biome, is found in high mountain areas around the 
					world. Harsh conditions cause vegetation to grow low to the ground in alpine meadows.
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					Tundra is the treeless plain that lies north of the northern coniferous forests and on the 
					Antarctic Peninsula in the southern hemisphere. 
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					Trees cannot survive in this biome because of the cold temperatures, high winds, and heavy 
					snowfall, as well as the permafrost, a layer of permanently frozen subsoil. Plant life tends 
					to grow low to the ground. In the summer, large numbers of birds migrate to the tundra to feed 
					on insects. Other animals found in this area include reindeer, wolves, fox, voles, and lemmings.
	   				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                     
					Content provided courtesy of 
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
				
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_boreal:entry"  >Boreal Forest Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_boreal:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/borealforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                                 
					The boreal forest biome, which consists of a great band of evergreen conifer forests, extends 
					around the Northern Hemisphere in the subarctic latitudes. Within this zone, the growing 
					season is brief and the winter is long and cold. These circumstances exclude most broadleaf 
					deciduous trees, which require more time to regrow their leaves than the subarctic climate 
					provides. Evergreen trees, on the other hand, are ready to resume photosynthesis whenever the 
					air grows mild enough. Furthermore, the compact, cylindrical shape and waxy skin of the 
					needlelike leaves retard moisture loss during the winter, when environmental water is 
					unavailable because it is frozen.
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					Compared with the forests of lower latitudes, the boreal forests - often called by their 
					Russian name of taiga - are rather uniform in structure and species composition. Trees, often 
					in dense stands of even age, dominate. Many assume a narrow, pointed habit that permits snow 
					to be shed readily. Ground vegetation within the shady forest is sparse, comprising low 
					shrubs, many of them in the heath family, and a layer of mosses. Another conspicuous feature 
					of the taiga region, from which the ice sheets retreated only about 10,000 years ago, is the 
					countless ponds and bogs that pock the flat and poorly drained terrain.
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					In Eurasia, the taiga spans the continent from the Russian Far East to Scandinavia. The 
					westernmost forests are very monotonous, but the number of species rises as one moves to 
					the east, and the forests of Hokkaido in northern Japan are comparatively diverse. An 
					exception to the evergreen character of most of the taiga is the deciduous larch forests 
					of eastern Siberia, where the bitterly cold winters of the continental interior make the 
					retention of any leaves, even needles, a liability.
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					The boreal forests of North America are richer in species than their Eurasian counterparts 
					but are in other ways similar. Because of the north-south alignment of North American 
					mountain ranges, taigalike conifer forests extend far into the temperate zone along the 
					spines of the Cascade Range and Sierra Nevada, the Rocky Mountains, and the Appalachians. 
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					Source: Encarta Interactive World Atlas
	   				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                     
					Content provided courtesy of 
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.	     
				
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_desert:entry"  >Desert Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_desert:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/desert_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					Desert is a term applied to regions of the earth that are characterized by less than 
					254 mm (10 in) of annual rainfall, an evaporation rate that exceeds precipitation, and, 
					in most cases, a high average temperature. Because of a lack of moisture in the soil and 
					low humidity in the atmosphere, most of the sunlight penetrates to the ground. Daytime 
					temperatures can reach 131° F (55° C) in the shade. At night the desert floor radiates 
					heat back to the atmosphere, and the temperature can drop to near freezing.
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                 
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					Most deserts arise due to atmospheric wind conditions. Warm air masses created two belts 
					of desert, one along the Tropic of Cancer and the other along the Tropic of Capricorn. Other 
					deserts result from the effects of ocean currents on landmasses, where cool air masses 
					carry fog and mist, but little rain, along coastal regions.
	   				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                     
					Content provided courtesy of 
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.	       
				
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_grassland:entry"  >Grassland Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_grassland:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/grassland_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Grassland is defined as an ecosystem in which grasses, sedges, and other forage plants 
               are the dominant vegetation. Although temperate grasslands may have more than 50 species 
               of vascular plants, and tropical grasslands more than 200, two or three species of grasses 
               usually dominate upward of 60 percent of the biomass above ground.
				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
				Grasslands are natural, seminatural, and cultivated. Natural grasslands occupy, or once 
				occupied, large areas of continental landmasses, including the prairies and plains of 
				North America, the pampas and paramos of South America, the veld of South Africa, and the 
				steppes of Eurasia. Temperate natural grasslands develop in regions characterized by an 
				annual rainfall between 250 and 750 mm (10 and 30 in), a high rate of evaporation, and 
				seasonal and annual droughts. 
				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
				Tropical grasslands develop in regions with marked wet and dry seasons. On the periphery 
				of these climatic regions, fire is important in maintaining grasslands by preventing the 
				encroachment of forests in moist regions and desert shrubs in semiarid regions.
				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
				Seminatural grassland occupies areas where moisture is sufficient to support forests. 
				Also called successional grassland, these areas resulted from deforestation and will 
				return to trees unless maintained by burning, mowing, or grazing. Cultivated grasslands, 
				such as hayfields and pastures, are artificially planted and maintained. They usually 
				consist of one or two species of grass and a legume such as clover or alfalfa. 
				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
				Native grasslands of the world support, or once supported, a diverse fauna. In North 
				America, large grazing herbivores such as the bison and their large predators were 
				dominant. Associated with such mammals are herbivorous rodents, including prairie dogs 
				and mice; seed-eating birds; hawks; snakes; and insects, especially grasshoppers. 
				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
				Grassland soils are inherently fertile. Due to low rainfall, soluble nutrients in the 
				soil have not washed away, and due to the absence of a tree canopy, the flourishing 
				grasses have built up organically rich topsoil. As a result, native grasslands of the 
				north temperate regions have been converted to grain crops such as corn and wheat. The 
				native grazing herbivores have been replaced by domestic cattle and sheep, and the large 
				predators have been destroyed. 
				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
				Contributed By: Robert Leo Smith
				
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                     
					Content provided courtesy of 
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.       	       
				
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_scrub:entry"  >Scrub Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_scrub:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <p/>
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/scrub_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  The scrub biome, also known as a chaparral, is type of shrub-land community that is dominated by small-leaved evergreen vegetation.			
               
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  Such habitats are characteristic of the Mediterranean type of climate with warm, wet winters and long, dry summers. The name is applied to the shrub lands of California and Baja California that are dominated by scrub oak and by the dense shrubs chamiso and manzanita.
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  Scrub is fire dependent. Fire wipes out decadent growth, disposes of accumulated litter, recycles nutrients, and stimulates new, vigorous growth from seeds and sprouts.
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_temperate:entry"  >Temperate Forest Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_temperate:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/temperateforest_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Temperate deciduous forests are the type of forest found in the eastern United States.
	       	       
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <br/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Forests composed of deciduous species - ones that periodically shed their leaves - grow in well-watered 
	       parts of the temperate zone in which a long, warm growing season alternates with a cold winter. 
	       Precipitation, as either rain or snow, tends to fall throughout the year.
	       
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Deciduous trees, shrubs, and woody vines, whether in the tropics or in the middle latitudes, drop their 
	       leaves during a time of drought. For woody plants in the temperate zone, winter is such a time. In regions 
	       where the winter is so severe that the ground freezes, water cannot be taken up by the plant roots. But 
	       even in milder areas, the cold air and winter winds would quickly suck the moisture from a plant through 
	       its broad, thin leaves if they did not fall first.
			
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       In the spring, the forest floor is carpeted with wildflowers that bloom in the sunlight that bathes 
	       the ground before the trees and shrubs regrow their shade-casting leaves. After the long season of growth 
	       and reproduction, the changing colors of the leaves signal the beginning of the woody plants' preparation 
	       for winter. The aspect of the forest during the cold season can be quite stark, although some evergreens 
	       may offer a bit of color. In colder parts of the deciduous forest region, approaching the coniferous 
	       forests to the north, transitional mixed forests of deciduous and evergreen species are the rule.
	       
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Temperate deciduous forests are almost entirely confined to the Northern Hemisphere, where they 
	       occur in three major tracts. In Europe, the zone of deciduous and mixed forests stretches from the 
	       British Isles and France through central and eastern Europe as far as the Ural Mountains. In East 
	       Asia, these forests clothe the Russian Far East, Korea, and Japan. Their counterparts in North America 
	       occupy most of the area from the Great Lakes to the Atlantic Ocean and south to the Gulf of Mexico. 
	       
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Although widely separated, these deciduous forests are much alike, not only in appearance but also in the 
	       groups of plants that compose them: birches, hornbeams, alders, beeches, oaks, chestnuts, lindens, elms, 
	       walnuts, maples, and ashes.
	       
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       A long history of human occupation of these wooded regions, especially in Eurasia, has reduced many 
	       forests to tiny remnants. In parts of western Europe, millennia of forest destruction have resulted in 
	       the development of extensive areas of treeless heaths. 
	       
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Source: Encarta Interactive World Atlas
	    
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                        
            Content provided courtesy of 
        	 
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                                
            (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.	       
				
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tundra:entry"  >Tundra Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tundra:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/tundra_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Tundra refers to the arctic plains encompassing most of the earth's terrain north of the coniferous forest belt, dominated by sedge, heath, willow, moss, and lichen. Similar plains, called alpine tundra, occur above the timberline in the high mountains of the world. 
               
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The Antarctic region has a few areas of tundra as well. Tundra climate is characterized by harsh winters, low average temperatures, little snow or rainfall, and a short summer season. 
               
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The arctic tundra, in particular, is influenced by permafrost, a layer of permanently frozen subsoil in the ground. The surface soil, which tends to be rocky, thaws in summer to varying depths. The combination of frozen ground and flat terrain on the tundra impedes the drainage of water. Held at the surface or saturating the upper layer of soil, the water forms ponds and bogs that provide moisture for plants, thereby counteracting the low precipitation. 
               
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                        
            Content provided courtesy of 
        	 
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                                
            (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
				
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_wetland:entry"  >Wetland Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_wetland:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/wetlands_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Wetland is defined as a geographic area with characteristics of both dry land and bodies of water. 
               
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <br/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Wetlands typically occur in low-lying areas that receive fresh water at the edges of lakes, ponds, streams, and rivers, 
               or salt water from tides in coastal areas protected from waves.  
               In wetlands, the surface of the water, called the water table, is usually at, above, or just below the land surface for 
               enough time to restrict the growth of plants to those that are adapted to wet conditions and promote the development of soils characteristic of a wet environment. Wetlands provide habitat for a wide variety of plants, invertebrates, fish, and larger animals, including many rare, threatened, or endangered species. 
               
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The plants and animals found in wetlands include both those that are able to live on dry land or in the water and 
               those that can live only in a wet environment. Wetlands are found on every continent except Antarctica and in 
               climates ranging from the tropics to the tundra. They occupy about 6 percent of the land surface of the world, 
               or approximately 890 million hectares (approximately 2.2 billion acres). 
               The United States contains about 111 million hectares (about 274 million acres) or approximately 12 percent of the 
               world's wetland.
	    
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
            Content provided courtesy of 
        	 
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                                
            (C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
				
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
