<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:intro"  >Elephant Herd Addition</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:overview"  >
         
         
         
         
                  A group of African elephants was scheduled to be culled in the Kingdom of Sironjia due to elephant overpopulation. Instead, they have been offered to the zoo that creates the best and most suitable habitat for the animals. One crated African elephant has been delivered to your zoo and can be found         near the front gate.          
         
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         
                  Create a wildlife exhibit for the elephant and ensure that its basic needs are met.         If you can demonstrate your ability to care for this species, you will be given three more animals of mixed gender to help you establish a thriving community.     
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:overviewshort"  >         A group of African elephants was scheduled to be culled in the Kingdom of Sironjia because of          elephant overpopulation. Instead, they have been offered to the zoo that creates the best and most suitable  habitat for the animals. Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock the sundial statue!      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:elephantpart1successoverview"  >         The Kingdom of Sironjia is pleased to be able to offer you the remaining African elephants. The animals will be delivered to your zoo shortly. The habitat conditions will be monitored by the International Society of Animal Wellbeing (ISAW) for the next 3 months. Should you fail to meet the basic needs for any of these animals, they will be removed from your zoo and donated to another facility.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:result"  >Elephant herd successfully added to your zoo!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:adoptelephant"  >Create an exhibit area to house your African elephant and then release it from its crate. Ensure that its environment need is met.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:finishadoptelephant"  >Great! Your new elephant seems content in its new exhibit area.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:meetneeds"  >Now that you have an appropriate exhibit, meet the basic needs of your African elephant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:finishmeetneeds"  >Excellent! You have met the basic needs of your African elephant!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:adoptfourelephants"  >Add the three crated African elephants to your elephant exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:finishadoptfourelephants"  >Great! All new elephants have been released from their crates.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:meetenvironmentfourelephants"  >Ensure your exhibit provides a suitable environment for your four elephants.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:finishmeetenvironmentfourelephants"  >Your environment is well suited to the four elephants.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:meetallneeds"  >Care for your elephants and strive to meet all needs. Their condition will be evaluated in three months.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:finishmeetallneeds"  >Your four African elephants have been well cared for! They are yours to keep.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:failedmeetneedsoverview"  >Unfortunately, ISAW officials are not satisfied that your facility is capable of providing adequate care for a herd of African elephants. The animals are being removed from your park and will be donated to an alternate facility.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:failedmeetneeds"  >Your animals did not do well in your facility. They have been sent to an alternate facility.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioGoals:finishmeetneedsoverview"  >ISAW officials are satisfied that your facility is capable of providing excellent care for your herd of African elephants. Your elephants are here to stay and the ISAW will contact you again should they become aware of other animals requiring suitable homes.      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:Cruelintro"  >Mistreated Animals</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:Crueloverview"  >
         
         
         
         
                  An unnamed zoo in North America has been operating in an unregulated and          uncontrolled environment. A series of animal abuse complaints brought against          the facility have initiated an official investigation. The animals were found          in poorly designed and poorly maintained facilities that did not provide for their  health and psychological well-being. These mistreated animals need          rehabilitative care.        
         
         
        
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         
                  Although your facility has so far only catered to small animals, you are one of the few in the area with vacant land. Due to the emergency nature of the situation, yours is the only facility capable of accommodating these animals. 
         
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         
          A herd of zebras and a pride of lions have been delivered to your zoo. Create exhibits large enough to accommodate these two animal groups, and then treat their illnesses  and provide basic care.     
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:Crueloverviewshort"  >         A series of animal abuse complaints brought against an unnamed facility have          initiated an official investigation and resulted in groups of animals being removed from the          zoo. Care for these mistreated animals in your facility. Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock the sundial statue!      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:Cruelsuccessoverview"  >Your zoo has been able to provide excellent care for these animals. In the meantime, the offending facility has been shutdown permanently and another group of animals has been delivered into your care! You have been given a cash grant of $8,000 to help defray the cost.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:Cruelresult"  >Abused animals restored to excellent health!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:Cruelaccomodatezebras"  >Create a habitat suitable for six common zebras.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:Cruelaccomodatelions"  >Create a habitat suitable for eight lions.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:Cruelmeetneeds"  >Cure any illnesses and meet the basic needs of these animals.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:finishCruelaccomodatezebras"  >The six common zebras are housed in a suitable habitat.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:finishCruelaccomodatelions"  >The eight lions are housed in a suitable habitat.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:finishCruelmeetneeds"  >All animals have been cured of illnesses and their basic needs have been met.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:Cruelaccomodatechimps"  >Create a habitat suitable for seven chimpanzees, and then cure their illnesses and meet their basic needs.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:finishCruelaccomodatechimps"  >Your chimpanzees are thriving!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:failedCruelscenario"  >Your %s has died! All abused animals have been shipped to another facility.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:failedCruelscenariooverview"  >Your %s has died! It seems your facility is not capable of providing adequate animal care. The surviving animals have been removed from your facility and will hopefully receive better care in their new homes.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditions:finishCruelscenariooverview"  >Congratulations! All of the animals removed from the offending facility have received excellent care in your zoo. Your efforts in preventing animal cruelty have been noticed by the wildlife community.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingintro"  >Smuggling Ring Exposed</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingoverview"  >         Authorities have exposed an international smuggling ring that was illegally trading          endangered animals. Many animals have been recovered in recent raids and are          desperate for suitable homes. You have been given the opportunity to obtain several          endangered animals if you can quickly prepare exhibits that will house them          successfully. You will receive a new crated animal near the front gate at a regular interval for as          long as you can maintain the happiness and welfare of the animals you have previously          received. Further shipments of animals will cease on first report that any animal          previously sent to your facility does not have its environment needs adequately met. You must make sure to          provide the animal with enough space in an exhibit area of the correct biome. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingoverviewshort"  >         Authorities have exposed an international smuggling ring that was illegally trading          endangered animals. Many animals have been recovered and are desperate for          suitable homes. If you act fast, several endangered animals can be yours. Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock the sundial statue!      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingFailureoverview"  >Sadly, you were unable to meet the environment need of your %s -- its exhibit was either too small or of the incorrect biome. It will be necessary for authorities to find an alternate solution.       </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingPart1Successoverview"  >You have successfully housed all of the animals rescued from an extensive smuggling ring. This Herculean effort on your part has ensured that these endangered animals will forever be protected from the threat of becoming merchandise on the black market.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingresult"  >Smuggling ring exposed! All animals rehabilitated.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingRedKangaroo"  >Time is of the essence! Create a habitat for the red kangaroo and release it from its crate.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingRedKangarooOK"  >The red kangaroo is content in its environment.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingBengalTiger"  >A new animal has been delivered! Create a habitat for the Bengal tiger and release it from its crate.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingBengalTigerOK"  >The Bengal tiger is content in its environment.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingGrizzlyBear"  >Another animal has arrived! Create a habitat for the grizzly bear and release it from its crate.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingGrizzlyBearOK"  >The grizzly bear is content in its environment.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingGorilla"  >Another animal delivered! Create a habitat for the gorilla and release it from its crate.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingGorillaOK"  >The gorilla is content in its environment.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingRhino"  >A new animal has arrived! Create a habitat for the black rhinoceros and release it from its crate.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingRhinoOK"  >The black rhinoceros is content in its environment.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingElephant"  >A new animal delivery... only a couple more! Create a habitat for the African elephant and release it from its crate.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingElephantOK"  >The African elephant is content in its environment.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingSnowLeopard"  >The last animal has been delivered! Create a habitat for the snow leopard and release it from its crate.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingSnowLeopardOK"  >The snow leopard is content in its environment.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingNeedPoints"  >Ensure the animals are happy and that their environment needs are met until the last animal has been delivered.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingNeedPointsDone"  >        Congratulations! All of the animals have been housed in appropriate exhibits and you've been able to         manage their happiness throughout the rush of placing all these new additions.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingAnimalUnhappy"  >An animal has become unhappy with its care or environment. Further animal shipments have ceased.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingAnimalDeath"  >An animal has died! Your facility is incapable of handling the influx of animals!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingPart2overview"  >        The animals you received were confiscated from a smuggling operation and had         likely been poached from game reserves. Many of them may have been separated from their         mothers while very young. It would be an incredible accomplishment to be able to return         these animals to the wild. A cooperative group has donated additional animals to your facility so that         your animals will have social companions. Meet the advanced needs of the animals so that you may release one animal from        each species back into their natural habitats.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingMeedAdvancedNeeds"  >Meet the advanced needs and release one of each species to the wild.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingMeedAdvancedNeedsDone"  >You have successfully released many endangered animals back into the wild!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRing:SmugglingRingPart2Successoverview"  >Congratulations!  You have successfully returned one of each species rescued from an international smuggling ring to their natural habitats, and your efforts are lauded by animal conservationists worldwide. In recognition of your efforts, you have been presented with a commemorative sundial which represents the timelessness of your achievement. You will be able to use this sundial in all of your future endeavors.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Camp2introlabel:Camp2intro"  >Prevent Animal Abuse</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioLabels:C2S1"  >African Elephant Rescue</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ElephantHerdScenarioLabels:C2S1short"  >African Elephant Rescue</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditionsLabels:C2S2"  >Combatting Cruelty</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CruelConditionsLabels:C2S2short"  >Combatting Cruelty</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRingLabels:C2S3"  >Smuggling Ring Exposed</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="SmugglingRingLabels:C2S3short"  >Smuggling Ring Exposed</LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
