<ZT2Strings>
   <ChallengePack1Text>
      <CHHygiene>

			The Animal Hygiene Association (AHA) has selected your zoo for a test program promoting cleaner zoos and zoo animals. If your zoo can go for 30 days without any of your animals reaching a pressing or critical hygiene need, the AHA will award you a cash grant of %s.

         <br/>

			Difficulty: Variable

      </CHHygiene>
      <CHHygieneShort>Run your zoo for 30 days without any animal reaching a pressing or critical hygiene need to receive a cash grant of %s.</CHHygieneShort>
      <CHHygieneSuccess>You've kept your animals squeaky clean for an entire month! The Animal Hygiene Association has presented you with a grant of %s in recognition of your achievement.</CHHygieneSuccess>
      <CHHygieneSuccessShort>Congratulations! None of your animals had a pressing or critical hygiene need during the evaluation period.</CHHygieneSuccessShort>
      <CHHygieneFailureShort>You failed to keep your animals from reaching a pressing or critical hygiene need during the 30 day evaluation period.</CHHygieneFailureShort>
      <CHHygieneFailure>Unfortunately you were unable to make it through the entire evaluation period without one of your animals reaching a pressing or critical hygiene need. Try to keep them cleaner next time!</CHHygieneFailure>
      <CHMatchingFunds>

			The Axel Charitable Foundation has declared your zoo eligible for their matching funds program, which helps out newer or smaller zoos. If you can raise more than %s in donations during the next 30 days the foundation will contribute an equal amount to your zoo.

         <br/>

			Difficulty: Easy

      </CHMatchingFunds>
      <CHMatchingFundsShort>Raise more than %s in donations during a 30 day period to receive a matching grant.</CHMatchingFundsShort>
      <CHMatchingFundsSuccess>The Axel Foundation was impressed with your fundraising efforts over the past month. They've awarded you a matching grant of %s.</CHMatchingFundsSuccess>
      <CHMatchingFundsSuccessShort>Your zoo received a matching grant from the Axel Foundation!</CHMatchingFundsSuccessShort>
      <CHMatchingFundsFailureShort>You failed to qualify for the matching grant program.</CHMatchingFundsFailureShort>
      <CHMatchingFundsFailure>Since you failed to raise the specified sum during the 30 day evaluation period, the Axel Foundation is unable to contribute matching funds to your zoo.</CHMatchingFundsFailure>
      <CHMatchingFundsStatus>So far you have raised %s of the %s you need to qualify for a matching grant.</CHMatchingFundsStatus>
      <CHFelineFan>

			Feline Fan magazine, the world's most famous cat publication, is doing a story on how big cats adapt to life in a zoo. If you can adopt one new species of big cat within the next 30 days, Feline Fan will base its article on your zoo and award you $1500 for promoting big cat conservation. The resulting publicity will focus public attention on your park and may make your zoo more famous.

         <br/>

			Difficulty: Moderate

      </CHFelineFan>
      <CHFelineFanShort>Add an additional new species from family Felidae to your zoo and Feline Fan magazine will pay you $1500 and help publicize your zoo.</CHFelineFanShort>
      <CHFelineFanSuccess>You added a new species of big cat to your zoo, and Feline Fan magazine has published a story about it in its latest issue. They've made a donation of $1500 to your zoo to recognize your efforts on behalf of feline conservation. The resulting publicity has helped make your zoo more famous.</CHFelineFanSuccess>
      <CHFelineFanSuccessShort>The Feline Fan article on your new cat species has made your zoo more famous!</CHFelineFanSuccessShort>
      <CHFelineFanFailureShort>You have failed to obtain an additional species in the Felidae family during the specified time period.</CHFelineFanFailureShort>
      <CHFelineFanFailure>The deadline for adding a new big cat species to your park has passed. Feline Fan was unable to include your zoo in their article and you've missed your chance to make your zoo more famous.</CHFelineFanFailure>
      <CHWildAnimalCoalition>

			The Wild Animal Coalition has initiated a publicity campaign encouraging prominent zoos around the world to return more animals to the wild. Because your zoo is so famous the Coalition has publicly challenged you to release two giant pandas to the wild within the next two months. If at the end of two months you've released two giant pandas and your zoo fame is still five stars, your guests will be much happier with your zoo. However, if at the end of the two-month period you've failed to release two giant pandas or your fame is below five stars, the resulting bad publicity will cause your zoo fame to fall.

         <br/>

			Difficulty: Challenging

      </CHWildAnimalCoalition>
      <CHWildAnimalCoalitionShort>Release two giant pandas into the wild and still have a five-star fame rating at the end of the two-month evaluation period.</CHWildAnimalCoalitionShort>
      <CHWildAnimalCoalitionSuccess>Well done! Two giant pandas have been successfully reintroduced to the wild, and your zoo is still as famous as ever. The Wild Animal Coalition has praised your efforts, and as a result your guests are delighted with your zoo.</CHWildAnimalCoalitionSuccess>
      <CHWildAnimalCoalitionSuccessShort>Success! You've released two giant pandas into the wild and kept your five-star rating.</CHWildAnimalCoalitionSuccessShort>
      <CHWildAnimalCoalitionReleaseFailureShort>You've failed to release two giant pandas into the wild during the required time period.</CHWildAnimalCoalitionReleaseFailureShort>
      <CHWildAnimalCoalitionReleaseFailure>The deadline for releasing two pandas into the wild has passed. The Wild Animal Coalition has criticized your zoo for failing to meet the deadline, and the resulting bad publicity has caused your zoo fame to fall.</CHWildAnimalCoalitionReleaseFailure>
      <CHWildAnimalCoalitionFameFailureShort>You've released two pandas to the wild, but you've failed to keep your zoo fame at five stars.</CHWildAnimalCoalitionFameFailureShort>
      <CHWildAnimalCoalitionFameFailure>Two months have passed. Although you've managed to release two giant pandas to the wild, you've failed to keep your zoo fame at the five star level. Word has spread that your zoo isn't quite what it used to be. Your zoo fame has fallen even further as a result.</CHWildAnimalCoalitionFameFailure>
      <CHTravelWorld>

			The Travel World travel agency is considering including your zoo in one of their vacation packages. Travel World wants to evaluate your zoo for a two-month period to make sure the zoo meets their standards. If you can run your zoo for two months without more than five different guests reaching a critical amusement need, Travel World will add your zoo to their vacation package. Additional guests will visit your zoo as a result. (Hint: children are amused by playground equipment, while adults are amused by statues and kiosks.)

         <br/>

			Difficulty: Moderate

      </CHTravelWorld>
      <CHTravelWorldShort>Run your zoo for two months without a total of five different guests reaching a critical amusement need and additional guests will visit your zoo.</CHTravelWorldShort>
      <CHTravelWorldSuccess>Excellent! Travel World's evaluation period has ended. They're very impressed with the way you managed to keep your guests amused, so they've added your zoo to their vacation package. You can expect additional guests to visit your zoo as a result.</CHTravelWorldSuccess>
      <CHTravelWorldSuccessShort>Success! Travel World has added your zoo to their vacation package. Additional guests will be visiting your zoo.</CHTravelWorldSuccessShort>
      <CHTravelWorldFailureShort>Unfortunately five or more of your guests have reached a critical amusement need, so Travel World has declined to add your zoo to their vacation package.</CHTravelWorldFailureShort>
      <CHTravelWorldFailure>Too bad! Five or more of your guests have reached a critical amusement need. Travel World has decided not to add your zoo to their vacation package because it isn't amusing enough for their customers.</CHTravelWorldFailure>
      <CHTravelWorldOneCritical>One of your guests has reached a critical amusement need so far.</CHTravelWorldOneCritical>
      <CHTravelWorldTwoCritical>Two of your guests have reached a critical amusement need so far.</CHTravelWorldTwoCritical>
      <CHTravelWorldThreeCritical>Three of your guests have reached a critical amusement need so far.</CHTravelWorldThreeCritical>
      <CHTravelWorldFourCritical>Four of your guests have reached a critical amusement need so far.</CHTravelWorldFourCritical>
      <PHAviaryMonthlyPhotos>Aviary Monthly Photo</PHAviaryMonthlyPhotos>
      <PHAviaryMonthly>

			Aviary Monthly magazine is preparing an article on the grooming habits of exotic birds for their next issue. If you can snap a picture of a common peafowl taking a dust bath, the magazine will pay you $1500 for the photo. (Hint: Peafowl only take dust baths when they have a high hygiene need!)

         <br/>

			Difficulty: Easy

      </PHAviaryMonthly>
      <PHAviaryMonthlyShort>Take a picture of a common peafowl taking a dust bath.</PHAviaryMonthlyShort>
      <PHAviaryMonthlySuccess>The editors of Aviary Monthly have received your peafowl photo, and it goes perfectly with their article on the grooming habits of exotic birds. They've given you $1500 for taking the picture.</PHAviaryMonthlySuccess>
      <PHAviaryMonthlySuccessShort>Aviary Monthly magazine loved your peafowl picture and have paid you $1500 for the photo.</PHAviaryMonthlySuccessShort>
      <stt_PeafowlDustBath>Take a photo of a common peafowl taking a dust bath.</stt_PeafowlDustBath>
      <PHWebSitePhotos>Web Site Photos</PHWebSitePhotos>
      <PHWebSite>

			The manager of your zoo's Web site has asked you for some new photos to help promote your zoo on the Internet. She'd like you to take pictures of any animal eating from a food dish, any land animal sleeping, and any animal running or chasing another animal. She says that if she adds those three photos to your revamped Web site, it will surely attract additional new guests to your zoo.

         <br/>

			Difficulty: Easy

      </PHWebSite>
      <PHWebSiteShort>

			Take three photos that show:

         <p/>

   			*  Any animal eating from a food dish

         <br/>

   			*  Any land animal sleeping

         <br/>

   			*  Any animal running or chasing another animal.

      </PHWebSiteShort>
      <PHWebSiteSuccess>Your photos have been posted on the Internet, and they're a big hit! Your zoo's new Web site has made your zoo more popular and attracted some additional guests. </PHWebSiteSuccess>
      <PHWebSiteSuccessShort>Your Web site photos have attracted additional guests to your park.</PHWebSiteSuccessShort>
      <stt_AnyAnimalEating>Take a photo of any animal eating from a food dish.</stt_AnyAnimalEating>
      <stt_AnyAnimalSleeping>Take a photo of any land animal sleeping.</stt_AnyAnimalSleeping>
      <stt_AnyAnimalRunning>Take a photo of any animal running or chasing another animal.</stt_AnyAnimalRunning>
      <PHSpeciesDiversityPhotos>Species Diversity</PHSpeciesDiversityPhotos>
      <PHSpeciesDiversity>

			The Species Diversity Fund has created a program to reward zoos that can prove they have happy, well-adjusted animals from a wide variety of different species. If you can take three photos of different animals exhibiting specific behaviors, the Species Diversity Fund will give you a specimen of a species you don't already have in your zoo. The particular photos they want to see are: an emperor penguin doing a preening walk, one okapi play chasing another, and a Nile crocodile blowing bubbles in the water.

         <br/>

			Difficulty: Moderate

      </PHSpeciesDiversity>
      <PHSpeciesDiversityShort>

	   		Take photos of the following behaviors:

         <p/>

   			*  An emperor penguin doing a preening walk.

         <br/>

   			*  An okapi play chasing another okapi.

         <br/>

   			*  A Nile crocodile blowing bubbles in the water.

      </PHSpeciesDiversityShort>
      <PHSpeciesDiversitySuccess>The people at the Species Diversity Fund were extremely impressed with your photos. You've convinced them that your zoo has a diverse and happy collection of animals. As a reward they've presented you with a new animal, which has been crated and placed near the entrance to your zoo.</PHSpeciesDiversitySuccess>
      <PHSpeciesDiversitySuccessShort>The Species Diversity Fund was impressed by your photos. They have presented you with a new animal.</PHSpeciesDiversitySuccessShort>
      <stt_PenguinPreeningWalk>Take a photo of an emperor penguin doing a preening walk.</stt_PenguinPreeningWalk>
      <stt_OkapiPlayChasing>Take a photo of an okapi play chasing another okapi.</stt_OkapiPlayChasing>
      <stt_CrocBlowingBubbles>Take a photo of a Nile crocodile blowing bubbles in the water.</stt_CrocBlowingBubbles>
      <PHRainforestCoalitionPhotos>The Rainforest Coalition</PHRainforestCoalitionPhotos>
      <PHRainforestCoalition>

			The Rainforest Coalition is preparing a series of newspaper ads that promote awareness of rainforest wildlife and its endangered habitat. They'd like you to provide them with pictures of rainforest animals doing specific things. If you can get the pictures the Rainforest Coalition will pay you $10,000. In addition, the publicity generated by the ads may make your zoo more popular. They're interested in photos of a jaguar cub pouncing, a chimpanzee eating fruit in a banana tree, and a Bengal tiger resting on a tropical rainforest rock.

         <br/>

			Difficulty: Challenging

      </PHRainforestCoalition>
      <PHRainforestCoalitionShort>

	   		Take photos of the following animal behaviors:

         <p/>

   			*  A jaguar cub pouncing.

         <br/>

   			*  A chimpanzee eating fruit in a banana tree.

         <br/>

   			*  A Bengal tiger resting on a tropical rainforest rock.

      </PHRainforestCoalitionShort>
      <PHRainforestCoalitionSuccess>The Rainforest Coalition has paid you $10,000 for your photos. Their newspaper ad campaign was a huge success. You've not only helped educate the public about rainforest animals--the publicity from the ads has attracted more guests to your zoo!</PHRainforestCoalitionSuccess>
      <PHRainforestCoalitionSuccessShort>Your photos of rainforest animals have earned you $10,000 and the resulting publicity from the ad campaign has attracted more guests to your zoo.</PHRainforestCoalitionSuccessShort>
      <stt_JaguarCubPouncing>Take a photo of a jaguar cub pouncing.</stt_JaguarCubPouncing>
      <stt_ChimpEatingBanana>Take a photo of a chimpanzee eating fruit in a banana tree.</stt_ChimpEatingBanana>
      <stt_TigerRestingRock>Take a photo of a Bengal tiger resting on a tropical rainforest rock.</stt_TigerRestingRock>
      <PHChildrensReaderPhotos>Animal Instincts</PHChildrensReaderPhotos>
      <PHChildrensReader>

			Children's Reader magazine is having a contest for the best animal photographs of the year. If you can get photos of giant pandas, red pandas, and beavers engaged in specific behaviors, you'll win the coveted Children's Reader Photo Award. Winning the award will make your child guests much happier with your zoo for a period of time.

         <br/>

			Difficulty: Challenging

      </PHChildrensReader>
      <PHChildrensReaderShort>

	   		Take pictures of the following animal behaviors:

         <p/>

   			*  A giant panda marking scent on a tree.

         <br/>

   			*  Two American beavers with a beaver lodge.

         <br/>

   			*  A red panda resting in a tree.

      </PHChildrensReaderShort>
      <PHChildrensReaderSuccess>Congratulations! The Children's Reader liked your photos so much that they've given you their Children's Reader Photo Award. Your young guests are delighted to see your zoo written up in their favorite magazine. Each child in your zoo is now much happier as a result.</PHChildrensReaderSuccess>
      <PHChildrensReaderSuccessShort>Your photos won the Children's Reader Photo Award, which made your child guests happier.</PHChildrensReaderSuccessShort>
      <stt_GiantPandaScent>Take a photo of a giant panda marking scent on a tree.</stt_GiantPandaScent>
      <stt_BeaversLodge>Take a photo of two American beavers and a beaver lodge.</stt_BeaversLodge>
      <stt_RedPandaInTree>Take a photo of a red panda resting in a tree.</stt_RedPandaInTree>
   </ChallengePack1Text>
   <awards>
      <ChildrensReaderPhotoAward_name>
         <font name="arial" size="10" shadowx="-1" shadowy="1" shadowa="32">
            <b>Children's Reader Photo Award</b>
         </font>
      </ChildrensReaderPhotoAward_name>
      <ChildrensReaderPhotoAward_pre_ltt>
         <font name="arial" size="10" shadowx="-1" shadowy="1" shadowa="32">
            <b>Complete the Children's Reader photo challenge to receive the </b>
            <color r="255" g="255" b="0" a="255">
               <b>Children's Reader Photo Award.</b>
            </color>
         </font>
      </ChildrensReaderPhotoAward_pre_ltt>
      <ChildrensReaderPhotoAward_post_ltt>
         <font name="arial" size="10" shadowx="-1" shadowy="1" shadowa="32">
            <b>Congratulations! You have received the </b>
            <color r="255" g="255" b="0" a="255">
               <b>Children's Reader Photo Award.</b>
            </color>
         </font>
      </ChildrensReaderPhotoAward_post_ltt>
   </awards>
</ZT2Strings>
