<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:easy"  >Easy</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:medium"  >Moderate</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:hard"  >Challenging</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:variable"  >Variable</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:GenericMoneyGrant"  >You have received a cash grant!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:GenericMoneyLoss"  >Cash has been deducted from your bank account!    </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:GenericRandomAnimal"  >Want a random animal?</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHgrantmoney"  >
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         Your local city council and animal welfare society want to run a "Free Admission" promotion at your zoo for community residents. They hope to deliver the message that proper        care and feeding is essential to all animals, and that domestic animals deserve the same attention        as the exotic animals in your zoo. They have agreed to pay you an upfront fee of $2,500. This        promotion will last for up to one month as long as your animals remain healthy. At the        end of the promotion period, if no animals became ill, you will receive an additional $2,500 and additional compensation for your lost admissions fees. If an animal becomes ill, the promotion will end        immediately. You'll receive no further compensation and the animal will be removed from your facility.                                   
         
     
         
        
         
         
         
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                         Difficulty: Easy                      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHgrantmoneyShort"  >       Run a "Free Admissions" promotion for one month.      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHgrantmoneySuccess"  >       The promotion period has ended and the animals in your facility have been receiving excellent care. City council considers the promotion a resounding success and have reimbursed you for the lost admissions during       the promotional period.      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHgrantmoneySuccessShort"  >       The promotion was a success! You've received an additional $2,500 and have been reimbursed for lost admissions!       </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHgrantmoneyFailure"  >Unfortunately your %s has become ill. City council does not feel that this is the message they wish to deliver and have cancelled the promotion. Your admission prices will return to normal, and you will not receive any additional funds for lost admissions. Also, the sick animal has been confiscated and sent to an alternate facility.      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHgrantmoneyFailureShort"  >You have failed to maintain healthy animals. The promotion is now over and your %s has been sent to another facility due to illness.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHgrantmoney2"  >
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            You've been approached by a venture capitalist who is certain that there is a buck to be made in creating a top notch zoo. He's ready to provide $10,000 in immediate funding. You will need to repay him at a rate of 40% of your donation income, up until the point where he has achieved a gain of $2,000 over and above his initial investment.                                   
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            Difficulty: Moderate                    
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHgrantmoney2Short"  >You've accepted a loan and are in the process of repaying it from your donation income. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHgrantmoney2Success"  >Your profitable facility has been able to repay the entire loan extended to you by venture capitalists. You can now enjoy your profits exclusively.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHgrantmoney2SuccessShort"  >Your loan has been repaid and your facility is in the clear!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBearConference"  >
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            Bear biologists from around the world are looking for a venue where they can hold a conference to share the latest research and management information about bears. They have agreed to hold their conference at your site and pay you a $2,000 site fee as long as you can add another species of Ursidae to your facility. According to the terms they have presented, you must have another species onsite within four months. If you fail, you will need to pay them a $3,000 cancellation fee.                                  
         
       
         
        
         
         
         
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            Difficulty: Moderate                    
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBearConferenceShort"  >Have two animal species in the family Ursidae in your zoo to be eligible to host a conference and receive a $2,000 fee.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBearSuccess"  >Excellent! Your recent addition of a new bear species to your park meets the requirements of the bear conference. $2,000 has been added to your account.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBearSuccessShort"  >Excellent! Your park features two species in the family of Ursidae.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBearFailureShort"  >Your park has failed to obtain two species in the Ursidae family in the required time period.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBearFailure"  >The deadline for adding a new bear species to your park has elapsed and the bear conference has been forced to book another venue. Per the terms of your agreement, $3,000 has been deducted from your account.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalTrade"  >
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                              The Zoological Cooperative Association (ZCA) is running a feasibility study to determine if member zoos can benefit from a program of trading species between zoos. As a member, you will exchange one of your species for a new species for a temporary one-month period. It is essential that you keep the new species healthy and achieve a donation income of $500 for your new species over this period. Otherwise, the venture will be financially unsuccessful. The study will determine if a regularly rotating exhibit cycle has a positive impact on zoo attendance and cash flow. If the venture proves to be a success, you will receive $2,500 for your efforts, and you will be able to keep the new animals.             
         
     
         
        
         
         
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                       Should you accept this challenge, the species on loan will be delivered crated near your front gate. At the end of this trial period, your original species will be returned to your zoo.                       
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                       Difficulty: Easy            
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalTradeRevealed"  >The ZCA has removed each %s from your zoo as per the terms of the study. Your new species, the %s, has been delivered crated to the area near your front gate. You have one month to earn $500 in guest donations for this new species.   </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalTradeFirstShort"  >Generate $500 in guest donations over a one-month period from the species (%s) on loan to your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalTradeFirstSuccessShort"  >Rotating species among member facilities has been a great success as proven by your donation income. Your participation was an asset to the study and you have received a cash grant of $2,500 and you can keep the new animals.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalTradeFailureShort"  >Unfortunately you failed to generate enough cash to indicate that species swapping is viable. The study has been cancelled and the loaned animals have been removed.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalTradeFirstSuccess"  >The ZCA has completed their study on the benefits of trading species among member zoos. Your results appear to be very positive and the Association will consider making this a regular benefit available to zoo members. You have been given a cash grant of $2,500, and you get to keep the new animals.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalTradeFailure"  >Unfortunately this exhibit swap has proven to be financially unattractive. Without donations of $500, the cost to transport the species exceeds the results obtained. The ZCA has cancelled the study and removed the animals on loan.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHGarbageStrike"  >
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                       The National Refuse Collectors (NRCU) union has just voted to go out on strike!  Pending the satisfactory negotiation of a new contract, your maintenance workers have walked off the job. It is expected that the strike action could last one month. You can pay a high-priced strike team $4,000 to handle trash cleanup until your maintenance workers return. Or, you can choose not to pay their fee and collect and clean the trash in your zoo yourself to avoid unhappy guests. Would you like to hire the strike team?                                    
         
     
         
        
         
         
         
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            Difficulty: Easy                    
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHGarbageStrikeShort"  >Clean your zoo for one month until your maintenance workers return.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHGarbageStrikePayShort"  >You've hired a strike team to clean your zoo for one month until your maintenance workers return.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHGarbageStrikeSuccessShort"  >Great! The strike is over and your maintenance workers are back at work. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHGarbageStrikePaySuccessShort"  >The strike team handled things successfully while your maintenance workers were on strike. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHGarbageStrikeSuccess"  >You've successfully handled the walk-out of your maintenance workers. All has been resolved and they are happy to be back at work.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalStress"  >
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            A national Zoo inspection agency has filed a complaint against your facility, citing that animals at your facility have been subjected to 'behavioral stress and unnecessary discomfort'. If you argue their claim, your zoo will be closed to the public for one month while they re-inspect the facility for ill or unhappy animals. If you do argue the claim and the animals are again found in poor condition at the end of the month, you will pay a $2500 fine.  If you do not argue the charge, your zoo will remain open to the public but you will be unable to adopt any new animals for one month. Do you wish to argue the claim?
         
    
         
        
         
        
        
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            Difficulty: Challenging                    
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalStressShort"  >Your zoo is restricted from adopting new animals for one month.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalStressArgueShort"  >Your zoo is closed. The condition of your animals will be monitored for one month.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalStressSuccessShort"  >The restriction on adopting new animals has been lifted. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalStressArgueSuccessShort"  >Your animals are in great shape. An apology has been issued and you have received a $5,000 payment for unnecessary hardship.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalStressArgueFailureShort"  >Your animals remain in poor shape. You have been fined $2,500.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalStressEnd"  >The inspection agency lifted the ban on animal adoptions. It is hoped that you will maintain an adequate facility as a result of this hardship.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalStressSuccess"  >The inspection agency has found no evidence of animal mistreatment and has rescinded their claim against your facility. As compensation for your lost income, they have paid you a one-time hardship fee of $5,000.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalStressArgueFailure"  >The inspection agency has again found evidence of animal mistreatment and has upgraded your violation status to red. They have fined you $2,500.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRandomAnimalChance"  >
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            You have the opportunity to obtain an animal that has been rescued from an illegally run animal "mill". The species has not been disclosed and your cost will be %s to ship the animal to your facility. While it is likely that the animal is in the Lower Risk category, there is also a good chance that it is vulnerable or endangered, in which case it would be a valuable acquisition. Should you accept this opportunity, your crated animal will be delivered to the area near your front gate.                                  
         
        
         
        
         
         
         
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            Difficulty: Easy                    
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRandomAnimalChanceShort"  >Provide a suitable environment for your new animal.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRandomAnimalChanceSuccessShort"  >Great! Your new animal will make a great addition to your zoo. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRandomAnimalChanceGreatSuccess"  >Congratulations! You've made a resourceful decision and have obtained an extraordinary animal at an excellent price.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRandomAnimalChanceSuccess"  >While you could have adopted an animal of this species at a lower cost, this animal is much better off in your care than that of the animal "mill," and your guests will still enjoy the new addition.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRandomAnimalChance2"  >
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            A private "benefactor" has approached your zoo and would like to make an anonymous transaction. They have an animal available, but they refuse to disclose what species. They've implied that it is a rare species, but won't provide a guarantee. They do guarantee that this is a legal transaction. They are offering the animal to you for their cost of %s and should you accept, your crated animal will be delivered to the area near your front gate.                                    
         
        
         
        
         
         
         
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            Difficulty: Easy                    
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRandomAnimalChance2SuccessShort"  >Great! Your new animal will make a great addition to your zoo. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRandomAnimalChance2GreatSuccessShort"  >You have been very fortunate to receive an extraordinary animal. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRandomAnimalChance2GreatSuccess"  >Congratulations! You've made a resourceful decision and have obtained an extraordinary animal at an excellent price.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRandomAnimalChance2Success"  >Unfortunately the anonymous "benefactor" did not accurately represent the facts. While you have received a healthy animal, it is not as exclusive as was implied and it is likely that you have overpaid. However, the animal is certainly better off in your care than in the hands of the unscrupulous "benefactor" and your guests will certainly enjoy your new addition.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRaffle"  >
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            The Health and Husbandry Association, a non-profit organization, is holding a 50/50 raffle and has offered to sell you a block of 10 tickets for %s. Their portion will be used to benefit the health of domestic farm animals nationwide. Would you like to participate in the raffle?                                     
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            Difficulty: Easy                    
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRaffleSuccessShort"  >Congratulations! You've won the 50/50 raffle!  </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRaffleSuccess"  >Congratulations! You've won the 50/50 raffle! You have received %s and the Health and Husbandry Association is grateful for your participation.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRaffleFailureShort"  >Too bad! You didn't win the raffle... but at least one of your guests did!  </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHRaffleFailure"  >The Health and Husbandry Association has drawn their raffle and one of your guests has won %s. Your guest is ecstatically happy and the Health and Husbandry Association is very grateful for your participation.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalSale"  >You've been approached by another zoo that is interested in obtaining one of your animals. In exchange for your animal, they have offered to make a generous donation to your facility. Would you like to release your %s to this facility in exchange for their donation of %s? Difficulty: Easy</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalSaleSuccessShort"  >Your animal is on its way to a new home and you have received a %s donation!  </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalSaleSuccess"  >You have donated your %s to another facility in exchange for their donation of %s. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalAwarenessDay"  >The board of directors of the National Animal Association has sent out a request to zoos nationwide. %s Awareness Day is two months away and they would like all member zoos to have at least one animal of this species on-site within that time period. Their promotional campaign will be extensive and if you have one of these animals in your zoo within two months, you will benefit not only from increased attendance but also from the %s cash grant available to all participating members. Difficulty: Variable</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalAwarenessDayShort"  >Have at least one %s in your zoo for %s Awareness Day in two months. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalAwarenessDaySuccessShort"  >%s Awareness Day was a hit! Zoo attendance was booming and you received the cash grant. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalAwarenessDaySuccess"  >Your participation helped make %s Awareness Day an enormous success. Zoo attendance was booming and the cash grant has been deposited to your account.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalAwarenessDayFailureShort"  >%s Awareness Day has come and gone. Too bad you couldn't participate. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalAwarenessDayFailure"  >%s Awareness Day has come and gone. Too bad you missed out on the cash grant. But even though you didn't receive the cash, you did see a small boost to zoo attendance due to the increase in the public's perception of zoos in general.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHEnrichingAnimals"  >
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            The Residential Family Society has begun a campaign promoting the benefits of enrichment and stimulation for pre-school children and is making the correlation that captive animals also benefit from enrichment and stimulation in their lives. They have issued a challenge to zoos nationwide to provide their animals with ample enrichment objects and have imposed a one-month deadline.                                   
         
         
         
        
         
         
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            Since your zoo is local to their headquarters, they have targeted your facility for extensive publicity. You will need to research six new enrichment objects and use them in your exhibits to demonstrate your commitment to animal enrichment.                                   
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            If you succeed, you will benefit from free publicity and a boost to your attendance. Should you fail to uphold their ideal they will be merciless in their criticism and you will likely see your attendance decrease.                                   
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
                                            Difficulty: Moderate                    
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHEnrichingAnimalsShort"  >Within one month, research six new enrichment objects and use them in your exhibits. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHEnrichingAnimalsSuccessShort"  >Your attendance increased due to positive press over the number of enrichment objects in your zoo. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHEnrichingAnimalsSuccess"  >The Residential Family Society was impressed that you were able to provide such a unique assortment of enriching items for your animals. Their words of support for the efforts of your facility were worth more than any advertising that you could have purchased. Your facility has received a notable boost to attendance. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHEnrichingAnimalsFailureShort"  >Your attendance suffered due to bad press over the lack of enrichment objects in your zoo. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHEnrichingAnimalsFailure"  >The Residential Family Society was disappointed at the lack of enrichment objects in your facility. Your animals seemed bored and under-stimulated and they felt this to be a poor example of the message that they were communicating. They were brutal in their assessment of your efforts, and your facility has definitely seen a drop in attendance as a result. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCompanions"  >An internationally funded conservation group has offered to send you an animal to allow you to set up a breeding situation. The cost to obtain this %s is %s. You may keep the animal for two months. If you successfully breed this animal within the time limit, the conservation group will issue a refund for your initial cost and the animal, and baby, are yours to keep. Should you fail to successfully breed this animal, the loaned animal will be returned to its owner and no refunds will be issued. Finally, if the animal meets with misfortune while in your care such that it cannot be returned to its owner, you will be forced to pay a %s penalty. Difficulty: Moderate</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCompanionsShort"  >Breed the animal on loan to you within a two-month period. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCompanionsSuccessShort"  >You successfully bred the animal on loan to your zoo and the animal and baby are yours to keep. Your fee has been refunded.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCompanionsSuccess"  >Congratulations! You have successfully bred the animal on loan to you. The animal and baby are yours to keep. Your initial fee has been refunded.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCompanionsFailureShort"  >You were unable to successfully breed the animal on loan to your zoo. It has been returned to its owner.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCompanionsFailure"  >The loan period has expired and the animal has been returned to its owner. Perhaps a subsequent breeding opportunity will produce better results. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCompanionsBadFailureShort"  >The animal on loan to you could not be returned to its owner! You've had to pay a penalty.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCompanionsBadFailure"  >The animal on loan to you appears to have met with misfortune and is unavailable for return to the owner! Per the terms of your agreement, %s has been deducted from your account.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalRelease"  >An internationally funded conservation group has offered you an incentive to release endangered animals to the wild in an effort to promote growth among old populations and make new populations of these animals self-sustaining. Their current research project involves the %s. You have been offered %s to prepare your %s for release to the wild. %s will be paid upfront and the remainder will be paid when the animal has been collected for its relocation to its natural habitat. Difficulty: Challenging</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalReleaseShort"  >Release one %s to the wild.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalReleaseSuccessShort"  >Congratulations! You've successfully released your %s to the wild!  </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalReleaseSuccess"  >Congratulations! You've successfully released your %s to the wild, enhancing the worldwide population growth of this endangered species. The remainder of your %s fee has been deposited to your account. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalReleaseFailureShort"  >You no longer can support the release of the %s to the wild. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalReleaseFailure"  >Regrettably, it appears that your zoo can no longer support the conservation effort for the %s. The conservation group funding the research project is disappointed that you failed to contribute to the effort to promote growth in the natural populations of these animals.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuest"  >You've received a tip that the CEO of a prominent and very wealthy corporation is planning to visit your zoo in the upcoming months. You've heard that %s's favorite animal is the %s and the rumor is that if this animal is in your zoo when %s visits, it is likely that you will receive a generous donation.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuestShort"  >Have a %s in your zoo before %s arrives.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuestSuccessShort"  >You had %s's favorite animal, the %s, and have received a generous donation.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuestSuccess"  >Congratulations! %s was impressed that you had the %s in your zoo and has chosen to make a generous donation of %s.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuestFailureShort"  >%s paid a visit to your zoo and was disappointed that you did not have the %s on display. Rumor is that %s made a donation to an alternate facility.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuestFailure"  >It's too bad that you did not have the %s on display during %s's visit. The rumor is that a donation of %s was made to an alternate facility that featured the %s.</LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
