<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapname:atlas"  >Atlas Mountains (M)</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapname:capegoodhope"  >Cape of Good Hope (M)</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapname:congo"  >Congo River Basin (M)</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapname:drakensberg"  >The Drakensberg (M)</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapname:kilimanjaro"  >Mount Kilimanjaro (M)</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapname:okavango"  >Okavango Delta (M)</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapname:sahara"  >Sahara Desert (M)</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapname:serengeti"  >Serengeti Plains (M)</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapdescription:atlasdescription"  >
   	In ancient Greek myths, these mountains in northwestern Africa were where the giant Atlas stood, holding the heavens on his back.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapdescription:capegoodhopedescription"  >
   	The Cape of Good Hope, on the southwestern tip of Africa, is home to a distinctive scrubland ecology known as the "fynbos."
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapdescription:congodescription"  >
   	The Congo River Basin is the world's second largest rainforest and home to thousands of different animal species.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapdescription:drakensbergdescription"  >
   	In southeast Africa the high continental plateau falls away abruptly, creating the scenic Drakensberg, the "dragon mountains." 
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapdescription:kilimanjarodescription"  >
   	Volcanic Mt. Kilimanjaro is the highest mountain in Africa. Its icy peaks are famous for their glaciers, even though the mountain is only a few degrees south of the equator.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapdescription:okavangodescription"  >
   		During the rainy season, the Okavango River is surrounded by lush wetlands. Yet the river never reaches the sea because it evaporates in the arid sands of the Kalahari Desert.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapdescription:saharadescription"  >
   		The vast Sahara Desert of northern Africa covers one third of the continent, an area about the size of the United States.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="mapdescription:serengetidescription"  >
   		More than a million wildebeest migrate across the Serengeti Plains every year, the most massive migration of large animals in the world.
   	</LOC_STRING>

</ZT2Strings>
