 <ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsIntro"  >A Mob of Meerkats</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsOverview"  >Your zoo wants to obtain more African animals. A nearby wildlife sanctuary has offered to donate two of their meerkats. There's no charge, but you have promised to take care good care of these small, sociable animals.       
         <p/>
         You will find the two meerkats in crates near the entrance to your zoo. Create an exhibit for the animals and meet all their basic needs. Once you've demonstrated that you can care for the creatures, the wildlife sanctuary may donate additional meerkats to your zoo.
         <p/>
         One thing to note about meerkats is that they are very good diggers. So good, in fact, that they can dig under many types of fences! If you don't have a fence that can keep them in you will either need to be clever when you design their exhibit or just catch them whenever they escape.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsOverviewShort"  >Your zoo has some new arrivals: mischievous meerkats. Can you care for these small, highly social creatures? Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock desert-themed buildings and objects.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsPart1SuccessOverview"  >You've done a fine job of caring for your meerkats! The wildlife sanctuary is so impressed with your efforts that they they're going to donate a few more. Actually, more than a few ... an entire mob of six meerkats! You'll find the meerkats crated near the entrance to your zoo. It will be a lot for you to handle, but these highly social animals refuse to be separated from each other.
      <p/>The wildlife sanctuary will check on the meerkats in two months. Should you fail to meet the basic needs of any of the meerkats, they will be removed from your zoo and donated to another facility.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsResult"  >The meerkats were successfully added to your zoo!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsAdoptFirst"  >Create an exhibit that contains your meerkats and meets their environment needs.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsFinishAdoptFirst"  >Well done! Your meerkats seem to be doing well in their new exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsMeetNeeds"  >Now that you have an appropriate exhibit, meet the basic needs of your meerkats.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsFinishMeetNeeds"  >You have met the basic needs of your meerkats!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsAdoptMore"  >Add the six crated meerkats to your meerkat exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsFinishAdoptMore"  >Great! All the new meerkats have been released from their crates.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsMeetEnvironmentMore"  >Be sure your exhibit provides a suitable environment for all your meerkats.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsFinishMeetEnvironmentMore"  >Your environment is well suited for the meerkats.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsMeetAllNeeds"  >Care for your meerkats and meet all their basic and advanced needs. Their condition will be evaluated in two months.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsFinishMeetAllNeeds"  >You've done a good job of taking care of your meerkats! They are yours to keep.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsFailedMeetNeedsOverview"  >Unfortunately, officials from the wildlife sanctuary are not satisfied with the care you are providing for the meerkats. The animals have been removed from your zoo and will be donated to another facility.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsFailedMeetNeeds"  >The meerkats did not do well in your zoo. They have been sent to another facility.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsFinishMeetNeedsOverview"  >Officials from the wildlife sanctuary have returned to check on the mob of meerkats they donated to your zoo. You've done a fine job of caring for the animals and the officials are delighted with the results! Your meerkats are here to stay.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsDonations"  >
To help spark interest in the meerkats, the wildlife sanctuary has made an additional offer. If you can earn $3,500 in donations from the meerkats, the sanctuary will donate a free meerkat enrichment object to your zoo!      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsDonationsGoal"  >(Optional) Earn $3,500 in donations from your meerkats and receive a free meerkat enrichment object.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsDonationsGoalDone"  >You received a free meerkat sentry post after earning $3,500 in donations from your meerkats.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsSentryPost"  >Guests are so delighted by the antics of the mischievous meerkats that they've donated more than $3,500. As promised, the wildlife sanctuary has donated a meerkat sentry post to your zoo. You'll find the meerkat sentry post in a crate near your zoo's entrance.
	  <p/>
	  The wildlife sanctuary has one final task for you. They're looking for a nice publicity photo for their Web site. If you take a picture of a meerkat inside a meerkat sentry post the wildlife sanctuary will donate $10,000 to your zoo!
	  </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsSentryPostSuccess"  >Well done! You've received $10,000 for your photo of a meerkat standing inside a meerkat sentry post.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsSentryPostGoal"  >(Optional) Take a photo of a meerkat inside a meerkat sentry post to receive a $10,000 grant.
	  </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:MeerkatsSentryPostGoalDone"  >You received $10,000 for your photo of a meerkat inside a meerkat sentry post.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdIntro"  >The Secretary Bird</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdOverviewShort"  >Can you capture the behaviors of this long-legged predator on film? Complete all of the scenarios in this campaign to unlock desert-themed buildings and objects.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdOverview"  >The secretary bird is a common sight in the savannahs and grasslands of Africa. Although these long-legged predators can fly, secretary birds spend most of their time on foot, striding over the landscape in search of lizards, insects, and rodents to feed on.
      <p/>
      The Raptor Protection Society helps protect birds of prey throughout the world. The society has donated a secretary bird to your zoo, which you will find crated near the entrance to your zoo. In exchange for the donation, the society wants you to take a series of secretary bird photos for the annual fundraising calendar. 
      <p/>
      The first two photos the society would like are:
      <br/>
			*  A photo of the secretary bird preening. (Hint: secretary birds preen when their hygiene need is high.)
			<br/>
			*  A photo of the secretary bird flapping its wings.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdGuests"  >The Raptor Protection Society wants to increase public awareness of the secretary bird exhibit at your zoo. If you can attract a grand total of 75 guests to your zoo, the society will give you a $20,000 donation.			
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdPart1Goals"  >
      Take the following photos:
      <br/>
			*  A photo of the secretary bird preening.
			<br/>
			*  A photo of the secretary bird flapping its wings.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdPart1GoalsDone"  >You have taken the first set of secretary bird photos. As a reward for your fine work on the pictures, you have been given a $10,000 bonus!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdBehaviors"  >The Raptor Protection Society was quite pleased with your first set of photos. Now the society wants you to photograph some of the secretary bird's more advanced behaviors.
      <p/>
      Take the following photos:
      <br/>
			*  A secretary bird using a pursuit ball. (Hint: the pursuit ball is available at 2 stars of zoo fame.)
			<br/>
			*  A secretary bird stalking live lizard food. (Hint: the live lizard food is available at 1 1/2 stars of zoo fame.)
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdPart2Goals"  >
      Take the following photos:
      <br/>
			*  A secretary bird using a pursuit ball. (Hint: the pursuit ball is available at 2 stars of zoo fame.)
			<br/>
			*  A secretary bird stalking live lizard food. (Hint: the live lizard food is available at 1 1/2 stars of zoo fame.)
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdPart2GoalsDone"  >You have completed the second set of secretary bird photos!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdBreed"  >
      The Raptor Protection Society was once again impressed by your secretary bird photos. The society would like just one more photo for the calendar: a secretary bird egg!
      <p/>
      Of course, before you can take a photo of a secretary bird egg, you'll need to obtain a male secretary bird and then breed your pair. (Hint: To encourage breeding, make sure all of the secretary birds' advanced needs are met.)
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdSuccessOverview"  >
Congratulations! Thanks to your photos, the Raptor Protection Society's calendar is sure to raise a lot of money to help protect wild birds of prey.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdOverallGoal"  >Use your camera to take photos of the secretary bird.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdPreenGoal"  >Take a photo of a secretary bird preening.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdPreenGoalDone"  >You have taken a photo of a secretary bird preening!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdFlapGoal"  >Take a photo of a secretary bird flapping its wings.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdFlapGoalDone"  >You have taken a photo of a secretary bird flapping its wings!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdPursuitBallGoal"  >Take a photo of a secretary bird using a pursuit ball.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdPursuitBallGoalDone"  >You have taken a photo of a secretary bird using a pursuit ball!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdLizardGoal"  >Take a photo of a secretary bird stalking live lizard food.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdLizardGoalDone"  >You have taken a photo of a secretary bird stalking live lizard food!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdEggGoal"  >Take a photo of a secretary bird egg.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdEggGoalDone"  >You have taken a photo of a secretary bird egg!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdGuestsGoal"  >(Optional) Have more than 75 guests visit your zoo to receive a $20,000 grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:SecretaryBirdGuestsGoalDone"  >Your zoo has had more than 75 guests!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityIntro"  >The African Diversity Zoo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityOverview"  >
You've been hired to build a new zoo that will spotlight the vast diversity of African wildlife. The zoo's board of directors would like you to create a zoo containing at least 14 different species of African animals. Your zoo may contain animals from other areas of the world as well, but they won't count toward your goal.
         <p/>
Since the intention is to spotlight Africa's natural diversity, the board doesn't want you to rely too heavily on traditional savannah species like zebras and lions. So only four of the 14 African species in your zoo can be savannah species!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityOverviewShort"  >You've been hired to create a zoo containing 14 African species, but only four of the species can be savannah animals. Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock desert-themed buildings and objects.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversitySuccessOverview"  >Your zoo's board of directors is pleased with your efforts! You've built a zoo containing 14 different African species, with only four savannah species. Congratulations on building a zoo that illustrates the diversity of African wildlife!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityResult"  >savannah animals on exhibit!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityFourSpecies"  >The board of directors has promised you a $20,000 grant after you have four different African species in your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityFourSpeciesSuccess"  >Now that you've obtained four different African species, the board of directors has given you a $20,000 grant! The board has promised you an additional grant of $40,000 after you obtain a total of eight different African species.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityEightSpeciesSuccess"  >Good work! You now have eight different species of African animals in your zoo. The board of directors has given you a $40,000 grant in recognition of your efforts.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityTwoScrub"  >
In addition, the board of directors has promised you a $10,000 grant if you obtain two different African species from the scrub biome.
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityTwoScrubSuccess"  >You've obtained two different African species from the scrub biome, and the board of directors has rewarded you with a $10,000 grant! The board has promised you an additional $20,000 grant if you can obtain two different species of African animals from the grasslands biome.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityTwoGrasslandsSuccess"  >You now have two different species of African animals from the grasslands biome in your zoo. The board of directors is delighted and has given you a $20,000 grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityOverallGoal"  >Adopt 14 African animal species (but only four can be African savannah species).</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityOverallGoalDone"  >Congratulations! You have succeeded in building an African wildlife zoo with no more than four African savannah species.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversitySavannahExcess"  >You have at least 14 African species in your zoo, but more than four of them are savannah animals.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityFourSpeciesGoal"  >Obtain four different species of African animals to receive a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityFourSpeciesGoalDone"  >You have obtained four different African species.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityEightSpeciesGoal"  >Obtain a total of eight different species of African animals to receive a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityEightSpeciesGoalDone"  >You have obtained eight different African species.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityTwoScrubGoal"  >(Optional) Obtain two different species of African scrub animals to receive a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityTwoScrubGoalDone"  >You have obtained two different species of African scrub animals.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityTwoGrasslandsGoal"  >(Optional) Obtain two different species of African grasslands animals to receive a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:AfricanDiversityTwoGrasslandsGoalDone"  >You have obtained two different species of African grasslands animals.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaign:newitemdesert"  >
Congratulations! You have unlocked the desert-themed buildings and objects!
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaignLabels:AfricaCampaignshort"  >African Adventure</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaignLabels:AfricaCampaignS1"  >A Mob of Meerkats</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaignLabels:AfricaCampaignS1short"  >A Mob of Meerkats</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaignLabels:AfricaCampaignS2"  >The Secretary Bird</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaignLabels:AfricaCampaignS2short"  >The Secretary Bird</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaignLabels:AfricaCampaignS3"  >The African Diversity Zoo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AfricaCampaignLabels:AfricaCampaignS3short"  >The African Diversity Zoo</LOC_STRING>
   
</ZT2Strings>
