	<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHUngulatesUnbound"  >Ungulates Unlimited, an animal conservation group, has agreed to donate a Thomson's gazelle to your zoo if you can acquire three African buffalo within one month. Difficulty: Easy</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHUngulatesUnboundShort"  >Acquire three African buffalo within one month.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHUngulatesUnboundSuccessShort"  >You have acquired three African buffalo and received a Thomson's gazelle as a reward.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHUngulatesUnboundSuccess"  >You now have three African buffalo in your zoo. In recognition of your efforts on behalf of hooved herbivorous mammals, Ungulates Unlimited has donated a Thomson's gazelle to your zoo. You will find the gazelle crated near the entrance to your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHUngulatesUnboundFailureShort"  >You didn't obtain three African buffalo within one month, so you did not receive a free Thomson's gazelle.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHUngulatesUnboundFailure"  >A month has passed since Ungulates Unlimited made their donation offer and you still do not have three African buffalo in your zoo. The donation offer has expired, so you will not receive a free Thomson's gazelle.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAcmeAmusements2"  >Your zoo has been contacted by Acme Amusements Inc., a firm that makes animal-themed gift items. Acme is considering donating a gift cart to your zoo, but first they want proof that your park is popular. If you have total attendance of more than 20 guests during your first month of operation, Acme will donate a gift cart to your zoo. Difficulty: Easy</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAcmeAmusements2Short"  >Have total attendance of more than 20 guests during the first month to receive a free gift cart.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAcmeAmusements2SuccessShort"  >More than 20 guests visited your zoo during its first month, so you received a free gift cart.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAcmeAmusements2Success"  >You're doing well! More than 20 guests have visited your zoo in less than a month! Acme Amusements Inc. is so impressed by your zoo's popularity that they have donated a free gift cart to your zoo. You'll find the gift cart crated near your zoo entrance.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAcmeAmusements2FailureShort"  >Fewer than 20 guests visited during the first month your zoo was open, so you did not receive a free gift cart.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAcmeAmusements2Failure"  >Your zoo has been open for more than a month, but you still haven't attracted 20 guests, so Acme Amusements Inc. has donated their gift cart to a more popular zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortium"  >The African Conservation Consortium is devoted to preserving African wildlife. The Consortium has offered your zoo a cash grant of $20,000 if you can breed three different species of African animals within three months. Difficulty: Challenging</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortiumShort"  >Breed three different species of African animals within three months.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortiumBredOne"  >You have bred one species of African animal. Breed two more to receive a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortiumBredTwo"  >You have bred two species of African animals. Breed one more to receive a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortiumSuccessShort"  >You have bred three species of African animals within three months and received a cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortiumSuccess"  >Congratulations! You successfully bred three different species of African animals within three months. The African Conservation Consortium is so impressed with your achievement that they have awarded you a $20,000 cash grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortiumFailureShort"  >You were unable to breed three species of African animals within three months.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortiumFailure"  >Unfortunately, you were unable to breed three different species of African animals within two three, so you have missed your chance to receive a cash grant from the African Conservation Consortium.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortium2"  >The African Conservation Consortium is impressed with your zoo and has offered you financial assistance. If you can earn $8,000 in donations from African animals during the next month, the consortium will award you $8,000 as a matching grant. Difficulty: Varies</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortium2Short"  >Raise $8,000 in donations from African animals within one month.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortium2SuccessShort"  >You raised $8,000 in donations from African animals and received a matching grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortium2Success"  >Your African animals are a big hit with your guests! You've managed to raise $8,000 in donations from African animals in less than a month. The African Conservation Consortium has awarded you an $8,000 matching grant. Even better, the publicity from the grant has made your zoo slightly more famous.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortium2FailureShort"  >You were unable to earn $8,000 from African animals within one month.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAfricanConservationConsortium2Failure"  >It's been a month since the African Conservation Consortium made their offer. Sadly, you have not been able to raise $8,000 in donations from African animals and you will not receive the matching grant.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHMasaiGiraffe"  >A local business tycoon wants to help bring more African animals to your zoo. If you can breed your Masai giraffe within the next four months, he's offered to donate a pair of white rhinos!  Difficulty: Moderate</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHMasaiGiraffeShort"  >Breed a Masai giraffe within the next four months to receive a pair of white rhinos.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHMasaiGiraffeSuccessShort"  >You bred your Masai giraffe within four months and received a pair of white rhinos as a reward.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHMasaiGiraffeSuccess"  >Terrific! You've bred your Masai giraffe. In addition to having a newborn to take care of, you have also received a pair of white rhinos as a reward. You will find the white rhinos crated near the entrance to your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHMasaiGiraffeFailureShort"  >You were unable to breed the Masai giraffe within four months.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHMasaiGiraffeFailure"  >You were not able to breed the Masai giraffe within four months, so you will not receive a free pair of white rhinos.</LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
