<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBackFromExtinction"  >
      Ancient Animals Monthly wants to do a feature story about animals brought back from extinction. If you can acquire animals from four different extinct species in the next two months, your zoo's name gets in the headline! Difficulty: Easy 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBackFromExtinctionShort"  >
      Acquire four extinct species in two months.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBackFromExtinctionSuccessShort"  >
      You successfully acquired four extinct species! You got $3,500 and your zoo is more famous!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBackFromExtinctionSuccess"  >
      You now have four extinct species in your zoo. Ancient Animals Monthly published a glowing review of your zoo, and it's the cover story in this month's issue! Your zoo just got more famous, and Ancient Animals Monthly gave you a $3,500 bonus!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBackFromExtinctionFailureShort"  >
      Because you failed to obtain four extinct species within the two months, Ancient Animals Monthly didn't get their story.  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHBackFromExtinctionFailure"  >
      You didn't acquire four extinct species in the two-month period. Ancient Animals Monthly ran their cover story on a rival zoo! Admissions to your zoo could slow for a while.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHExtinctDonations"  >
      The Aurochs Recovery Association wants to put one of its aurochs in a good home. There's no charge for the animal, but they want to make sure your zoo is a good fit. If you can prove your zoo is safe and financially stable by raising $1,500 in donations for extinct animals over the next two months, you get the aurochs. Difficulty: Easy
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHExtinctDonationsShort"  >
      Raise $1,500 in donations for extinct animals in the next two months to receive a free aurochs.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHExtinctDonationsSuccessShort"  >
      You collected $1,500 in extinct animal donations! Your new aurochs is on its way.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHExtinctDonationsSuccess"  >
      After raising $1,500 in donations, the Aurochs Recovery Association is pleased to send their precious aurochs to your zoo. You can find it in a crate near your zoo entrance.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHExtinctDonationsFailureShort"  >
      You failed to raise $1,500 in extinct animal donations in the past two months.  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHExtinctDonationsFailure"  >
      The Aurochs Recovery Association is concerned that your zoo won't be able to provide a good home for its aurochs. Since you failed to get the $1,500 in extinct animal donations, the association decided not to give you their aurochs.  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHQuarantine"  >
      A neighboring zoo has a sick female %s, and they need your help to nurse it back to health. Their animal has contracted a disease. If you accept this challenge, they will drop off the diseased animal at your zoo's front gate. You can slow or stop the spread of the disease by keeping the diseased animal away from your healthy ones. If you can eradicate the disease from your zoo within two months, you'll receive the animal's male mate free of charge, and you'll receive matching donations for your extinct species during that time. An animal infected with the disease will have a cloud of germs around its head. To cure the animal, go to your Extinct Research Lab and select the Disease Curing tab. Your research team should be able to help you find the cure for the disease. An animal is cured when germs no longer surround it.  

      Difficulty: Challenging
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHQuarantineShort"  >
      Uncrate the %s at your zoo gate, cure its disease, and eliminate any disease among the extinct animals in your zoo in two months.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHQuarantineSeedDisease"  >
      It spread to another animal in your zoo! Better find that cure -- quick!  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHQuarantineSuccessShort"  >
      You cured the sick %s and eliminated the disease!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHQuarantineSuccess"  >
      You've eradicated the disease from your zoo! Your extinct animals have some immunity to the disease now, but keep them healthy and clean to avoid another outbreak. Your new %s and a check matching the donations you earned for your extinct species are on their way!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHQuarantineDeathShort"  >
      Oh, no! One of your animals died from the disease.  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHQuarantineTimeFailureShort"  >
      You didn't rid your zoo of the disease within two months.  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHQuarantineDeath"  >
      Unfortunately, your animals, and even your guests, spread the disease quickly throughout your zoo. Now one of your animals has died. Remember, diseased animals should be kept far away from any guests and other animals so you can cure them without spreading the disease.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHQuarantineTimeFailure"  >
      You were unable to cure the %s and eliminate the disease in two months. You can continue caring for the animal, but its mate is in the care of another zoo. Remember, diseased animals should be kept far away from any guests and other animals so you can cure them without spreading the disease.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCaptureCavemen"  >
      Oh, no! Your glacier is melting and five prehistoric cavemen are loose in your zoo! It's up to you to round them up before they escape! Hint: To capture them, go into Zoo Guest Mode. Difficulty: Easy  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCaptureCavemenShort"  >
      Capture the wandering cavemen before they escape your zoo!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCaptureCavemenSuccessShort"  >
      You captured all the cavemen!  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCaptureCavemenSuccess"  >
      Because you could account for all your cavemen, you received a $3,000 grant from the International Prehistoric Security Fund -- and another glacier to put anywhere in your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCaptureCavemenFailureShort"  >
      One of your cavemen escaped! You received a $500 fine.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCaptureCavemenFailure"  >
      One of your cavemen escaped into a nearby park. A park ranger captured him and brought him back to your zoo. Unfortunately, your caveman violated a city ordinance against carrying big clubs, so you received a $500 fine!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:Caveman1"  >
      Grunt Rockbasher
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:Caveman2"  >
      Flint Boulder
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:Caveman3"  >
      Stone Fillmore
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:Caveman4"  >
      Slate Grindstone
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:Caveman5"  >
      Clyde Cavedweller
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCraftyCloning"  >
      Scientists around the world are competing for the coveted new Crafty Creations Prize! Your state-of-the-art Extinct Research Lab has everything you need to put your (and your animals') best feet forward. If you create three different animals of exceptional quality (a score of 90 or better), you win the prize and a $7,500 award! You have two months to earn this prize. Difficulty: Easy
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCraftyCloningShort"  >
      Create three exceptional animals from different species within two months to win the Crafty Creations Prize!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCraftyCloningSuccessShort"  >
      Your created three perfect extinct animal specimens! You won the Crafty Creations Prize!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCraftyCloningSuccess"  >
      Your skills in the Extinct Research Lab didn't go unnoticed. You won the Crafty Creations Prize! In addition to keeping your three perfect animals, you also won $7,500! You should have a few extra guests visiting your zoo this month because of all the positive publicity! 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCraftyCloningFailureShort"  >
      Two months have passed and your animals didn't quite make the cut. You didn't win the Crafty Creations Prize.  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHCraftyCloningFailure"  >
      Two months have passed and your animals weren't quite good enough to win the Crafty Creations Prize -- but you do get to keep them! Better luck next year. Keep practicing!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHKillerPenguin"  >
      A zoologist recently came upon a lone penguin wandering in the Arctic. Wanting to find a good home for it, she decided to donate the penguin to your zoo free of charge. Want a free penguin? Click the Check for yes or the X for no.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHKillerPenguinSuccessShort"  >
      You received a free penguin!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHKillerPenguinSuccess"  >
      Your new penguin sure doesn't look like any other penguin you've seen, but it's going to make an interesting addition to your zoo. You can find it crated at the front gate.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilFinding"  >
      A local paleontologists' union is approaching you with a unique offer to share information. They want some data on which fossils you are finding in your zoo. If you find all the pieces for an animal you haven't already discovered yet, they promise to share some of their fossils with you! This is a limited time offer. If you don't get it done in one month, they go to another zoo. Difficulty: Easy
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilFindingShort"  >
      Find all the pieces to a fossilized animal you haven't discovered yet.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilFindingSuccessShort"  >
      Your information sharing is a success! You can now build the %s at your Extinct Research Lab!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilFindingSuccess"  >
      The paleontologists' union was so happy you let them study your fossils that they donated some of their collection to your zoo! You can now build %s at your Extinct Research Lab -- without having to find all the pieces yourself!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilFindingFailureShort"  >
      You didn't find the fossils fast enough. The paleontologists' union decided to go to another zoo. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilFindingFailure"  >
      You didn't find the fossils fast enough. The paleontologists' union decided to go to another zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilBuilding"  >
      Researchers at the local science museum recently came across a collection of fossil pieces in storage. They need your help in putting these pieces together. They know that the fossilized bones are from the %s. If you assemble the pieces in one month or less, they are going to give you the research needed to create that animal in your Extinct Research Lab. They are asking for a $2,000 deposit, in case you aren't able to piece together their fossil. Don't worry -- you get the $2,000 back if you succeed. Difficulty: Easy 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilBuildingShort"  >
      Assemble the %s at the Extinct Research Lab.  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilBuildingSuccessShort"  >
      You managed to put together the %s! Now you can create it at the Extinct Research Lab. The museum also refunded your $2,000 deposit.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilBuildingSuccess"  >
      Congratulations! Once again your fossil-building skills are proven to be topnotch. The science museum uploaded all the files you need to create the %s in your Extinct Research Lab! They also refunded your $2,000 deposit.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilBuildingFailureShort"  >
      Looks like the fossil was too puzzling for you. The museum asked you to return their fossil pieces.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHFossilBuildingFailure"  >
      You weren't able to piece together the fossil pieces in one month. The museum asked you to return them, and they are keeping your $2,000 deposit.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCreation"  >
      Your sister zoo wants you to participate in an experimental new study in extinct animal research. They are offering to give you the data needed to create the %s in the Extinct Research Lab for $5,000. If you prove your skills by creating three super specimens of the %s in two months, you get a $5,000 grant to offset the costs and get the animal data. Difficulty: Intermediate
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCreationShort"  >
      Create three super versions of the %s at the Extinct Research Lab.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCreationSuccessShort"  >
      Whoa! You squeezed plenty of super out of your Extinct Research Lab! You received $5,000.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCreationSuccess"  >
      Once again you showed your skills at creating a family of super animals! Your sister zoo is pleased with the results. They awarded you the $5,000 grant.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCreationFailureShort"  >
      Two months have passed and you didn't create the required animals. You missed out on the $5,000 grant.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCreationFailure"  >
      Two months have passed and you didn't create the required animals. Your sister zoo couldn't complete its extinct animal experiment, and you missed out on the $5,000 grant.
      </LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
