<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_blackthorn:entry"  >Plant, Blackthorn Bush</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_blackthorn:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/BlackThornBush/BlackThornBush_Savannah_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
            		Blackthorn, species of plum, native to the eastern hemisphere, is also known as sloe or sloe plum. The blackthorn has short, stiff, very thorny branches that bear numerous small leaves. Its small white flowers give way to dark blue fruit that is about 1.3 cm (0.5 in) in diameter. The blackthorn can reach a height of 3 to 4 m (10 to 12 ft).
		</cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
            	Content provided courtesy of 
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="321" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_bananaleaf:entry"  >Plant, Banana Leaf Plant</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_bananaleaf:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/BananaLeaf/BananaLeaf_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
            The banana leaf plant looks very similar to a banana tree and has many of the same 
            characteristics, but is significantly smaller.
		</cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_gambagrass:entry"  >Plant, Gamba Grass</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_gambagrass:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/GambaGrass/GambaGrass_Wetlands_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Gamba grass is a tall, tropical perennial grass that forms large dense tussocks up to 
               70 cm (2 ft) in diameter.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Native to Africa, gamba grass was introduced to Australia’s Northern Territory and western 
	       Australia in the 1980s in an effort to encourage the growth of food plants for grazing 
	       animals.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       With its complex root structure that finds water deep beneath the surface, gamba grass 
	       stays green well through the dry season, but it can quickly become a major fire hazard 
	       when left to grow unabated during the long, hot summers of Africa and Australia.
      
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_papyrus:entry"  >Plant, Papyrus</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_papyrus:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Papyrus/Papyrus_Wetlands_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Papyrus, also paper reed, is a common name for a plant of the 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_sedge:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">sedge </color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               family. The plant grows about 1 to 
               3 m (about 3 to 10 ft) high and has a woody, aromatic, creeping rhizome. The leaves are long and sharp-
               keeled, and the upright flowering stems are naked, soft, and triangular in shape. The lower part of the 
               stem is as thick as a human arm, and at the top is a compound umbel of numerous drooping spikelets, 
               with a whorl of eight leaves. Papyrus grows in Egypt, in Ethiopia, in the Jordan River valley, and in 
               Sicily.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Various parts of the papyrus were used in antiquity for both ornamental and useful purposes, including 
	       wreaths for the head, sandals, boxes, boats, and rope. The roots were dried and used for fuel. The pith 
	       of the stem was boiled and eaten, but it was used mainly in making papyrus, the sort of paper that was 
	       the primary writing material of classical antiquity.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The papyrus of the Egyptians was made of slices of the cellular pith laid lengthwise, with other layers 
	       laid crosswise on it. The whole was then moistened with water, pressed and dried, and rubbed smooth with 
	       ivory or a smooth shell. The sheets of papyrus, varying from about 12.5 by 22.5 cm (about 5 by 9 in) to 
	       about 22.5 by 37.5 cm (about 9 by 15 in), were made into rolls, probably some 6 to 9 m (about 20 to 30 ft) 
	       in length. The Egyptians wrote on papyrus in regular columns, which in literary prose rarely exceeded 7.6 
	       cm (3 in) in width; in poetry the columns were often wider in order to accommodate the length of the 
	       verse.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The Greeks seem to have known papyrus as early as the beginning of the 5th century BC, but the earliest 
	       extant Greek papyrus is believed to be the Persae of the poet Timotheus, who lived during the 5th and 
	       early 4th century BC. The use of papyrus for literary works continued among the Greeks and the Romans to 
	       the 4th century AD, when it was superseded by parchment. It was still used for official and private 
	       documents until the 8th or 9th century.
      
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_cattails:entry"  >Plant, Cattails</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_cattails:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Cattails/Cattails_Wetlands_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
               Cattail is the common name for a tall perennial herb. It is characterized by a creeping rootstock; 
               long, flat leaves; flowers in dense cylindrical terminal spikes; and brown, cylindrical fruit with a 
               velvety surface. The plant grows in freshwater swamps, in both temperate and tropical climates, and is 
               occasionally cultivated along pond borders and in bog gardens. It grows and spreads rapidly when 
               sufficient water is present in the soil. The most common species, the common cattail, grows to about 1 to 
               2 m (about 5 to 9 ft) high. Another species widely distributed throughout the northern hemisphere, the 
               narrow-leaved cattail, grows to a height of 3 m (10 ft), and a species of California, Texas, Mexico, and 
               Argentina attains a height of about 5 m (about 18 ft) and an inflorescence of 1 m (3 ft). The leaves are 
               often used for making chair seats, mats, and baskets.
         </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_bluebush:entry"  >Plant, Bluebush</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_bluebush:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Bluebush/Bluebush_Scrub_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Bluebush is a shrub that is native to western Australian wheatbelt. Plants vary in size, 
               with the largest plants measuring 3 ft (1 m) high and 5 ft (1.5 m) wide. Bluebush grows 
               particularly well in salt marsh, swamps, and wetland areas.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Bluebush provides an excellent, nutritious food source for grazing animals.
      
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_sedge:entry"  >Plant, Sedge</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_sedge:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Sedge/Sedge_Grassland_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Sedge is the common name for a family of grasslike flowering plants with characteristically triangular 
               stems. The family is worldwide in distribution but is particularly abundant in wet, marshy areas of the 
               temperate and subarctic zones, where it is ecologically important in binding and stabilizing soils.The 
               family contains about 115 genera and 3600 species.
               
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Members of the sedge family typically possess a rhizome, a rootlike underground stem out of which grows a 
	       tuft of basal leaves. The leaf bases expand into sheaths that entirely close around the stem. The stem 
	       itself is usually unbranched and leafless, with a cluster of inconspicuous flowers at its tip. Each 
	       flower is borne in a single bract (modified leaf) and has either no perianth (floral envelope) or one 
	       reduced to a series of scales or bristles rather than showy petals. Sedges are generally distinguished 
	       from grasses by their triangular stems and by leaves with closed sheaths.
	       
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The family is of some economic importance. Stems and leaves of many genera, including the bulrush, are 
	       used for weaving mats, baskets, and hats, as well as in papermaking. The paper reed was the source of 
	       ancient Egyptian 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_papyrus:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">papyrus</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       . One genus in the sedge family includes species used for hay and packing 
	       materials. Cotton grass is used in pillow stuffing.
      
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_spinosa:entry"  >Plant, Spinosa Bush</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_spinosa:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/SpinosaBush/SpinosaBush_Scrub_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
               The spinosa bush is a dwarf shrub that is native to the arid and semi-arid regions of northeastern Africa, where it is a very important food source for grazing animals, especially the camel. 
               Due to its hearty nature and adaptability, ecologists in northern Kenya have experimented with using the spinosa bush as a solution to salty soil problems.
		</cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_flowerbed:entry"  >Plant, Flowerbeds</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_flowerbed:text"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <p/>
                  <img src="entities\objects\foliage\RedFlowerbedSmall\RedFlowerbedSmall_Zoo_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
                  <img src="entities\objects\foliage\WhiteFlowerbedSmall\WhiteFlowerbedSmall_Zoo_ icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
                  <img src="entities\objects\foliage\PurpleFlowerbedMedium\PurpleFlowerbedMedium_Zoo_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
                  <img src="entities\objects\foliage\YellowFlowerbedMedium\YellowFlowerbedMedium_Zoo_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
                  <img src="entities\objects\foliage\BlueFlowerbedLarge\BlueFlowerbedLarge_Zoo_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
                  <img src="entities\objects\foliage\OrangeFlowerbedLarge\OrangeFlowerbedLarge_Zoo_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64"/>
                  <br/>A bed of decorative flowers helps enhance the visual aesthetics of your zoo and creates a pleasing environment for your zoo guests.
               </color>
            </cell>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_desertgrass:entry"  >Plant, Desert Grass</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_desertgrass:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/DesertGrass/DesertGrass_Desert_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">Desert grass is an ornamental type grass that often grows in isolated tufts. Desert grass thrives in dry, hot, desert climates.	
      </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_elephantgrass:entry"  >Plant, Elephant Grass</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_elephantgrass:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/ElephantGrass/ElephantGrass_Savannah_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">Elephant grass is a tall, coarse grass that is native to tropical Africa and southern Asia. It grows in dense clumps up to 3 m (10 ft) tall, most commonly in moist soil along the lake and riverbeds of the African savannah.
                  <p/>The edges of its leaves are very sharp, making a patch of elephant grass almost impenetrable. Many different species of birds appreciate the protection a clump of elephant grass provides.
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_toadstools:entry"  >Plant, Toadstools</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_toadstools:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Toadstools/Toadstools_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
               Toadstools, also known as mushrooms, are technically confined to members of a family of fungi with gills, but in popular usage any of the larger fleshy or woody fungi. 
               The application of the term mushroom to edible species only and the term toadstool to those considered poisonous or otherwise objectionable has no scientific basis. 
               For example, two poisonous fungi may be less closely related than are a poisonous species and an edible one. 
               Of the thousands of species of mushrooms known throughout the world, the great majority are tough, woody, bitter, tasteless, or of such rare occurrence that they are of no interest as food. 
               A few species produce death or serious illness when eaten. 
               No simple rule exists for distinguishing edible and poisonous mushrooms, but the characteristics of the more common edible species can be readily learned, and collecting activities should be confined to such species. 
               Morels, puffballs, and other species described below are not ordinarily confused with dangerous types; whenever doubt arises, the only safe procedure is to discard all suspicious mushrooms. 
               Fresh commercially grown mushrooms can always be eaten with safety. 
		</cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_reindeerlichen:entry"  >Plant, Reindeer Lichen</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_reindeerlichen:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/ReindeerLichen/ReindeerLichen_Boreal_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
               Reindeer lichen, also known as reindeer moss, is a species of lichen of great importance in arctic ecosystems. It is the chief winter 
               food of reindeer, moose, and caribou. Reindeer moss is variable in form but typically has a many-branched, 
               erect, tubular thallus, or body, and small perforations in the axils. It grows very slowly and is easily 
               destroyed by overgrazing and fires. Reindeer moss grows most rapidly in spring and fall, when temperature 
               and humidity are highest. It readily concentrates pollutants and radioactive substances, which can be 
               harmful to the plant and to animals that eat it.
</cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_waterlily:entry"  >Plant, Water Lily</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_waterlily:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/WaterLily/WaterLily_Wetlands_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Water lily is the common name for a small family of aquatic flowering plants, and for its 
               representative genus. The family includes about 70 species. Its leaves are usually peltate, that is, 
               the leafstalk (petiole) is attached at the center of the leaf rather than at an edge. The leaves often 
               float on the water's surface, maintaining their position, even if the water rises, by continuing stalk 
               growth. Water lilies typically grow in quiet waters covering deep, saturated, oxygen-poor soils. Oxygen 
               needed for root growth is supplied by air passages extending down the leaf petioles. Many water lilies 
               are grown as pond ornamentals, and numerous hybrids have been produced.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Members of the representative genus, with floating leaves, are also called lotus. Two species were both 
	       represented in ancient Egyptian art. The family also contains the gigantic lilies of the Amazon.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The family is placed with three or four other families in an order that is cosmopolitan in distribution 
	       but restricted to freshwater habitats. In addition to being of aquatic habit, members of the order are 
	       characteristically herbaceous (nonwoody) and bear solitary rather than clustered flowers. The flower 
	       parts are usually numerous and unfused, traits found in orders that resemble the most ancestral flowering 
	       plants.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The lotus-lily family contains one genus, with two species: the sacred lotus, which is sacred to 
	       Buddhists, and the American lotus. The seeds and rhizomes of these lotuses are edible; the leaves are 
	       held above water on long stalks. The two species constituting the hornwort family are often grown in 
	       household aquariums. They grow totally submerged, usually even producing their flowers and fruits under 
	       water. They completely lack roots. The individual leaves are finely divided into narrow segments and grow 
	       in whorls at each node, giving the plants a raccoon-tail look. The water-shield family contains two 
	       genera and eight species of herbs; some are also used as aquarium plants.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Contributed By: Marshall R. Crosby
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_junegrass:entry"  >Plant, June Grass</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_junegrass:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/juneGrass/JuneGrass_Grassland_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               June grass, also known as bluegrass, is a blue-green grass found in North America and Europe, used for 
               fodder and as a lawn grass.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Grasses are the primary source of food for domestic and wild grazing animals, which feed on pastures 
	       and grasslands and which are fed hay and silage harvested from them. The total land area devoted to 
	       these kinds of croplands is greater than the land area for all other kinds of croplands combined.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_dandelions:entry"  >Plant, Dandelions</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_dandelions:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Dandelions/Dandelions_Grassland_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Dandelion is the common name for stemless perennial or biennial herbs of the composite flower 
               family, especially the common dandelion. The species has long taproots, rosettes of deeply incised 
               lanceolate leaves, and flat flower heads containing bright yellow florets on hollow, stemlike stalks. 
               The root of the common dandelion contains a substance used as a laxative; the root is also roasted and 
               ground as a substitute or adulterant for coffee. The leaves are used for salad greens and potherbs, and 
               the flowers are sometimes used for making wine. It is occasionally cultivated, especially in Europe, but 
               is found chiefly as a persistent weed in all temperate regions. The red-seeded dandelion is similar to 
               the common species, but is smaller, with reddish seeds and darker down. A Russian species has some 
               importance as a source of latex.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_arcticmoss:entry"  >Plant, Arctic Moss</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_arcticmoss:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/ArcticMoss/ArcticMoss_Tundra_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Arctic moss is a plant that, along with shrubs, grasses, herbs, and other low-growing plants, covers the 
               plains and coastal regions of the Arctic, forming tundra.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Moss is the common name for members of a division of plants (Bryophytes), native to the entire land area 
	       of the world. Mosses grow on soil, rocks, and the bark of trees, and in bogs and shallow streams. Moss 
	       plants consist of small, slender stalks and leaves; vascular tissue is not present. They lack true roots, 
	       the functions of underground support and conduction being carried on by filamentous structures called 
	       rhizoids. The organs of sexual reproduction, called antheridia and archegonia, contain sperms and egg, 
	       respectively, and are borne on the gametophyte, which is an independent leafy plant. Fertilization can 
	       take place only when the plants are wet; after fertilization, the egg grows into a sporophyte. The 
	       sporophyte consists of a base, or foot, embedded in gametophyte tissue; a stalk that is usually long 
	       and hairlike; and a terminal capsule. The capsule, which in most species is covered by a small-toothed 
	       lid, contains numerous spores. The spores are either released explosively or by special peristome teeth. 
	       Under suitable conditions they germinate by forming slender underground filaments called protonemata. 
	       Small buds produced by protonemata give rise to gametophyte plants. Mosses also produce gametophytes from 
	       such specialized vegetative organs as bulbils, produced by rhizoids; gemmae, produced on leaves or stems; 
	       and secondary protonemata, produced by rhizoids or wounded portions of the leafy shoot. The division is 
	       commonly divided into three classes: the liverworts, the hornworts, and the mosses.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Many mosslike plants, unrelated to the moss division, are commonly called mosses. These include Irish 
	       moss, or carrageen, which is a red alga. Iceland moss is a common name applied to a lichen and to a 
	       flowering plant also known as wild stonecrop. Rock moss is a common name applied to several lichens 
	       that grow on rocks, and to widow's-cross. Plants known as club moss are related to the ferns. Spanish 
	       moss, or long moss, is a flowering plant that grows as an epiphyte on tree trunks in the southern regions 
	       of the United States and in the West Indies.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_whitelillies:entry"  >Plant, White Lilies</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_whitelillies:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/WhiteLillies/WhiteLillies_Temperate_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">The white lily is a perennial plant that has layered bulbs, blade-shaped leaves, and single, large, sometimes trumpet-shaped flowers. 
               The flowers often have spotted petals and conspicuous protruding stamens. 
               The white lily was used as a medicinal plant until the 17th century, treating a range of maladies from scorpion stings and snakebites to stiff muscles and reproductive problems.
		</cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_larkspur:entry"  >Plant, Larkspur</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_larkspur:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Larkspur/Larkspur_Alpine_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  Larkspur is the common name for the members of a genus of flowering plants in the buttercup 
               family. The genus contains about 40 species, which are native to temperate regions in the northern 
               hemisphere. The flowers may be purple to pale pink in color; some species are also white. The flowers 
               grow in loose clusters, and the leaves are feathery in appearance. The name larkspur is sometimes used 
               interchangeably with the name delphinium, but the latter plants are now generally considered a separate 
               genus.
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_africandaisy:entry"  >Plant, African Daisies</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_africandaisy:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/AfricanDaisy/AfricanDaisy_Savannah_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">The blue-eyed African daisy is the most common species of Arctotis, a genus of annual plants native to southern Africa. They are grown in the United States in gardens that have good soil and sun. Arctotis blossoms last throughout the summer and autumn. The most common species is known as the blue-eyed African daisy. It grows to a height of more than 60 cm (24 in) and bears composite flowers up to 7 cm (3 in) in diameter with white rays and blue centers. The flowers close each night and open again the following morning. Dwarf forms exist, which have orange flowers.
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
            	Content provided courtesy of 
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_africanviolet:entry"  >Plant, African Violet</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_africanviolet:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/AfricanViolets/AfricanViolets_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="128" height="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               African violet is the common name for certain flowering plants often grown as houseplants. Unrelated 
               to violets, they are members of a genus in the family that also contains gloxinia, but their petals 
               are shaped like those of violets and are often violet in color. The genus contains about 20 species 
               of small, hairy, herbaceous perennials with clusters of long-stalked, fleshy leaves at the base. The 
               violetlike flowers are borne on loosely branched stalks that rise from between the leaves. All are 
               native to the mountains of Tanzania and Kenya in East Africa, and most are cultivated. Numerous 
               cultivars, including double-flowered forms and many color variations, have been developed from the 
               common African violet.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_junglelillies:entry"  >Plant, Jungle Lilies</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_junglelillies:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/JungleLillies/JungleLillies_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="128" height="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
               With its large, star-shaped petals and highly fragrant flowers, the jungle lily, also 
               known as the oriental lily, is one of the most popular (and profitable) flowers in the 
               worldwide cut-florist industry today. With their gorgeous colors and dramatic scents, 
               they are especially popular for weddings.
		</cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_lilyofvalley:entry"  >Plant, Lily of the Valley</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_lilyofvalley:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/LilyOfTheValley/LilyOfTheValley_Temperate_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Lily of the valley is the common name for any of a genus of perennial herbs. The cultivated species is 
               native to temperate Eurasia and is probably of introduced origin in North America. Lily of the valley is 
               a longtime favorite for shady gardens, where it will form a dense stand to the exclusion of all other 
               vegetation. The leaves are tongue-shaped, parallel-veined, and arise from ground level. The fruit is a 
               red berry. Flowers are tiny white bells (occasionally other colors) hanging from a single erect stem 
               about 30 cm (about 12 in) tall. Because of their fragrance, the flowers are used in the manufacture of 
               perfume. In cultivation, the lily of the valley is usually propagated from the terminal buds, called 
               pips, of the underground rootstock. Once established, populations tend to persist with great tenacity.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_fringedpolygala:entry"  >Plant, Fringed Polygala</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_fringedpolygala:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/FringedPolygala/FringedPolygala_Boreal_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Although it looks like an orchid, the fringed polygala flower, also known as gaywings or 
               flowering wintergreen, is a member of the milkwort family. Milkwort is common name for a 
               family of mostly tropical trees and climbers, and for its representative genus. This 
               low-growing flower grows well in damp forest settings.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
           	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_proteawildflowers:entry"  >Plant, Protea Wildflowers</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_proteawildflowers:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/ProteaWildflowers/ProteaWildflowers_Desert_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
         Protea is an evergreen shrub with dense flowers. Native to northern Africa, protea is grown for its 
               colorful bracts and dense flower heads.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_baobab:entry"  >Tree, Baobab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_baobab:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Baobob/Baobob_Savannah_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The baobab is a large African tree, found primarily in semiarid regions, where it is highly valued by 
               many African peoples.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The baobab tree grows only to the height of a large 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_maple:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">maple </color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       tree (about 15 m/50 ft), but the trunk 
	       sometimes attains a diameter of 9 m (30 ft), making it one of the world's largest trees. Only the 
	       sequoia and the eucalyptus have greater trunk diameters. The branches, frequently as thick as the 
	       trunks of other large trees, form a hemispherical mass of foliage often 45 m (150 ft) in diameter. 
	       The large diameters of the trunk and the tree's lower limbs allow the tree to store large amounts of 
	       water. During the dry season, baobabs drop their leaves to conserve much of the water that would be 
	       lost through transpiration.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The baobab provides food and shelter for many animals. The baobab fruit, commonly called monkey bread, 
	       is about the size of a grapefruit. People eat the fruit and use pulp from the tree to prepare cooling 
	       drinks. In addition, the bark of the tree yields a strong cordage fiber. 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The baobab holds spiritual significance for some peoples living in the Sudanic savannah region of West 
	       Africa, including the Serer, the Wolof, and the Mandinka. Their griots - community oral historians, 
	       storytellers, and praise singers - have traditionally been buried in baobab trunks because griots are 
	       believed too sacred to be buried in the ground. The Jola people of Senegal revere baobabs because of 
	       the spirits that are said to live inside them. The Jola also believe that baobabs are harbingers of 
	       the rainy season because they produce leaves just before the rain arrives. 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                 
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_umbrellaacacia:entry"  >Tree, Umbrella Acacia</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_umbrellaacacia:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/UmbrellaAcacia/UmbrellaAcacia_Savannah_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The umbrella acacia is one of the most recognizable trees of the African savannah. It belongs to the 
               acacia family, an important genus of trees or shrubs of the legume family. Most of the 1,200 species 
               of the genus are native to tropical Africa or Australia. The normal type of leaf is bipinnate, but it 
               is often modified, especially among the species that have had to adapt to the intense heat and drought 
               of Australia. The Australian species have vertical phyllodes that are modified leaves. The genus is of 
               great and varied economic importance, yielding edible seeds and valuable timber and gum.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                 
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_acaciacaffra:entry"  >Tree, Acacia Caffra</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_acaciacaffra:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/AcaciaCaffra/AcaciaCaffra_Savannah_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The acacia caffra, also known as cat thorn, belongs to the acacia family, an important genus of trees 
               or shrubs of the legume family. Most of the 1,200 species of the genus are native to tropical Africa 
               or Australia. The normal type of leaf is bipinnate, but it is often modified, especially among the 
               species that have had to adapt to the intense heat and drought of Australia. The Australian species 
               have vertical phyllodes that are modified leaves. The genus is of great and varied economic importance, 
               yielding edible seeds and valuable timber and gum.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_orchid:entry"  >Tree, Orchid</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_orchid:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Orchid/Orchid_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Orchid is the common name for about 250 species of tropical trees, shrubs, and woody vines belonging to the legume family. 
               Many species of orchid tree have large, showy flowers ranging in color from lavender to purple and generally blooming in late winter. 
               One species of orchid tree, the Saint Thomas tree, is a shrub that grows up to 5 m (15 ft) tall. It is planted as an ornamental in warm climates.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_elephantear:entry"  >Tree, Elephant Ear</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_elephantear:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/ElephantEar/ElephantEar_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                   Elephant's Ear is the common name for about eight species of large herbs of a genus of the arum 
               family, native to South America. The leaves, which give the plant its name, may reach a 
               length of 1 m (40 in) in some species. Several species are grown as house and garden plants in the 
               United States, including culcas, with shield-shaped leaves edged and veined in purple. Taro, which 
               grows in the islands of the Pacific, has large edible underground tubers. Like other members of the 
               arum family, elephant's ear plants contain calcium oxalate, which produces a burning sensation and 
               sometimes swelling in the mouth and throat if the leaves are eaten.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                 
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_kily:entry"  >Tree, Kily</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_kily:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Kily/Kily_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The kily tree, also known as the tamarind, is the common name for a tropical evergreen 
               tree, of the legume family, native to fertile areas throughout tropical Africa and 
               southern Asia. The tamarind is a large tree, attaining a height of 24 m (80 ft). The 
               extremely hard wood, which has been known to cause a spark when struck with an axe, is 
               used in cabinetwork.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Ring tailed lemurs love the fruit, seeds, and pods of the kily tree, which is cultivated 
	       widely in tropical areas of the eastern and western hemispheres as an ornamental tree and 
	       for its acidic fruits. The pale yellow flowers, arranged in loose, terminal racemes, have 
	       a four-parted calyx, five petals, three fertile stamens, and a solitary pistil. The fruit 
	       is a tapering, indehiscent (remaining closed at maturity), many-seeded pod. Tamarind juice 
	       mixed with sugar and water is a popular drink in Latin America.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_bananatree:entry"  >Tree, Banana</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_bananatree:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/BananaTree/BananaTree_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The banana tree, as it is commonly known, is not really a tree at all. It is a tropical, treelike 
               herb.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Banana is the common name for any of a genus of tropical, treelike herbs and also for their fruit. 
	       Species of the genus are native to Southeast Asia but are now grown extensively in all tropical countries 
	       for their fruit, fiber, or foliage. The banana is a large, herbaceous plant with a perennial root, or 
	       rhizome, from which the plant is perpetuated by sprouts or suckers. In the tropics the stems are 
	       annual - that is, they die after perfecting the fruit, and new stems are developed from buds in the 
	       rootstock. These stems, or buds, are the common means of propagating and making new plantations, and 
	       the growth is so rapid that the fruit is usually ripe within ten months after the offsets are planted. 
	       When fully grown the stem attains a height of 3 to 12 m (10 to 40 ft) and is surmounted by a crown of 
	       large oval leaves up to 3 m (10 ft) long, with a strong fleshy footstalk and midrib. The flowers spring 
	       in great spikes from the center of the crown of leaves and are arranged in whorl-like clusters along the 
	       spike; the female flowers occupy the base of the spike, and the male the apex. The fruits vary in length 
	       from about 10 to 30 cm (about 4 to 12 in). The average weight of a bunch is about 11 kg (about 25 lb), 
	       but individual bunches often exceed 18 kg (40 lb). A stalk bears only once, dies down, and is replaced 
	       by sprouts, two or three of which are allowed to bear fruit.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The fruit of the plantain, or cooking banana, is larger, coarser, and less sweet than the kinds that are 
	       generally eaten raw. The edible part of the banana contains, on the average, 75 percent water, 21 percent 
	       carbohydrate, and about 1 percent each of fat, protein, fiber, and ash. Other parts of the plant abound in 
	       fiber, which can be used in the manufacture of paper and cordage. One species is the source of Manila hemp.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Half of the world's banana crops are grown in Africa, and much of the produce is used locally. The 
	       leading banana-export regions are Central America and northern South America.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_kapok:entry"  >Tree, Kapok</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_kapok:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Kapok/Kapok_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The kapok tree belongs to the Ceiba genus, which is a common and scientific name for a large genus of 
               trees that reach a height of 40 m (130 ft) or more. They have palmate leaves and large, bell-shaped 
               flowers. Their thick, woody seed capsules contain a kind of fiber that resembles cotton.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The kapok tree, ceiba tree, or silk-cotton tree, is widely cultivated in tropical regions for its 
	       fiber, known as kapok. Because of its shortness, elasticity, and brittleness, the fiber cannot be 
	       spun like cotton but is used in various ways in upholstery and in making floss. Because of its 
	       lightness and water-repellent properties, kapok has been used in large quantities in life preservers 
	       and as stuffing and insulation. The principal supplies of kapok come from the island of Java. The 
	       seeds of the tree also yield kapok oil, used in making soap. The soft, spongy wood of the African 
	       variety, which is called bentang, is used for making canoes. The round seeds, the size of peas, are 
	       eaten on the Indonesian island of Sulawesi (Celebes).
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_redcedar:entry"  >Tree, Red Cedar</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_redcedar:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/RedCedar/RedCedar_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The red cedar is one of two arborvitae species native to North America; it's found west of the Rocky 
               Mountains from northern California to Alaska. Sometimes called the giant arborvitae or canoe cedar, it 
               may attain a height of 60 m (200 ft) under favorable conditions, and the trunk may exceed 4.5 m (15 ft) 
               in diameter.
	       Arborvitae (Latin for "tree of life") is the common name for certain related evergreen trees of the 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_cypress:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">cypress </color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       family, so named early in the 17th century because of the medicinal value ascribed to their 
	       balsamic resin. Extracts of this resin increase blood pressure and reduce fever. The leaves have a 
	       fragrant, balsamlike odor. The wood is reddish, light, and durable. Some of the larger species are 
	       valuable timber trees. The smaller species are cultivated in gardens and as wind screens for more 
	       tender plants.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_foxtailpalm:entry"  >Tree, Foxtail Palm</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_foxtailpalm:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/FoxtailPalm/FoxtailPalm_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The exotic-looking foxtail palm tree is a native of southeast Asia. It grows best in 
               sub-tropical or tropical climates. In the past decade, the foxtail palm has been listed as 
               an endangered species in Australia, but there are signs it is making a comeback.
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The foxtail palm is best known for its green arching fronds that resemble a bottle brush or 
	       the tail of a fox.
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_treefern:entry"  >Tree, Tree Fern</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_treefern:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/TreeFern/TreeFern_Rainforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The tree fern is a tall fern that resembles a tree. It is found in warm regions throughout the 
               world. The tree fern has a woody trunk, known as a caudex, which is tall and slender in some 
               species, and somewhat stout in others. At the top of the trunk is a rosette of large, graceful, 
               finely cut leaves, sometimes 3 m (10 ft) in length. Many tree ferns reach 4.6 to 9 m (15 to 30 ft) 
               in height. Species of the genus Cyathea may exceed 15 m (50 ft). Tree ferns are a beautiful feature 
               of tropical vegetation, and several species are planted in conservatories. 
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_birch:entry"  >Tree, Birch</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_birch:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Birch/Birch_Temperate_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Birch is the common name for a family of woody trees or shrubs that produce separate, abundant, tiny 
               male and female flowers in dense clusters. The family (see Beech) is widely distributed in temperate 
               and arctic regions of the northern hemisphere, reaching the southern hemisphere only in South America. 
               The family contains 6 genera and about 150 species.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Birch trees of the family's representative genus produce close-grained wood of uniform texture that 
	       is used in furniture, flooring, plywood, and veneers. Birch beer, once popular, is derived from the 
	       sap. The bark of paper birch was used by Native Americans to build canoes. Oil of wintergreen, once 
	       derived from the bark of sweet birch, is now manufactured synthetically. Several species are useful 
	       ornamentals, for example, the European white birch, which has many horticultural varieties. One genus 
	       is the source of hazelnuts and filberts, which have been used as food since ancient times.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The family also contains alder, hornbeam, ironwood or hop hornbeam, among others. Most are shrubs or 
	       short-lived trees that are too small when mature to provide useful lumber. Red alder of the Pacific 
	       Northwest is an important exception, providing wood for inexpensive furniture.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Members of the birch family exhibit several adaptations to fertilization by wind pollination, which is 
	       common throughout the group. Separate clusters of male and female flowers are produced on the same 
	       plant, developing in the fall and maturing in the early spring. Sepals and petals are very small or 
	       entirely absent, exposing the pollen-bearing stamens and pollen-collecting pistils to the wind. 
	       Enormous quantities of small, easily wind-dispersed pollen grains are shed in the spring by male 
	       flowers. The female flowers, however, are not fully mature when the pollen is shed; the styles and 
	       pollen-receiving stigmas have formed, but the ovules, which must be fertilized to mature into seeds, 
	       have not formed. The pollen remains lodged in the tissue of the styles for several weeks while the 
	       ovules mature. Fertilization and seed production follow this process.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_maple:entry"  >Tree, Maple</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_maple:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Maple/Maple_Temperate_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Maple is the common name for a small family of trees, widespread in the temperate areas of the northern 
               hemisphere, and for its representative genus. The family, which contains 2 genera and about 113 species, 
               is recognized by its opposite leaves and small, radially symmetrical flowers in loose clusters. The 
               flowers often lack petals. The ovary (female flower part) consists of two fused carpels (egg-bearing 
               structures), which mature into two winged fruits. Maples are widely grown as ornamentals and street trees 
               for their foliage and autumn colors. The species most commonly grown are medium to large deciduous trees 
               with lobed "maple-shaped" leaves, such as the one depicted on the Canadian flag.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Commonly planted species are red maple, sugar maple, black maple, and Norway maple. All these are natives 
	       of North America and Europe. Many of the Asian species differ radically from their western relatives. 
	       Some are small trees or bushes, some are evergreen, and some have entire (unlobed) leaves. The box elder, 
	       a maple native to much of the United States, has compound leaves with three to five leaflets. In addition 
	       to their ornamental importance, maples are a source of good timber, especially sycamore maple, and of 
	       sugar or syrup, especially sugar maple. The other genus of the family contains two species that are found 
	       in China.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <br/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Contributed By: Marshall R. Crosby
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_fountainbamboo:entry"  >Plant, Fountain Bamboo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_fountainbamboo:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/FountainBamboo/FountainBamboo_Temperate_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
		Bamboo is the common name for about 45 genera and about 480 species of perennial, woody, 
		usually shrubby or treelike plants of the grass family. Bamboos occur mostly in tropical 
		and subtropical areas, from sea level to snow-capped mountain peaks, with a few species 
		reaching into temperate areas. They are most abundant in southeastern Asia, with some 
		species in the Americas and Africa and none in Australia. The plants range from stiff 
		reeds about 1 m (about 3 ft) tall to giants reaching 50 m (164 ft) in height and 30 cm 
		(12 in) in diameter near the base. Most bamboos are erect, but some are viny, producing 
		impenetrable thickets in some areas.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_waterbamboo:entry"  >Plant, Water Bamboo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_waterbamboo:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/WaterBamboo/WaterBamboo_Temperate_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Water bamboo is an aquatic plant that isn't really bamboo at all. It does, however, closely resemble 
               bamboo, a treelike plant.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Water bamboo is the most popular indoor plant grown in China, and it is very popular with 
	       practitioners of Feng-Shui.
      
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_himalayanbirch:entry"  >Tree, Himalayan Birch</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_himalayanbirch:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/HimalayanBirch/HimalayanBirch_Alpine_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
               With its brilliant white bark that strips off easily, the Himalayan birch is one of the 
               rarest and most attractive trees featured in Zoo Tycoon 2. Native to the western 
               Himalayas and China, the Himalayan birch can grow to heights up to between 10 and 
               20 m (30-60 ft).
		</cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_blackspruce:entry"  >Tree, Black Spruce</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_blackspruce:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/BlackSpruce/BlackSpruce_Boreal_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The black spruce belongs to the Spruce family which is a common name for a genus of about 40 species of 
               coniferous trees, indigenous to the northern hemisphere, nearly half being natives of North America.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The Spruce genus, of the pine family, was formerly combined with a fir genus, from which it differs in 
	       having pendulous cones, persistent woody leaf-bases, and four-angled leaves, scattered and pointing in 
	       every direction. Spruces occur farther north than most trees, forming forests within the Arctic Circle, 
	       and extending south, especially in the mountains, as far as the Pyrenees in Europe and the Himalayas in 
	       Asia; in the United States, spruces occur as far south as North Carolina and Arizona. The white spruce 
	       and black spruce cover extensive areas in Canada, almost to the total exclusion of other trees. In Europe 
	       the Norway spruce is similarly distributed; the timber is valuable for fuel and for house building and 
	       is exported from Norway and Sweden for masts and spars of sailing vessels.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       In North America the prevailing species over the greatest extent of territory are the white spruce and 
	       the black spruce, although in lumbering the two species are seldom distinguished. The former is found 
	       from New York to British Columbia and northward to Newfoundland and Labrador, Hudson Bay, and Alaska. 
	       The white wood is light in weight, soft, compact, nearly odorless, and with scarcely distinguishable 
	       sapwood. It is used for general building purposes and also yields some of the spruce gum of commerce.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The black spruce has a distribution somewhat similar to that of the white, except that it descends along 
	       the mountains to Virginia. It is a somewhat smaller tree, but otherwise similar to the white spruce. It 
	       forms immense forests in Maine, New York, Canada, and elsewhere and is used largely for wood pulp and 
	       paper. A third species, the red spruce, a valuable timber tree, is limited essentially to New England but 
	       is also found along the Appalachians as far south as Georgia.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
           	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_balsamfir:entry"  >Tree, Balsam Fir</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_balsamfir:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/BalsamFir/BalsamFir_Boreal_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The balsam fir is one of 10 species of fir are native to North America, growing chiefly in the region 
               west of the Rocky Mountains. They achieve maximum growth in the Sierra Nevada and Cascade mountain 
               ranges. The balsam fir is found from Virginia to the island of Newfoundland and northwestward to the 
               Yukon and Labrador. It grows from 12 to 18 m (40 to 60 ft) high, and its leaves are highly fragrant and 
               resinous. The balsam fir, probably the best known of the true firs, is used for pulpwood and yields the 
               oleoresin known as Canada balsam. The noble fir, found in California, Washington, and Oregon, grows to a 
               height of 30 to 60 m (100 to 200 ft), with a trunk as large as 2.4 m (8 ft) in diameter. The alpine fir 
               is smaller than the noble fir, growing commonly from 24 to 30 m (80 to 100 ft) high. It is found from New 
               Mexico to Alaska in the Rocky Mountains. The lowland or grand fir, growing from Montana to the Pacific 
               Coast, at times reaches a height of 91 m (300 ft). True firs do not have the resin ducts that typify true 
               pines or spruce, although these trees all resemble one another in softness of wood.
               
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Fir is a common name for any of a genus of trees. The trees, known as true firs, generally have a 
	       straight trunk with somewhat pyramidal growth. The branches grow in whorls from the trunk. The cones, 
	       which are erect at maturity, are composed of thin, close scales. Each scale bears two winged seeds. The 
	       flat leaves are scattered, with the midribs showing clearly on the whitish undersides.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tamarack:entry"  >Tree, Tamarack</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tamarack:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Tamarack/Tamarack_Borealforest_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The tamarack, also called the American larch or hackmatack, occurs from Newfoundland and Labrador to 
               Alaska. The strong durable wood is used in rough construction and as poles, posts, and railway ties. 
               Western larch occurs in the northwestern United States and southeastern Canada. Its close-grained, 
               durable wood is used in flooring. The subalpine larch, occurs in the same areas as the western larch 
               but usually at higher altitudes. The European larch is an important timber tree in Europe, where it has 
               been planted extensively as a crop. It is grown in North America as an ornamental.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Larch is the common name for a small genus of trees, restricted to the colder parts of the northern 
	       hemisphere. Larches belong to the pine family and are unusual among the conifers (see Conifer) in that 
	       they are deciduous: their soft, needlelike leaves, borne in dense clusters, drop in the fall, and new 
	       leaves do not appear until the following spring. Of the ten species of larch in the world, three occur 
	       in North America. 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_himalayanpine:entry"  >Tree, Himalayan Pine</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_himalayanpine:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/HimalayanPine/HimalayanPine_Alpine_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The Himalayan pine is one of two coniferous trees that predominate in the northwestern Himalayan 
               region, where dense forests remain in the few areas where agriculture and commercial forestry have had 
               little effect.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Pine is the common name for a medium-size family of trees, mostly evergreen, of widespread distribution 
	       in the temperate areas of the northern hemisphere, and for its representative genus. The family, which 
	       contains about 210 species placed in 10 genera, has enormous economic importance as a source of timber 
	       and pulpwood, among other products. Members of the family characteristically have helically arranged, 
	       needlelike leaves. In several genera - for example, pine, cedar, and larch - the leaves are borne in clusters 
	       that are actually short branches, or spurs, on which the leaves are arranged in tight helices.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The members of the pine family have separate female and male cones; the former produce the seeds, and 
	       the latter, the pollen. Male and female cones are produced on the same plant; the seed-bearing cones 
	       are woody when mature; the seeds are winged. The family is distinguished from other conifers on the basis 
	       of its seed cones. Each of the flattened scales on which the seeds are borne is underlaid by a distinct, 
	       sterile bract (reduced leaf) that is usually shorter than the scale. The seed cones are drooping in all 
	       members of the family except the fir and a small genus confined to South China and Southeast Asia. All 
	       members of the family have evergreen leaves except the golden larch and the larch.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       The pine genus itself is the largest in the family, with about 110 species, about 35 of which are in 
	       North America. Pines grow in a wide range of habitats, from sea level to altitudes of 4000 m (13,000 ft) 
	       and are distinguished from other members of the family by the leaves, which are in bundles. Each bundle 
	       contains a specific number of leaves, depending on the species, with a sheath of short, scalelike leaves 
	       at the base.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Pines are divided into two groups, based on the scale leaves and other characteristics. The soft pines 
	       have leaves in bundles of five, and the scale leaves fall away from mature leaf bundles. Their wood is 
	       soft and has a coarse grain. Well-known soft pines are the eastern white pine, of northeastern North 
	       America; pinon pine, of the Southwest, the seeds of which are edible; bristlecone pine, the Rocky 
	       Mountain species; and the Great Basin bristlecone, which can live more than 5000 years and is the oldest 
	       known living thing on the planet. Through analysis of bristlecone rings, scientists can tell what the 
	       climate was more than 10,000 years ago. The hard pines have leaves in clusters of two or three, and the 
	       scale leaves persist in mature clusters. The wood is usually hard, with a close grain. Well-known species 
	       include lodgepole pine, extending from Alaska to Baja California; longleaf pine, of the southeastern 
	       coastal plain; and ponderosa pine, of the American West. Both pine groups are economically important for 
	       their timber, pulp, tar, and turpentine and for their use as ornamentals. Members of a pine family thought 
	       to be extinct for 50 million years were discovered in a rain forest near Sydney, Australia, in 1994. Other 
	       members of the pine family include Douglas fir, hemlock, and spruce.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_yellowcedar:entry"  >Tree, Yellow Cedar</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_yellowcedar:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/YellowCedar/YellowCedar_Alpine_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Yellow cedar is one of two trees of the western United States to which the name  
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_cypress:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">cypress </color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               is often applied. The other is the Port Orford cedar. These two trees are so-called false cypress.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_datepalm:entry"  >Tree, Date Palm</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_datepalm:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/DatePalm/DatePalm_Desert_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Date palm is the common name for several related trees found in tropical regions. The common date palm 
               is native to northern Africa, southwest Asia, and India and is cultivated extensively in hot, dry 
               regions throughout the world. The trunk is straight and rough and grows to a height of up to 18 m (up to 
               60 ft). It bears a head of waxy-green, barbed leaves, about 3 m (about 9 ft) long, and a number of 
               branching spikes that, on the female tree, bear 200 to 1,000 dates each. A cluster of dates weighs up to 
               12 kg (up to 25 lb), and the annual yield of a single tree may reach 270 kg (600 lb). The tree begins to 
               bear about the eighth year, reaches maturity at 30 years, and begins to decline at about 100 years. From 
               earliest times, fertilization has been aided by cutting off the male flower cluster just before the 
               stamens ripen and suspending it among the flowers of the female tree.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       In many parts of northern Africa, Iran, and Arabia, date palms are the main wealth of the people, and 
	       dates are the chief article of food. The fleshy part of the fruit contains about 58 percent sugar and 
	       2 percent each of fat, protein, and minerals. Leaf stalks are used for basketry and wickerwork, leaves 
	       are woven into bags and mats, and fiber from both is made into cordage.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Another species, the sugar date palm, or toddy palm, is cultivated in India for its sap. The sap may be 
	       boiled down to form jaggery, or gur, a crude sugar; or it may be used as a fresh beverage, or to make 
	       palm wine, from which arrack, a rumlike liquor, may be distilled.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Date palms are often cultivated in the southern United States for ornamental effect in regions too cool 
	       for the fruit to ripen. The blue date palm grows in clumps and has silvery blue foliage; the pygmy date 
	       palm is a dwarf species that is also popular in the north as a greenhouse plant or houseplant.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_camelthornacacia:entry"  >Tree, Camel Thorn Acacia</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_camelthornacacia:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/CamelThornAcacia/CamelThornAcacia_Desert_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The camel thorn acacia is a large, umbrella-shaped tree with feathery foliage that is a 
               common sight in both Africa and Australia. The leaves of the camel thorn 
               acacia are popular browse food for 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_elephant:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">elephants</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               , 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_giraffe:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">giraffes</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               , and elk, and the seeds have 
               sometimes been used by humans as a coffee substitute.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_mangrove:entry"  >Tree, Mangrove</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_mangrove:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Mangrove/Mangrove_Wetland_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">Mangrove is the common name applied to several kinds of tropical flowering plants that are members of three different families. Mangroves are trees or shrubs that have the common trait of growing in shallow and muddy salt water or brackish waters, especially along quiet shorelines and in estuaries. Typically they produce tangled masses of arching roots that are exposed during low tides. Some mangrove roots extend above the water. These specialized vertical branches, called pneumatophores, act as aerating organs. The most common and most important species, the red mangrove, is so named because of its reddish wood. It has been exploited as a source of charcoal and of tannins, which are used in preparing leather. Its seeds are unusual in that they germinate while still on the tree, sprouting seedlings that grow up to 30 cm (12 in) long. The seedlings are cigar-shaped and heavier at the root end than at the leafy end. Upon falling, they tend to plant themselves in the mud below the parent tree. Red, white, and button mangroves occur in southern Florida and in other tropical areas. The black mangrove is a member of the verbena family.
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
           	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_cypress:entry"  >Tree, Cypress</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_cypress:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/Cypress/Cypress_Wetlands_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               Cypress is the common name for several related coniferous trees and shrubs. The common cypress, native 
               to the Mediterranean region, is a symmetrical evergreen that resembles some poplars and often reaches a 
               height of more than 27 m (about 90 ft). It has a close-grained yellow or reddish wood so resinous that 
               it resists rotting even after prolonged submersion in water. The Monterey cypress is an even larger tree 
               found on the Pacific Coast in California. It sometimes grows as tall as 46 m (about 150 ft), with a base 
               trunk circumference of 3 m (10 ft). This cypress is normally symmetrical but is often distorted into 
               fantastic shapes by the action of the winds. Another true cypress is the cedar of Goa, or Portugal cedar, 
               which is often planted in the United States for the decorative effect of its spreading branches.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Among trees to which the name cypress is often applied are two trees of the western United States, the 
	       Port Orford cedar and the 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_yellowcedar:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">yellow cedar</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       , and a pine of the eastern United States, the white cedar. These 
	       are so-called false cypress. The bald cypress is a valuable timber tree of Mexico and the southern United 
	       States. It is deciduous, with a massive trunk as much as 52 m (170 ft) high. This tree grows at the edges 
	       of swamps or streams, and its roots form natural crooks, or knees, that extend above the water. The knees 
	       are frequently used for curved members in the construction of wooden boats.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_weepingmyall:entry"  >Tree, Weeping Myall</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_weepingmyall:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/WeepingMyall/WeepingMyall_Scrub_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The weeping myall, also known as the weeping acacia, is a slow-growing evergreen tree native to eastern Australia. 
               With its drooping branch and leaf canopy, the weeping myall is very similar in appearance to the weeping willow, but 
               can survive better in a desert climate because it requires much less water. Giraffes are commonly known to eat the 
               steel-gray leaves of the weeping myall tree.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_yellowfeveracacia:entry"  >Tree, Yellow Fever Acacia</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_yellowfeveracacia:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/YellowFeverAcacia/YellowFeverAcacia_Scrub_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The umbrella-shaped yellow fever acacia tree is among the tallest and largest trees growing on the African plains, 
               providing shade and shelter for a wide range of savannah visitors, both animal and human. 
               The bark of the yellow fever acacia is traditionally used to treat yellow fever, a noncontagious, 
               infectious disease, caused by a virus that is usually transmitted by bites from infected mosquitoes.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                 
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tremblingaspen:entry"  >Tree, Trembling Aspen</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_tremblingaspen:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/TremblingAspen/TremblingAspen_Grassland_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
               The trembling aspen, also known as the quaking aspen, is among the most distinctive of the Aspen trees.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
	       Aspen is the common name for certain related trees, particularly the so-called trembling aspens, 
	       several species of which have the petioles, or leafstalks, so compressed that the leaves can move 
	       easily from side to side but not up or down. A breeze sets all leaves of one of these trees into 
	       motion. The most familiar species are the American aspen, found in North America; the large-toothed 
	       aspen, found in eastern Canada and the United States; and the European aspen, found in Europe, western 
	       Asia, and northern Africa.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_wetlandlog:entry"  >Plant, Wetland Log</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_wetlandlog:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="150">
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/LogMedium/LogMedium_Wetlands_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
                  <img src="entities/objects/foliage/LogSmall/LogSmall_Wetlands_ icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" height="128" width="128"/>
               </cell>
               <cell pady="15" width="400">
                  
                  
                  Both the large and small wetland logs can provide a comfortable resting place for wetland animals, including the beaver and crocodile.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
               </cell>
            </cell>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="620">
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	Content provided courtesy of 
         
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                  <u>
                     <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                  </u>
               </a>
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
               
            	(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
      
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
