<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_biomedef:entry"  >Biome Defined</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_biomedef:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
         Biomes, also known as life zones, are defined by all plants, animals, and other organisms, as well as the physical environment in a 
         particular area. A biome is characterized by its plant life, the types of which are determined by a location's climatic conditions, 
         latitude, and altitude. For example, northern boreal forests exist in sub-arctic portions of North America and Asia, but further 
         north, the conditions are simply too harsh and the season too brief for trees to grow. Instead of trees, the short vegetation of 
         the tundra thrives in these areas. The same phenomenon occurs with altitude, as trees give way to short alpine vegetation in high 
         mountainous regions.
        
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <br/>
                  <br/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
         A biome is composed of many ecosystems - smaller communities of plants and animals and their habitats (the physical parts of their 
         environment that affect them). Whereas the boundaries of a biome are determined by climate, the boundaries of ecosystems are 
         physical features, such as ridges or riverbanks, that separate one community from another. The ecosystems of a particular biome 
         tend to have plants with similar growth forms and animals with similar feeding habits.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
         Major terrestrial biomes include alpine, 
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_tropicalrainforest:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">tropical rainforest</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
         , boreal forest, temperate forest, tundra, desert, grassland,
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_savannah:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">savannah</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
         , and scrub. Although not necessarily associated with marine environments, the term biome is sometimes used by ecologists to 
         describe marine life zones such as the littoral zone, found in shallow water; the pelagic zone in the open ocean; and the benthic 
         zone on the ocean floor.
         
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                     
					Content provided courtesy of 
					
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <a href="zoopedia:zoopedia_encarta:entry">
                     <u>
                        <color r="255" g="231" b="135">Microsoft (R) Encarta (R) Reference Library 2004.</color>
                     </u>
                  </a>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
					(C) 1993-2003 Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
         
               
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_animalenrichmentdef:entry"  >Animal Enrichment Defined</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_animalenrichmentdef:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
                  
                  
                  
                  
  		The zookeepers and animal trainers in the world's best zoos spend a lot of their time focused on developing animal enrichment programs to keep their animals engaged, active, and interested in their surroundings.
		
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
Among other things, animal enrichment programs focus on finding creative ways to mimic an animal's natural hunting and eating behaviors. For example, pieces of fruit hidden in a cardboard box filled with sticks and shredded paper can become both a nutritional snack and an exciting puzzle for a curious chimpanzee.
		
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
Serving a lion the carcass of an antelope for lunch will keep the animal much more interested in the eating process than if you just simply plunk down a couple of pounds of ground beef in front of it.
		
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
Providing animals with natural nesting materials is another big part of animal enrichment. Zoo Tycoon 2 even features a flat heated rock, which makes savannah animals who are used to sitting on hot rocks in the sun feel right at home.
         
               
               
               
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_encarta:entry"  >About Encarta</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_encarta:text"  >
         <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
            <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
            <p/>
            <cell width="260"/>
            <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
               <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
  		Encarta Reference Library 2004 
  		
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
		All the tools you need in one great product!
  		
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                    		
		The comprehensive, award-winning Microsoft Encarta Reference Library is the ultimate reference 
		source for the entire family. You get more up-to-date content, more learning tools, and more 
		leading-edge multimedia than ever before!
		
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  
		For more information, please visit:
  		
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                     http://www.microsoft.com/products/encarta/
               
               </cell>
            </cell>
         </color>
      </LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
