<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_keepingguestshappy" version="9" />
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_keepingguestshappy:order" version="9"  >!!!Keeping Guests Happy</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_keepingguestshappy:entry" version="9"  >Keeping Guests Happy</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="zoopedia_keepingguestshappy:text" version="9"  >
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" height="320" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds">
            <cell width="600" padx="20" pady="20">
               <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
                  <p/>
                  

         All guests who show up at your entrance gate arrive with an interest in their favorite animals, foods, and attractions, not to mention 
         different levels of thirst, hunger, and fatigue.
		
               
 
                  <p/>

               
               
               
		There are two easy ways to quickly check in on your zoo guests to see how they're doing:
		
               

                  
                  <p/>
                  

               
               
		First, click on any individual guest in your zoo to display the Guest Information panel in the lower right corner of 
		the main game window. The Guest Information panel has lots of information about what that guest is 
		thinking and feeling.
		
               

                  <p/>
                  

		Second, click the View Quick Stats button on the main game panel to display the complete list of guests currently 
		in your zoo. On the View Quick Stats screen, you can sort your guest list based on their favorite animals, happiness levels, 
		bathroom need, and more.
		
               
               

                  <p/>
                  
   
               
		Check out the tips below for advice on how to keep your zoo guests happy and satisfied.
		
 
                  <p/>

                  <i>Top 10 tips for attracting guests to your zoo</i>

                  <p/>
  
                  1. Give 'em room. Build paths that leave plenty of elbow room for the crowds. Also, large viewing areas near popular exhibits 
		keep crowds happy. 
		
               
 
                  
                  <p/>
                  

                  
                  
                  2. Keep it clean. Placing recycling bins and trash cans around your zoo helps keep things spotless. 
		
    
                  
                  <p/>
                  

                  
                  3. Showcase popular animals, and add as many different species as possible (this has a huge effect on your zoo fame score!). 
		
               

                  
                  <p/>
                  

                  
                  
                  4. Provide facilities where guests can be fed, hydrated, and rested, and they should be happy. As it happens, they're not so different from your zoo's animal 
		inhabitants. 
		

                  
                  <p/>
                  

                  
                  5. Encourage reproduction among your animals. Zoo guests love baby animals. 


                  <p/>
                  

                  
                  6. Experiment with changing the price of zoo admission and concessions until you find the perfect balance between keeping 
		guests happy (and spending) and maximizing your profit potential. 
		
               
               

                  <p/>
 
                  
                  7. Guests like to be amused at the zoo. In addition to viewing animals, they like to admire interesting statues, fountains, 
		and themed areas. Young guests love to play on playground equipment. 
		
                                
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  8. Pay attention to your zoo's aesthetics. Flowers and fountains can make a real difference in guests' happiness levels. 
		
                  
                  
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  
                  
                  9. Guests are happiest when viewing happy, healthy animals in well-designed exhibits. 
		
               
                  <p/>
                  
                  
                  10. Guests also want to be educated. Seeing animals in exhibits that represent their natural biomes can prompt guests to donate 
		more money to your zoo.
               
                                           
                  <p/>
               </color>
            </cell>
         </cell>
      </LOC_STRING>
   
</ZT2Strings>