<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:Pandasintro"  >The Mysterious Panda</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:Pandaname"  >Li Ming</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:Pandasoverview"  >
         
         
	One of the most recognizable animals in the world, the giant panda is also one of the most endangered. Only 
	zoos with exceptional reputations are even considered as recipients for giant panda adoptions. 
	
         
         <p/>
         
         
	Due to a low reproductive rate, attempts to breed giant pandas in captivity often meet with 
	failure. Facilities that undertake efforts to aid in the conservation of the giant panda are highly 
	valued and often rely heavily on donations and grants.
	
         
         <p/>
         
         
	Create a zoo and build it to the 5-star level. If you can obtain one male giant panda for your zoo, you will then receive a female panda, as well as international assistance towards establishing a supportive breeding 
	environment. Play your cards right to breed two giant pandas, and your zoo will go down in 
	history as one of the few that has successfully bred giant pandas in captivity.
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:Pandasoverviewshort"  >
        One of the most recognizable animals in the world, the giant panda is also one of the most endangered. Only 
	zoos with exceptional reputations are even considered as recipients for giant panda adoptions. Will yours be one of them? Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock the gilded panda statue!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:PandasSuccessPart1overview"  >
	Your exemplary giant panda exhibit has come to the attention of a prominent zoo in Asia. They 
	would like to send their female giant panda, %s, to your facility on a breeding mission. Add %s 
to your panda exhibit and cater to her advanced needs in the hope that she will successfully give birth 
	to a baby panda. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:PandasSuccessPart2overview"  >
	You have successfully bred your giant pandas! %s is yours to keep. In further recognition of your achievement 
	and as a sign of their appreciation for your efforts, you have been presented with a gilded panda statue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:Pandasresult"  >A panda baby is born!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:PandasAdoptPanda"  >
      	Build your zoo to the 5-star level and adopt one male giant panda.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:PandasAdoptPandaOK"  >
      	You have adopted a giant panda!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:PandasBreeding"  >
      	Meet the advanced needs of your two giant pandas and successfully breed them.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Pandas:PandasBreedingOK"  >
      	Congratulations! You are one of the few facilities that have bred the giant panda in captivity.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PandasLabels:Pandasshort"  >The Mysterious Panda</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PandasLabels:PandasS1"  >The Mysterious Panda</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PandasLabels:PandasS1short"  >The Mysterious Panda</LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
