<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext" version="6" />
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalTradeRevealed" version="6"  >The ZCA has removed each %1s from your zoo as per the terms of the study. Your new species, the %2s, has been delivered crated to the area near your front gate. You have one month to earn $500 in guest donations for this new species.   </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalSale" version="6"  >You've been approached by another zoo that is interested in obtaining one of your animals. In exchange for your animal, they have offered to make a generous donation to your facility. Would you like to release your %1s to this facility in exchange for their donation of %2s? Difficulty: Easy</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalSaleSuccess" version="6"  >You have donated your %1s to another facility in exchange for their donation of %2s. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalAwarenessDay" version="6"  >The board of directors of the National Animal Association has sent out a request to zoos nationwide. %1s Awareness Day is two months away and they would like all member zoos to have at least one animal of this species on-site within that time period. Their promotional campaign will be extensive and if you have one of these animals in your zoo within two months, you will benefit not only from increased attendance but also from the %2s cash grant available to all participating members. Difficulty: Variable</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalAwarenessDayShort" version="6"  >Have at least one %1s in your zoo for %2s Awareness Day in two months. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalCompanions" version="6"  >An internationally funded conservation group has offered to send you an animal to allow you to set up a breeding situation. The cost to obtain this %1s is %2s. You may keep the animal for two months. If you successfully breed this animal within the time limit, the conservation group will issue a refund for your initial cost and the animal, and baby, are yours to keep. Should you fail to successfully breed this animal, the loaned animal will be returned to its owner and no refunds will be issued. Finally, if the animal meets with misfortune while in your care such that it cannot be returned to its owner, you will be forced to pay a %3s penalty. Difficulty: Moderate</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalRelease" version="6"  >An internationally funded conservation group has offered you an incentive to release endangered animals to the wild in an effort to promote growth among old populations and make new populations of these animals self-sustaining. Their current research project involves the %1s. You have been offered %2s to prepare your %3s for release to the wild. %4s will be paid upfront and the remainder will be paid when the animal has been collected for its relocation to its natural habitat. Difficulty: Challenging</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHAnimalReleaseSuccess" version="6"  >Congratulations! You've successfully released your %1s to the wild, enhancing the worldwide population growth of this endangered species. The remainder of your %2s fee has been deposited to your account. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuest" version="6"  >You've received a tip that the CEO of a prominent and very wealthy corporation is planning to visit your zoo in the upcoming months. You've heard that %1s's favorite animal is the %2s and the rumor is that if this animal is in your zoo when %3s visits, it is likely that you will receive a generous donation.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuestShort" version="6"  >Have a %1s in your zoo before %2s arrives.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuestSuccessShort" version="6"  >You had %1s's favorite animal, the %2s, and have received a generous donation.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuestSuccess" version="6"  >Congratulations! %1s was impressed that you had the %2s in your zoo and has chosen to make a generous donation of %3s.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuestFailureShort" version="6"  >%1s paid a visit to your zoo and was disappointed that you did not have the %2s on display. Rumor is that %3s made a donation to an alternate facility.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Challengetext:CHSpecialGuestFailure" version="6"  >It's too bad that you did not have the %1s on display during %2s's visit. The rumor is that a donation of %3s was made to an alternate facility that featured the %4s.</LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
