<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:cstt_genericgotphoto"  >This picture fulfills a photo challenge requirement.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHPromotionalPhotos"  >Promotional Photos</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHMarketingBrochure"  >
         
         
         
		The marketing department is preparing a new zoo brochure and has requested pictures of the 
		following: 
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
		*  A guest holding an ice cold soda.		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
		*  A guest sitting on a bench. 
		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
		Providing these pictures will help improve your zoo fame as flyers promoting your zoo begin 
		to circulate around your community.
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
		Difficulty: Easy
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHMarketingBrochureShort"  >
   		Photograph a guest drinking an ice cold soda and a guest sitting on a bench.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHMarketingBrochureSuccess"  >
   		Marketing has received your pictures of a guest drinking an ice cold soda and a guest sitting on a bench. 
   		The new glossy brochure has been distributed around your community and news of your zoo
   		is spreading rapidly!
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHMarketingBrochureSuccessShort"  >
   		Great pictures! Your completed brochure will have a positive impact on zoo fame.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_guestsonbench"  >Take a picture of a guest sitting on a bench.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_guestswithsoda"  >Take a picture of a guest holding a soda.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHUngulatePhotos"  >Scientific Journal</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHUngulate"  >
         
         
         
		You have been approached by a scientific journal writing an educational piece about 
		Even-Toed Ungulates (Artiodactyls). They have requested 3 specific pictures for their 
		article and have offered you $750 per picture. If you can provide a picture of a 
		Dromedary Camel, a Gemsbok and a Thomson's Gazelle, you will be paid $2250. The 
		publicity will also provide a bonus to your zoo fame.
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
		Difficulty: Easy
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHUngulateShort"  >
   		Provide a photograph of a dromedary camel, gemsbok, and Thomson's gazelle.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHCamelShort"  >
   		Provide a photograph of a dromedary camel.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHGemsbokShort"  >
   		Provide a photograph of a gemsbok.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHThomsonsGazelleShort"  >
   		Provide a photograph of a Thomson's gazelle.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHUngulateSuccess"  >
   		The journal loved your photos!  You have been paid $2250 for the photos and you are sure
   		to gain increased popularity as a result of the published article.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:PHUngulateSuccessShort"  >
   		Your photos will really enhance the piece on even-toed ungulates.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_Camel"  >Take a picture of a dromedary camel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_Gemsbok"  >Take a picture of a gemsbok.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PhotoChallengetext:stt_Gazelle"  >Take a picture of a Thomson's gazelle.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooNewstext:PHZooNewsPhotos"  >Zoo News Monthly</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooNewstext:PHZooNews"  >
         
         
         
		Zoo News Monthly wants to run an article on your zoo but needs pictures to 
		back up their story. Once you provide the photos, they can run the news piece which 
		will have a positive impact on your attendance for the next 3 months that the issue is 
		displayed on the news stands. They are looking for photos of:
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
		*  A jaguar swimming in the water. 
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
		*  An ibex resting in a stable.
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  A moose rubbing its antlers on a tree.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Moderate
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooNewstext:PHZooNewsShort"  >
         
         
         
   		Provide the following photographs:
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  A jaguar swimming in the water. 
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  An ibex resting in a stable.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  A moose rubbing its antlers on a tree.
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooNewstext:PHZooNewsSuccess"  >
		The Zoo News article looks fantastic and the photos were so impressive that
		your zoo has gotten a mention on the magazine cover! Your attendance is sure
		to get a boost while the magazine stays on the news stands.
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooNewstext:PHZooNewsSuccessShort"  >
   		Your photos were fantastic. Your zoo was given a cover mention on Zoo News Monthly's magazine cover!
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooNewstext:stt_JaguarSwimming"  >Take a single photo of a jaguar swimming in the water.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooNewstext:stt_IbexRestStable"  >Take a picture of an ibex resting in a stable.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooNewstext:stt_MooseRubAntlers"  >Take a picture of a moose rubbing its antlers.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="FoodChaintext:PHFoodChainPhotos"  >High School Class Demonstration</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="FoodChaintext:PHFoodChain"  >
         
         
         
		The local high school is currently studying the concept of the food chain. They 
		would like to demonstrate this concept to the class and have asked if you can 
		provide a sequence of pictures demonstrating how the food chain works. They 
		will be sure to spread the word to other schools about the help you have 
		provided and this will enhance your attendance. You will need to 
		set up an exhibit where a carnivore can hunt its prey.
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Challenging	
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="FoodChaintext:PHFoodChainShort"  >
         
         
         
   		Take a series of 2 pictures that show a predatory animal:
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  Hunting its prey.   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Catching its prey.
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="FoodChaintext:PHFoodChainSuccess"  >
		Your photographs really helped the students grasp the concept of the food chain and
		they were totally engrossed during the class on the subject. 
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="FoodChaintext:PHFoodChainSuccessShort"  >
   		Your photographs really helped the students understand what the food chain is all about.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="FoodChaintext:stt_CarnivoreStalking"  >Take a photo of a carnivore hunting its prey.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="FoodChaintext:stt_CarnivoreCatching"  >Take a photo of a carnivore catching its prey.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooDesigntext:PHZooDesignPhotos"  >Building Design</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooDesigntext:PHZooDesign"  >
         
         
         

		Zoo Design, Inc. is running a trade piece on maximizing guest amenities and is 
		particularly interested in your zoo's offerings. They will mention your zoo in their 
		article, boosting your zoo fame, if you provide them with pictures of some of your 
		amenities. You will need to photograph the following amenities:
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
		*  Gift Cart  
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
		*  Kangaroo Bouncy Ride
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
		*  Small Restroom
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Any food stand
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Easy
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooDesigntext:PHZooDesignShort"  >
         
         
         
   		Zoo Design, Inc. would like pictures of the following amenities:
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  Gift Cart  
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Kangaroo Bouncy Ride
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Small Restroom
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Any food stand
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooDesigntext:PHZooDesignSuccess"  >
		Your photographs were used by Zoo Design, Inc. to demonstrate excellent 
		use of guest amenities with full credit given to your zoo for creative designs. Guests
		are sure to be impressed by the accolades received by your zoo in this trade article and your 
		fame will increase as a result.
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooDesigntext:PHZooDesignSuccessShort"  >
   		The photographs showed off your excellent guest amenities and boosted your zoo fame.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooDesigntext:stt_SmallRestroom"  >Take a photo of a Small Restroom.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooDesigntext:stt_GiftCart"  >Take a photo of a Gift Cart.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooDesigntext:stt_KangarooRide"  >Take a photo of a Kangaroo Bouncy Ride.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooDesigntext:stt_AnyFoodStand"  >Take a photo of any food stand.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="GardeningSocietytext:PHGardeningSocietyPhotos"  >Gardening Society Demonstration</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="GardeningSocietytext:PHGardeningSociety"  >
         
         
         
		The Gardening Society is interested in your display of plant life and has asked you to 
		make a presentation about the foliage in your park. They will pay you $2000 for your 
		appearance. To support your presentation, you will need 4 photographs of plant life 
		from 4 different regions of the world, where each picture shows the foliage displayed 
		in its appropriate biome. The presentation will increase public awareness by appealing 
		to an audience that may not be aware that your zoo offers more than just animals. 
		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
		You'll need foliage from the Savannah, Tropical Rainforest, Boreal Forest and the 
		Alpine biomes. 
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Easy
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="GardeningSocietytext:PHGardeningSocietyShort"  >
         
         
         
   		You need to provide the following photos:
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  Baobab: Savannah biome, Africa  
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Kapok: Tropical Rainforest, South America
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Tamarack: Boreal Forest, North America
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Himalayan Pine: Alpine, China
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="GardeningSocietytext:PHGardeningSocietySuccess"  >
		Your foliage presentation was a huge success. With standing room only crowds, a second 
		session was added to your schedule and your fee was doubled. You've received $4000!
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="GardeningSocietytext:PHGardeningSocietySuccessShort"  >
   		Your foliage presentation was a hit and your fee was doubled to $4000!
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="GardeningSocietytext:stt_Baobob"  >Take a photo of a baobab tree.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="GardeningSocietytext:stt_Kapok"  >Take a photo of a kapok tree.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="GardeningSocietytext:stt_Tamarack"  >Take a photo of a tamarack tree.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="GardeningSocietytext:stt_HimalayanPine"  >Take a photo of a Himalayan pine tree.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooAssociationtext:PHZooAssociationPhotos"  >National Zoo Association Contest</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooAssociationtext:PHZooAssociation"  >
         
         
         
		The National Zoo Association is running a contest among all member zoos and will award 
		all participants with a $5,000 grant. They have requested 2 pictures of rare zoo 
		events. Specifically they are looking for a photo of any animal baby with its mother and any animal 
		making use of an enrichment object. 
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Moderate
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooAssociationtext:PHZooAssociationShort"  >
         
         
         
   		Capture specific images as follows: 
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Any animal baby with its mother.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Any animal using an enrichment object.
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooAssociationtext:PHZooAssociationSuccess"  >
		Your photographs of hard to capture zoo events like a baby animal with its mother and an animal using an enrichment object have earned you a $5,000 grant!
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooAssociationtext:PHZooAssociationSuccessShort"  >
   		Your photos of hard to capture zoo events have earned you a $5,000 grant!
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooAssociationtext:stt_AnyBabyAnimal"  >Take a photo of any baby animal.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooAssociationtext:stt_AnyBabyAnimalwithMother"  >Take a photo of a baby animal with its mother.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooAssociationtext:stt_TwoZebrasGrooming"  >Take a photo of two Common Zebras grooming each other.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="ZooAssociationtext:stt_AnimalUsingEnrichment"  >Take a photo of any animal using an enrichment object.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CenterAnimalConservationtext:PHCenterAnimalConservationPhotos"  >Center for Animal Conservation Contest</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CenterAnimalConservationtext:PHCenterAnimalConservation"  >
         
         
         

		The Center for Animal Conservation has issued an open contest to obtain pictures of 
		endangered animals. Winners will receive the Animal Conservation Image Award and a 
		cash bonus of $15,000. The required animals are: Bengal Tiger, Snow Leopard, Mountain 
		Gorilla, and Grizzly Bear.
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Moderate
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CenterAnimalConservationtext:PHCenterAnimalConservationShort"  >
         
         
         
   		Capture 1 picture of each of the following animals to qualify for the award.  
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  Bengal Tiger
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Snow Leopard
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Mountain Gorilla
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Grizzly Bear
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CenterAnimalConservationtext:PHCenterAnimalConservationSuccess"  >
		Your photographs of endangered animals were magnificent and earned first place. You have won $15,000 and the Animal Conservation Image Award!
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CenterAnimalConservationtext:PHCenterAnimalConservationSuccessShort"  >
   		Your photos of endangered animals have earned you $15,000 and the Animal Conservation Image Award!
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CenterAnimalConservationtext:stt_BengalTiger"  >Take a photo of a Bengal tiger.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CenterAnimalConservationtext:stt_SnowLeopard"  >Take a photo of a snow leopard.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CenterAnimalConservationtext:stt_MountainGorilla"  >Take a photo of a mountain gorilla.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="CenterAnimalConservationtext:stt_GrizzlyBear"  >Take a photo of a grizzly bear.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="UngulatesPart2text:PHUngulatesPart2Photos"  >Scientific Journal Follow-up Article</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="UngulatesPart2text:PHUngulatesPart2"  >
         
         
         
		You have been approached by the scientific journal for a second series of pictures on the 
		Dromedary Camel, Gemsbok and the Thomson's Gazelle. They will pay you $1500 per picture 
		for photographs that capture these animals performing specific activities.
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Moderate
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="UngulatesPart2text:PHUngulatesPart2Short"  >
         
         
         
   		Capture these animals performing the following activities:  
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  A Dromedary Camel grooming another camel.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  A Gemsbok sleeping in the shade.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  A Thomson's Gazelle greeting another gazelle.
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="UngulatesPart2text:PHUngulatesPart2Success"  >
		The scientific journal was pleased with the latest round of pictures and has paid you 
		your $4500 fee.
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="UngulatesPart2text:PHUngulatesPart2SuccessShort"  >
   		Your second batch of Even-Toed Ungulate pictures has earned you $4500.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="UngulatesPart2text:PHUngulatesPart2Failure"  >
		The scientific journal's deadline for the second batch of Even-Toed Ungulate pictures has
		expired. Unfortunately they've had to go ahead without your photographs.
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="UngulatesPart2text:PHUngulatesPart2FailureShort"  >
   		Unfortunately the deadline for the second batch of Even-Toed Ungulate pictures has expired.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="UngulatesPart2text:stt_CamelsGrooming"  >Take a photo of a Dromedary Camel grooming another camel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="UngulatesPart2text:stt_GemsbokSleepingShade"  >Take a photo of a Gemsbok sleeping in the shade.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="UngulatesPart2text:stt_GazelleGreeting"  >Take a photo of a Thomson's Gazelle greeting another gazelle.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="BistroMagazinetext:PHBistroMagazinePhotos"  >El Bistro Magazine</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="BistroMagazinetext:PHBistroMagazine"  >
         
         
         
		El Bistro Magazine wants a unique angle for an upcoming issue and would like to feature 
		photographs of animals eating from interesting containers. They have requested 
		photographs of a cheetah, a reticulated giraffe, and a ring-tailed lemur eating from 
		specific food containers and will pay you $2000 per photo. 
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Moderate
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="BistroMagazinetext:PHBistroMagazineShort"  >
         
         
         
   		Provide the following photographs:  
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  A cheetah eating meat from an artificial carcass.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  A reticulated giraffe eating branches from a browse holder.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  A ring-tailed lemur eating from an elevated food dish.
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="BistroMagazinetext:PHBistroMagazineSuccess"  >
		El Bistro Magazine was thrilled with your photographs. The cheetah eating meat from the artificial carcass
		was a perfect backdrop for the serving suggestions for BBQ ribs! And the browse
		holder made the presentation of the salad course an interesting feature by itself. 
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="BistroMagazinetext:PHBistroMagazineSuccessShort"  >
   		Your photos of animals eating from interesting containers earned you $6000!
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="BistroMagazinetext:stt_CheetahEatMeatCarcass"  >Take a photo of a cheetah eating meat from an artificial carcass.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="BistroMagazinetext:stt_GiraffeEatBranchesBrowseHolder"  >Take a photo of a reticulated giraffe eating branches from a browse holder.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="BistroMagazinetext:stt_LemurEatElevatedDish"  >Take a photo of a ring-tailed lemur eating from an elevated food dish.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PsychologicalConferencetext:PHPsychologicalConferencePhotos"  >Animal Enrichment</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PsychologicalConferencetext:PHPsychologicalConference"  >
         
         
         

		A national conference has scheduled a session on the topic of psychological 
		stimulation for animals in captivity. You have been offered a spot on the interactive 
		panel segment and have been asked to provide photographs to support the discussion. You 
		will be paid $20,000 if you participate and provide photographs of the required animals interacting
		with specific enrichment objects. 
		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
		You will need a Polar Bear, an African Elephant, a Bengal Tiger and a Black Rhinoceros.  
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Challenging
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PsychologicalConferencetext:PHPsychologicalConferenceShort"  >
         
         
         
   		Capture photographs of the following animals:  
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  A Polar Bear using a car tire.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  An African Elephant using the easel.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  A Bengal Tiger lying on a heated rock.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  A Black Rhinoceros playing with a pursuit ball.   		
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PsychologicalConferencetext:PHPsychologicalConferenceSuccess"  >
		Your participation in the interactive panel segment on the topic of psychological 
		stimulation for animals in captivity was extremely polished. The spectacular photos of your
		animals performing interesting actions was a great demonstration of
		animals achieving enrichment from unusual objects. You received a $20,000 fee for your appearance.
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PsychologicalConferencetext:PHPsychologicalConferenceSuccessShort"  >
   		Your photos of animals using interesting object were a polished addition to your conference 
   		participation! You received a $20,000 fee for your appearance.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PsychologicalConferencetext:stt_BearPolarUseCarTire"  >Take a photo of a polar bear using a car tire.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PsychologicalConferencetext:stt_ElephantUseEasel"  >Take a photo of an African elephant using the easel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PsychologicalConferencetext:stt_TigerBengalUseHeatedRock"  >Take a photo of a Bengal tiger lying on a heated rock.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PsychologicalConferencetext:stt_RhinoUsePursuitBall"  >Take a photo of a black rhinoceros playing with a pursuit ball.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AnimalInstinctstext:PHAnimalInstinctsPhotos"  >Animal Instincts</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AnimalInstinctstext:PHAnimalInstincts"  >
         
         
         
		A group of ethologists will be visiting your zoo to further their studies of animal 
		instinctual behaviors. To help make their visit more time efficient, they have 
		asked you to capture images of certain behaviors. If you can accommodate their request, they'll 
		share their knowledge of animal behaviors with your guests and boost your zoo fame. You will need to capture 
		photographs of ring-tailed lemurs, a pride of lions, ostriches and reticulated giraffes.
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Challenging
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AnimalInstinctstext:PHAnimalInstinctsShort"  >
         
         
         
   		Capture photographs of the following animal behaviors:  
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  A ring-tailed lemur grooming another lemur, satisfying social and hygienic instincts.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  A pride of lions consisting of one adult male, three females and one young lion.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  An ostrich doing a mating dance.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  A young giraffe calling to its mother.   		
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AnimalInstinctstext:PHAnimalInstinctsSuccess"  >
		The ethologists were amazed to see the range of behaviors that your animals performed and were 
		delighted to share their knowledge with your guests. They found their visit so productive that 
		they stayed twice as long as they expected. Your zoo guests enjoyed the additional information
		about animal instincts immensely and you have received a boost to zoo fame.
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AnimalInstinctstext:PHAnimalInstinctsSuccessShort"  >
   		The ethologists' visit was a huge success and your guests really enjoyed learning more about the animals.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AnimalInstinctstext:stt_LemursGrooming"  >Take a photo of a ring-tailed lemur grooming another lemur.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AnimalInstinctstext:stt_LionsSleepinShade"  >Take a photo of a pride of lions.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AnimalInstinctstext:stt_OstrichMatingDance"  >Take a photo of an ostrich doing a mating dance.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AnimalInstinctstext:stt_YoungGiraffeCalling"  >Take a photo of a young giraffe calling to its mother.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AlfredWindsorSchooltext:PHAlfredWindsorSchoolPhotos"  >Wildlife Photography Lesson</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AlfredWindsorSchooltext:PHAlfredWindsorSchool"  >
         
         
         
		The Alfred Windsor School of Photography would like you to provide them with a photo 
		to use as a sample during the wildlife photography segment of their curriculum. They 
		need only one photograph, but to make it more interesting for the students, they would 
		like it to be a snapshot that contains at least two animals. In return for 
		this photograph, they will present you with the Alfred Windsor Photography Award of 
		Merit that you can display as an example of your efforts to help the 
		community. You will also receive a $2000 licensing fee.
		
        
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Easy
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AlfredWindsorSchooltext:PHAlfredWindsorSchoolShort"  >
         
         
         
   		Capture the following photograph:  
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  Take a photo that features two animals.
 		
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AlfredWindsorSchooltext:PHAlfredWindsorSchoolSuccess"  >
		Your photo of two animals was exceptionally detailed. It was a great example of 
		brilliant wildlife photography. The Alfred Windsor School of Photography has licensed your wildlife photo for $2000 
   		and has presented you with the Alfred Windsor Photography Award of Merit.
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AlfredWindsorSchooltext:PHAlfredWindsorSchoolSuccessShort"  >
   		The Alfred Windsor School of Photography licensed your wildlife photo for $2000 
   		and presented you with the Alfred Windsor Photography Award of Merit.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="AlfredWindsorSchooltext:stt_TwoAnimalsUpClose"  >Take a close up photo that features two animals.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PrimatePicturestext:PHPrimatePicturesPhotos"  >Beckenspot Primate Photographs</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PrimatePicturestext:PHPrimatePictures"  >
         
         
         
		A school group will be taking a field trip sponsored by the Beckenspot Charitable 
		Foundation to visit the primates in your zoo. The Foundation would like souvenir 
		photos to give to each of the students as a reminder of their visit. They have 
		asked you to provide specific photos of Mountain Gorillas and Chimpanzees. In return 
		for your efforts, they will present you with the Beckenspot Charitable Foundation 
		Photographic Portfolio Award at a black tie awards ceremony recognizing 
		benefactors of the Foundation. The publicity you will receive at this well-heeled 
		event will provide a significant boost to your attendance.            
		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		Difficulty: Challenging
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PrimatePicturestext:PHPrimatePicturesShort"  >
         
         
         
   		Photograph the following animals:  
   		
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
   		*  Photograph a mountain gorilla chuckling.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Photograph a male mountain gorilla calling to his troop.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Photograph a chimpanzee using the monkey bars.
   		
         
         
         <br/>
         
         
         
   		*  Photograph a chimpanzee climbing a tree.	
   	
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PrimatePicturestext:PHPrimatePicturesSuccess"  >
		The Beckenspot Charitable Foundation was grateful for the pictures you were able to provide. The visit 
		was a success and the Foundation really promoted your zoo at their black tie gala. Earning the
		Beckenspot Charitable Foundation Photographic Portfolio Award is an impressive achievement. The benefactors 
		of the Foundation have all indicated they will be making a special trip to your facility. The 
		benefits to your attendance and donation collections will be significant.
	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PrimatePicturestext:PHPrimatePicturesSuccessShort"  >
   		The Beckenspot Charitable Foundation presented you with the Beckenspot Charitable Foundation 
   		Photographic Portfolio Award. The publicity you have received among the
   		benefactors of the Foundation will boost your attendance and donation collections.
   	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PrimatePicturestext:stt_GorillaChuckling"  >Take a photo of a gorilla chuckling.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PrimatePicturestext:stt_GorillaCalling"  >Take a photo of a male gorilla calling.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PrimatePicturestext:stt_ChimpUseMonkeyBars"  >Take a photo of a chimpanzee using the monkey bars.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="PrimatePicturestext:stt_ChimpClimbTree"  >Take a photo of a chimpanzee climbing a tree.</LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
