<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:tutorial1_welcome"  >


















         Welcome to the Zoo Tycoon 2 Tutorials. In the following tutorials, you will learn the basics of how to control the camera. Then you'll move on to construction techniques and accessing all the information available to you about your zoo.



















         <br>So let's get started! Click the check button on this panel to continue.</br>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:goalpanelheading"  >Open the Goal Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:opengoalpanel"  >Open the Goal Panel by clicking the Scenario Goals Button on the Primary Game Button Panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:opengoalpanelcompleted"  >Great! Return to the goal panel anytime to see what your current goals are during a Campaign or Challenge game. Now we
      	can learn how to move the camera around the game world. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:closegoalpanelheading"  >Close Goal Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:closegoalpanel"  >Close the Goal Panel by clicking the X button on the Scenario Goals Panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:goalpaneldisplay"  >
	Your scenario and challenge goals will appear here when you play a Campaign or Challenge game. Normally
	this panel will update whenever you succeed, or fail, to complete a goal.
	The tutorials are a little different, though, so for now this is the only goal that will appear here!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:cameracontrolscrollheading"  >Camera Controls: Scrolling</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:cameracontolscroll"  >Now we need to practice moving the camera around. Scroll the map by using the arrow keys, or the W A S or D keys on your
      	keyboard, or by moving your mouse cursor all the way to any of the map edges.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:cameracontolscrollcompleted"  >
      	Scrolling the map will allow you to view and monitor various areas of your zoo. Click the check button on this panel to
      	continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:cameracontrolzoomheading"  >Camera Controls: Zoom In or Zoom Out</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:cameracontolzoom"  >
      	Zoom in and out using the Camera Control Zoom buttons on the Primary Game Button Panel, or use the mouse wheel if
      	your mouse supports this function.
      	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:cameracontolzoomcompleted"  >
      	Zooming in gives you a close up view of anything in the zoo. Zooming out gives you a better
      	perspective of the overall structure. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:cameracontrolrotateheading"  >Camera Controls: Rotate Game World</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:cameracontolrotate"  >
      	Rotate the map by using the Camera Control Rotate buttons on the Primary Game Button Panel. You can also hold down the CTRL key or click and hold the left mouse button while moving
      	the mouse to rotate the camera. Go ahead and rotate your view now.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:cameracontolrotatecompleted"  >
      	Rotating allows you to view buildings, animals, and guests from different angles. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:guestmodeheading"  >Guest Mode</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:guestmode"  >Enter Zoo Guest Mode by clicking on the Zoo Guest Mode button to the left of the Primary Game Button Panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:guestmodecompleted"  >
      	In Zoo Guest Mode, you can walk around your zoo by pressing the left mouse button. Normally, when you enter Zoo Guest Mode, the mouse cursor is hidden so that your view is unobstructed. To toggle your mouse cursor on and off or to switch to Photo Safari view, right-click the mouse. For now, though, just click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:superstaffheading"  >Staff Mode</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:superstaff"  >
      	You can also take on the duties of a maintenance worker to sweep trash and empty trash cans. When you
      	approach something that you can interact with, it will automatically be selected. Just hit SPACEBAR
      	to perform the action. Now it's your turn! Press the left mouse button or use the movement keys to
      	walk up to a piece of trash  or a trash can and clean it up now.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:superstaffcompleted"  >
      	Great! You can also perform zookeeper duties in the same way. You can feed and water
      	animals, groom them, heal them and... of course, rake poop. TIP: Doing these things yourself could mean that you
      	don't need to pay a staff member to do it -- very helpful for a financially struggling zoo! Click
      	the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:photosafariheading"  >Photo Safari</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:photosafari"  >
      	Time to check out Photo Safari mode. Click on the Photo Safari View button to bring up the camera.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:photosafaricompleted"  >
      	In Photo Safari mode, you can use your camera to take photographs of anything in your zoo. Just press SPACEBAR
      	to take a picture. Again, right-click the mouse to toggle the mouse cursor on and off, but for
      	now, just click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:openpeanutcompleted"  >
      	From here you can change your view to Zoo Guest Mode, Photo Safari Mode, or Overhead Mode. Click the check button on this
      	panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:overheadmapheading"  >Overhead View</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:overheadmap"  >
      	Let's return to the Overhead View. Click on the Overhead View button.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:overviewmapheading"  >Overview Map</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:overviewmap"  >View the Overview Map by clicking on the Overview Map button to the left of the Primary Game Button Panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:overviewmapcompleted"  >
      	The Overview Map gives you a broad layout of your zoo. You can quickly jump around from place
      	to place in your zoo by clicking any location on the Overview Map. Click the check button on this
      	panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:overviewmapcloseheading"  >Overview Map</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:overviewmapclose"  >
      	The map legend allows you to toggle various objects on the map on and off. To close the Overview Map and
      	return to the game, click the X button in the lower right corner of the screen.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:zoopediaheading"  >Zoopedia and Help</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:zoopedia"  >Press F1 to open Zoopedia.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:zoopediacloseheading"  >Zoopedia and Help</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:zoopediaclose"  >Zoopedia contains information about game controls and the animals and objects in Zoo Tycoon 2. Press F1 to open Zoopedia. On some panels, you can click the small purple book button to jump directly to a Zoopedia topic for that object. To exit, click the exit button in the upper right corner.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:zoopediaclosecompleted"  >
      	Great job! This is the end of the Controls Tutorial. The next tutorial will show you a few things about construction techniques. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial1:tutorial_1_complete"  >This is the end of the Controls Tutorial. The next tutorial will show you a few things
      	about construction techniques. To continue playing the next tutorial, click the check mark button in the
      	lower right, or if you wish to return to the Main Menu, click the X button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:tutorial2_welcome"  >



















         In the following tutorial you will learn the basics of construction techniques -- essentially
         how to make a basic exhibit, change the terrain, add animals, and provide paths and buildings for your guests.



















         <br>So let's get started!  Click the check button on this panel to continue.</br>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectrecyclebuttonheading"  >Recycle</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectrecyclebutton"  >Select the Recycle Objects and Buildings button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectrecyclebuttoncompleted"  >
      	Great! You can use the Recycle tool to remove unwanted objects from your zoo. Click the check button on
      	this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:recycletreeheading"  >Recycle</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:recycletree"  >
      	Look for the solitary tree inside the rectangular
      	area enclosed by a path (it's marked with an "X" painted in the dirt). The baobab tree is right in the center of this area. Move
      	your cursor over the baobab tree and click on it to recycle it now.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:recycletreecompleted"  >
      	Good job! You will receive cash for recycled objects, but it will only be a portion of its
      	full purchase price. Note that you cannot recycle animals - that just wouldn't be right! Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectundoheading"  >Undo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectundo"  >Whoops! We really wanted that tree. We can get it back though. Click on the Undo button now to undo the recycling that you just did.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectundocompleted"  >
      	Excellent! You can use undo to reverse the last thing you did -- this is very
      	handy if you find you've made a mistake or just don't like the way something looks. Note that you can
      	only undo the LAST thing you did, but it will undo any action, including an animal placement or terrain change. Click on the check button to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openconstructionpanelheading"  >Construction Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openconstructionpanel"  >




















         It's time to start building!




















         <p/>




















         Open the Construction Panel by clicking the Construction button.



















      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openconstructionpanelcompleted"  >
      	The Construction Panel is where you'll go when you want to place fences, paths, zoo buildings, scenery objects and all kinds of other
      	"man-made" objects in your zoo. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openfencerectangletoolheading"  >Fence Placement Rectangle Tool</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openfencerectangletool"  >
      	Fences are the most common way to keep your animals in... and your guests out! Click on
      	the Rectangle Fence Placement button in the Fence Buy panel.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openfencerectangletoolcompleted"  >
      	The Rectangle Mode tool lets you easily create an enclosed habitat area. Click the check
      	button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placefencesheading"  >Buy Fence</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placefences"  >Find the rectangular area enclosed by a path (it's the same area where you just replaced the baobab tree). Let's create a fenced area. First select the chain-link fence, then click on the ground to "anchor" the corner. Move your mouse to see a preview of the enclosed area, and click again to
place the fence. Make a fenced area as large as the rectangular area.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placefencescompleted"  >
      	Great! Now you have a basic enclosure. Later you can try the Octagonal Placement Mode to make an
      	octagonal shape or the Rubber Band Mode to place single sections. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placegateheading"  >Staff Gate</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placegate"  >
      	Now it's time to place a gate. Select the staff gate and place it over the fenced area you just made. The
      	gate preview will snap into place when your cursor is over the fence. Just click to insert the gate in that location.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placegatecompleted"  >
      	You'll want to make sure that your enclosed areas have gates so your staff can get in and
      	care for the animals. Right now we're only using the chain-link fence, but there are all kinds of
      	different fence types. The staff gate will automatically work on any of them. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectscenerytabheading"  >Scenery Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectscenerytab"  >
      	Click on the Scenery Tab to open the Scenery Buy panel. Here's where you'll find
      	useful and decorative objects that you can place in your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectscenerytabcompleted"  >
      	Normally, you'd see many objects on the Scenery Buy panel but, for now, we've
      	narrowed it down to just one - the donation box. Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placedonationboxheading"  >Donation Box</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placedonationbox"  >
You have a donation box selected. Move your mouse over the world to see a preview. When an item is on your cursor, you can rotate it by using the &lt; &gt; keys. Note the green arrow pointing to it. This shows the side your guests will approach. Make sure it isn't blocked by anything. Click to place the donation box near the fenced area you made earlier.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placedonationboxcompleted"  >
   You should place donation boxes near every exhibit. If guests can't find a donation box, their cash will stay in their pockets instead of going into yours. It's often a good idea to place multiple donation boxes so that guests won't be inconvenienced in any way. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectpathtabheading"  >Path Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectpathtab"  >Click on the Path Tab to open the Path Buy panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectpathtabcompleted"  >
      	You'll see that there are a number of different paths that you can choose from. Guests don't so much care what
      	type of path surface is in your zoo, but they do care that there is one! Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placepathheading"  >Place Path</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placepath"  >Paths work like fences do. Click on the ground to "anchor" the path. Then move the mouse to see a preview of where the path will go. Click again to place it. Notice that the
path in the map is very narrow around the rectangular exhibit area. Place some new path to make it wider for your guests.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placepathcompleted"  >
      	You'll want to make sure that your paths lead to your exhibits. Guests stand on paths to view exhibits
      	so if your paths are too far away,  your guests won't see your exhibits. They'll miss out on your great animals, and you'll
      	miss out on their donations. (Yup, you'll want those paths leading to your donation
      	boxes, too!) Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectbuildingtabheading"  >Building Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectbuildingtab"  >
      	Click on the Building Tab to access the Building Buy panel... and you guessed it... this is where you'll find buildings to
      	place in your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectbuildingtabcompleted"  >
      	You'll find all sorts of buildings on the Building Buy panel, from food and drink stands to restrooms and
      	more. Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placebuildingsheading"  >Purchase Buildings</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placebuildings"  >Now purchase a hot dog food stand, a pretzel cart, and a soda drink stand. You already have the hot dog food stand selected. Move your mouse over the zoo to see a preview of the selected object. To select other buildings, just click on them. Notice the green access arrow, which shows side that guests will approach. Go ahead and place one of each building now.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placebuildingscompleted"  >
      	Guests get hungry, thirsty, and need to use a restroom while visiting your zoo. If you don't provide them
      	with amenities to meet these needs, they may leave prematurely and take their cash with them. Like exhibits and donation boxes, make sure that you have paths leading to all your great
      	amenities! Click the check button on this panel to continue. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectpretzelcartheading"  >Selecting Objects</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectpretzelcart"  >
      	Click on the pretzel cart that you just placed in your zoo to select it. If another object is already on
      	your cursor, you can right-click to clear it.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectpretzelcartcompleted"  >
      	Great, you have the pretzel cart selected! Note that an information panel opens up showing the item
      	you have selected. Don't worry about all the things on this panel for now -- we'll come back to this
      	in more detail later. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:moveselectedentityheading"  >Moving Objects</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:moveselectedentity"  >
      	Many objects can be moved to other locations (though there are some that can't be). Once you have selected an object, you can use the Pick Up
      	Building button to "pick it up". You can also just click on the object again once it is selected.
      	Now move the pretzel cart to another location.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:moveselectedentitycompleted"  >
      	Remember, when an item is on your cursor, you can rotate it by using the &lt; &gt; keys or by clicking AND holding the left
      	mouse button while you move the cursor around the screen. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openanimalpanelheading"  >Adopting Animals</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openanimalpanel"  >
      	Click on the Animals button to open the Animal Adoption panel. This is where you'll obtain animals for
      	your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openanimalpanelcompleted"  >Great! Now let's adopt an animal. Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeanimalheading"  >Adopt Animal</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeanimal"  >
      	You'll see that you already have the African elephant selected on the Adoption panel. Move your mouse cursor over to the fenced area that
      	you made earlier and click to place the African elephant inside the basic enclosure.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeanimalcompleted"  >
      	Excellent! Now you have a new animal. Guests come to see the animals, so if you have no animals, you'll have
      	no guests! Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectfoodtabheading"  >Animal Food Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectfoodtab"  >Select the Animal Food Tab to open the Animal Food Buy panel. If you want your animals to thrive,
      	you'll need to make sure they have food and water.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectfoodtabcompleted"  >
      	All animals require food and water, but they won't eat just anything (will you?). We'll tell you
      	more about how to determine what an animal eats later, but, for now, just click the check button on this
      	panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placewaterfoodheading"  >Purchase Food and Water</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placewaterfood"  >Place a food trough with hay and a food trough with water near the African elephant by clicking on the dish, then clicking inside the enclosure to place it.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placewaterfoodcompleted"  >
      	Great! Placing food and water in your exhibits will allow your animals to satisfy their hunger and thirst
      	needs. Remember... a hungry or thirsty animal is not a happy animal! Click the check button on
      	this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectsheltertabheading"  >Shelter Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectsheltertab"  >Select the Animal Shelters Tab to open the Animal Shelter Buy panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectsheltertabcompeted"  >While an exhausted animal might sleep just anywhere, most animals require a shelter to meet their need for privacy. Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:researchobjectheading"  >Research</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:researchobject"  >
      	Certain advanced objects need to be studied more carefully before you have access to them. You do this by
      	choosing to research the object. Objects that need to be researched have a small beaker
      	appearing over their icon. Press the Research button on the Object Info panel
      	to begin research on an object.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:researchobjectcompleted"  >
      	It takes time and money to research an object. Once the research has been completed, the object is available for
      	purchase. Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeshelterheading"  >Purchase Shelter</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeshelter"  >Wait for the elephant house to finish being researched. You can
do other things while objects are being researched. (This would be a great time to take a look around the zoo!). Once the research is completed, select the elephant house, and then move your cursor into your zoo to see a preview of the item. Click to place the shelter in the African elephant's enclosure.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placesheltercompleted"  >Great! Your animal has a place to go for a little privacy. Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:enrichmentpanelheading"  >Animal Enrichment Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:enrichmentpanel"  >
      	Select the Animal Enrichment Tab to open the Animal Enrichment Object Buy panel.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:enrichmentpanelcompleted"  >
      	Enrichment objects enhance an exhibit area for many species of animals by keeping them
      	active and entertained in their environment. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeopursuitballheading"  >Pursuit Ball</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeopursuitball"  >
      	There are many enrichment objects available in Zoo Tycoon 2, but, for now, we've narrowed the selection down to
      	one. You'll see that you have a pursuit ball selected. Click in the African elephant's enclosure to place the object.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeopursuitballcompleted"  >
      	Different species of animals have different levels of interest in enrichment objects for
      	stimulation. We'll go into more detail later about how to find out about what items
      	stimulate different animals. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openlandscapingpanelheading"  >Landscaping </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openlandscapingpanel"  >
      	Open the Landscaping panel by clicking the Landscaping button. The Landscaping panel is where you'll go to modify
      	the "organic" parts of your zoo by changing the terrain, and placing trees, rocks, and other foliage.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openlandscapingpanelcompleted"  >
      	The Landscaping panel is also where you have all the tools you'll need to create a proper habitat (also known as a biome) for
      	your animal(s) to live in. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:paintsavannahheading"  >Paint Savannah Biome</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:paintsavannah"  >
      	Move through the different biomes by clicking on the arrows until you locate the
      	savannah biome. After you find it, move the cursor into the African elephant's enclosure and click and drag to
      	start painting with land appropriate to the savannah biome.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:paintsavannahcompleted"  >
      	Great job! Animals prefer to be in exhibits that resemble their natural habitats. Use these biome brushes
      	to paint the terrain that best suits their natural environments. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:pausegameheading"  >Game Pause</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:pausegame"  >You can pause the game whenever you need to. Click the Pause button in the upper left corner or use the P key to pause the game now.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:pausegamecompleted"  >
      	Great! If "real life" beckons, you can pause the game and never miss the action. Keep in mind, though, that
 you can also build while the game is paused. This can be helpful if guests or animals move
      	into an area where you want to build -- just pause the game and move them out of the way.
      	Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openstaffpanelheading"  >Staff Panel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openstaffpanel"  >Open the Hire Staff panel by clicking on the Staff button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openstaffpanelcompleted"  >
      	This is where you will find workers to handle general zoo maintenance, animal care, and guest
      	education. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:hirezookeeperheading"  >Hire Staff</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:hirezookeeper"  >
      	The zookeeper staff member specializes in animal care and will make sure that your animals receive food
      	and water as needed. They will also treat illnesses and groom dirty animals. Select a zookeeper and move the
      	cursor into your zoo. Click to place your new zookeeper in the world.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:hirezookeepercompleted"  >Excellent! Your zookeeper can now care for your African elephant. Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:hireeducatorheading"  >Educator</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:hireeducator"  >The educator will enhance the educational experience for your guests. Select an educator and move the
      	cursor into your zoo. Click to place your new educator in the world.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:hireeducatorcompleteted"  >
      	Great! You have an educator. Educators need an educator podium to speak from. Otherwise, the guests
      	won't be able to hear them. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openconstructionpanel2heading"  >Back to Construction</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openconstructionpanel2"  >Time to purchase an educator podium. Open the Construction panel now.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:openconstructionpanel2completed"  >Great! Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectbuildingtab2heading"  >Building Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectbuildingtab2"  >Click on the Building Tab to access the Building Buy panel... and you guessed it... this is
      	where you'll find an educator podium.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:selectbuildingtab2completed"  >Good job! Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeeducatorpodiumheading"  >Educator Podium</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeeducatorpodium"  >
      	Now purchase an educator podium. Click on the podium, then move your mouse over the zoo
      	to see a preview of the object. Don't forget the green directional arrow. In this case, it shows the position where the educator
      	will stand to speak to the guests. Click to place an educator podium.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:placeeducatorpodiumcompleted"  >Excellent! Now that your educator has a podium to speak from, he or she can go to
      	work educating your guests. By educating your guests, you can increase the amount of money you
      	receive from educational donations. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial2:tutorial_2_complete"  >
      	Great job! This is the end of the Construction Tutorial. The next tutorial will
      	teach you a few things about accessing information about your zoo. To continue playing the next tutorial, click the check mark button in the lower right, or if you wish to return to the Main Menu, click on the back button. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:tutorial3_welcome"  >

























          In the following tutorial you will learn how to get information about animals, staff, guests, buildings and your zoo's status.

























         <br>Let's get started!  Click the check button on this panel to continue.</br>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectanimalheading"  >Select an Animal</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectanimal"  >Let's start by learning how to get more information about animals. Click on one of the animals in your zoo to open its Information panel. Don't forget you can scroll the map around in case an
      	animal isn't currently in view.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectanimalcompleted"  >Great! When you first open the Animal Information panel, you'll see a number of icons that indicate the state of the animal's needs. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:trackanimalheading"  >Tracking On</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:trackanimal"  >Click on the picture of the animal on the Animal Information panel. This enables tracking, and your camera will begin following the selected animal around.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:trackanimalcompleted"  >Great! You can also do this for guests and staff, and it's a handy way to see what an animal or person is up to. Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:zoommaponanimalheading"  >Zoom In</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:zoommaponanimal"  >Now zoom in on the selected animal to get a better view.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:zoommaponanimalcompleted"  >

























      	Great! A closer view will help you see the animals' "emoticons".
























         <br/>
























         "Er, emoti..what? Is that a disease?"
























         <br/>
























         Nope.
      	Emoticons are how animals tell you about their needs... and we'll tell you more about needs in a sec. When you're all through watching your animal, click
      	the check button on this panel to continue.
























      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:untrackanimalheading"  >Tracking Off</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:untrackanimal"  >Once again, click on the picture of the animal on the Animal Information panel. This will disable tracking, and your camera will stop following the selected animal around.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:untrackanimalcompleted"  >Great! Time to move on to learning about the animal's needs. Click
      	the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalneedsheading"  >View Animal Status</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalneeds"  >
      	The next tab will take you to the Animal Status panel. Click on the Animal Status Tab.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalneedscompleted"  >
      	Great! This panel shows you what the animal's current activity is and a few other
      	things about the animal's condition that you want to be aware of. This is where you'll see whether an animal
      	is ill or, ah, expecting a new addition! Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalbasicneeds_1heading"  >A Satisfied Need</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalbasicneeds_1"  >See how cool need 1 is</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalbasicneeds_1completed"  >The icons on the Animal Information panel represent the animal's needs.
      	The icon shown on this tutorial panel represents an animal's need to exercise. When it's shown with a green
      	overlay, it means that the need is Satisfied and all is good. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalbasicneeds_2heading"  >A Pressing Need</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalbasicneeds_2"  >See how cool need 2 is</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalbasicneeds_2completed"  >
      	The icon shown on this tutorial panel represents an animal's thirst. When it's shown with a yellow
      	overlay, it means that the need is pressing. This means that the animal will be soon trying to satisfy this need.
      	Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalbasicneeds_3heading"  >A Critical Need</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalbasicneeds_3"  />
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalbasicneeds_3completed"  >The icon shown here represents an animal's hunger. When it's shown with a red
overlay, it means that the need is critical and the animal has not been able to satisfy it. This is a good time to check your exhibit area to make sure the right objects, in this case, the right kind of foods, are available.
 Click the check button on this panel to continue.
   </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalgeneralheading"  >View General Animal Info</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalgeneral"  >
      	The last tab on this panel will take you to the animal's General Information panel. Click on the General Information
      	Tab.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewanimalgeneralcompleted"  >
      	Excellent! This is where you'll find information about the animal's gender, preferred biome, and which
      	part of the world it originates in. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewrecommendationsheading"  >Zookeeper Recommendations</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewrecommendations"  >
      	You can get a lot of helpful information about an animal's preferences using the Zookeeper Recommendations
      	panel. Click on the Zookeeper Recommendations button to open the Zookeeper Recommendations panel now.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewrecommendationscompleted"  >
      	Excellent! All of the objects that you see on this panel are filtered to include only
      	those that are useful to the animal you have selected. You can choose objects
      	from this panel and place them in your zoo just as you did with the other. The Buy panel is covered in the second tutorial. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:closerecommendations"  >
You can use the mini-tabs on the Zookeeper Recommendation panel to see which foods, shelters, plants, trees, and enrichment objects the animal prefers. When you are finished, click the close button in the upper right corner of the Zookeeper
      	Recommendations panel.
  </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectkeeperheading"  >Select a Zookeeper</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectkeeper"  >Locate a zookeeper in your zoo. If they're not in the middle of performing a specific task, you might find them
      	sitting on one of your benches... they're a lot like real people, after all. Otherwise, they'll be walking around tending to your exhibits.
      	Click on a zookeeper to open the Zookeeper Information panel.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectkeepercompleted"  >
      	Great! The Staff Status Panel is where you'll see your Zookeeper's Current Duty. This is what your zookeeper
      	is doing right now. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewassignmentsheading"  >View Keeper Assignments</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewassignments"  >Click on the Staff Assignments tab to view the zookeeper's assignments.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewassignmentscompleted"  >
      	You can assign zookeepers to specific exhibit areas. This will keep them focused on the exhibits that
	you select. If a zookeeper does not have an assignment, he or she will  head for any exhibit that needs
	attention. Depending on your zoo, this could mean they do a lot of walking! Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectaddassignheading"  >Select Add Assignment</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectaddassign"  >Click on the Add New Assignment button now.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectaddassigncompleted"  >When you select Add Assignment, the cursor turns into a flag post. Place the flag post in your zoo to assign a zookeeper to an exhibit area. When finished, right-click the mouse to clear the cursor. If you assign a zookeeper to more than one exhibit area, he/she may become ineffective. Click the check button on this panel to continue.

     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectstaffthoughtsheading"  >Select Staff Thoughts</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectstaffthoughts"  >Click on the Staff Thoughts button to view the staff thoughts.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectstaffthoughtscompleted"  >
      	The Staff Thoughts panel is where you'll see what your staff are thinking. Here you might get a bit of insight about whether there is something
      	standing in the way of them caring for your animals properly. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectstaffsalaryheading"  >Select Staff Salary</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectstaffsalary"  >Click on the Staff Salary button.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectstaffsalarycompleted"  >
      	This is where you'll see their salary and how long they've been employed. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectguestheading"  >Select a Guest</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectguest"  >Now let's move on to the guests. Click on any guest to select him (or her).</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectguestcompleted"  >
      	The Guest Activities and Needs panel shows you what the guest is currently doing along with icons
     	indicating the status of the guest's various needs. Just like animals, if a need is green, it is satisfied, if it's yellow, it's pressing, and if it's red, it's critical.
     	Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectgueststatusheading"  >Select Guest Status</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectgueststatus"  >
      	Click on the Guest Status Tab to open a guest's Information Panel.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectgueststatuscompleted"  >
	On this panel, you can see how much cash the guest is carrying, and if the guest has purchased a souvenir
	in your zoo. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectguestfavoritesheading"  >Select Guest Favorites</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectguestfavorites"  >
      	Click on the Guest Favorites Tab.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectguestfavoritescompleted"  >
      	Here you will see the guest's favorite animal. Guests are likely to make larger donations if they see their
      	favorite animals so if you stay on top of your guests' favorites, you'll reap the reward of more money coming
      	in from donations. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectguestthoughtsheading"  >Select Guest Thoughts</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectguestthoughts"  >
      	Click on the Guest Thoughts Tab.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectguestthoughtscompleted"  >
      	 Here's where you can find out what the guest thinks about your zoo. (Don't you wish you could read
      	 everyone's mind this way?) This might give you some ideas about what things you can
      	do to improve your guests' experience. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectfoodstandheading"  >Select a Food Stand</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectfoodstand"  >
      	Buildings have information panels as well. Click on any food stand in your zoo to open its Building Information
      	panel. Don't forget... you may need to scroll your map in order to locate one of the food stands.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectfoodstandcompleted"  >
      	The Building Status panel shows you the current price level for items being sold in the building and the items it
      	sells. Some buildings may display slightly different information here. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectfoodstandfinanceheading"  >Select Finance Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectfoodstandfinance"  >
      	Click on the Finance Tab.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectfoodstandfinancecompleted"  >
      	This is where you'll see a mini "balance sheet" for the selected building. It shows how many months it's been operating, and more
      	importantly, whether it's turning a profit. The information on the Finance tab can help you decide what buildings are paying off for your zoo. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectzoostatusheading"  >Select Zoo Status</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectzoostatus"  >
      	You can get a complete overview about how your zoo is doing from the Zoo Status panel. Click the Zoo
      	Finances button to open the Zoo Status panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectzoostatuscompleted"  >
      	This first information panel gives you some summary information about your zoo. This is where you can mark
      	your zoo as Open or Closed and alter the level of your admission prices. When you close the zoo, all your guests
      	will begin to leave. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectzoofameheading"  >Zoo Fame</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectzoofame"  >Click on the Zoo Fame Tab to open the Zoo Fame panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectzoofamecompleted"  >The Zoo Fame panel shows the status of the various elements that contribute to your zoo fame score, including the number of animals, different species, and the suitability of their habitats, among other things. To view more information about each of these elements, move your mouse over the bars. Click the check button on this panel to continue. </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectzoofinancesheading"  >Select Income/Expense Tab</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectzoofinances"  >
	Now click on the Income and Expense Report Tab to open the balance sheet for your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:selectzoofinancescompleted"  >
      	Great! The Income and Expense report will give you a monthly tally of your financial comings and goings. If
      	you're seeing lots of red, your zoo is probably spending more than it's receiving. Remember...green is good,
 and this is one place where you don't want to be looking through rose-colored glasses! Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:closezoostatusheading"  >Close Zoo Status</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:closezoostatus"  >
      	Notice that there are a number of other tabs where you can go to see graphs, a list of awards earned by your zoo,
      	donation summaries, and more. Click on the Close button when you are finished viewing zoo information.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:closezoostatuscompleted"  />
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:openquickstatsheading"  >Open Quick Stats</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:openquickstats"  >
      	The Quick Stats panel provides you with a list of all the warm bodies in your zoo, including
      	animals, guests, and staff. (Don't worry, cold-blooded animals are included, too!)  Click on the Quick Stats button to open the Quick Stats Panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:openquickstatscompleted"  >
      	Great! The first panel shows you a list of all the animals in your zoo. You'll see icons representing the basic needs
      	of your animals and any other special conditions they may be experiencing... like illness. This can be very helpful
      	at giving you an overview of things that may need your attention. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewguestlistheading"  >View Guest List</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewguestlist"  >
	Click on the Guest Information Tab.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewguestlistcompleted"  >
      	While viewing any of the lists, you can click on an animal or person in the list to select it. The camera will jump to that
      	location and begin tracking the movements of the animal or person selected (hmmm, maybe
      	another one of those "don't you wish you could..." things). Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewstafflistheading"  >View Staff List</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewstafflist"  >
      	Now click on the Staff Information Tab.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewstafflistcompleted"  >
      	You can easily find the whereabouts of the staff in your zoo by selecting them from the staff list. The camera will jump to
      	their location and open their Staff Information panel showing you what they're currently up to. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:closequickstatsheading"  >Close Quick Stats</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:closequickstats"  >When you're finished viewing the people and animals in your zoo, close the Quick Stats panel.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:closequickstatscompleted"  >
      	Great! Now it's time to move on to learning more about the Photo Safari. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:enterphotosafariheading"  >Select Camera Mode</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:enterphotosafari"  >
      	Click on the Photo Safari button to enter Camera Mode.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:enterphotosafaricompleted"  >
      	You can take pictures of anything in your zoo using Photo Safari view. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:PHTutorial3"  >Tutorial 3 Photo Challenge</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewphotochallengeheading"  >View Photo Challenges</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewphotochallenge"  >When a photo challenge is available, you can right-click to view the challenge.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewphotochallengecompleted"  >This challenge asks you to take a picture of a dromedary camel. Think you're up for the challenge?</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:completephotochallengeheading"  >Photograph a Dromedary Camel</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:completephotochallenge"  >
      	You can walk around using the left mouse button or the movement keys. Locate a dromedary
      	camel in your zoo. You can adjust the zoom of your camera in and out using the mouse wheel. Once you have a dromedary camel in view, press Spacebar to take a picture of it.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:completephotochallengecompleted"  >Excellent photo! Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewphotochallenge2heading"  >View Photo Challenges</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewphotochallenge2"  >Right-click to go back to the photo challenges.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:viewphotochallenge2completed"  >This way, you can take another look at the picture(s) that you took for the photo challenge. Click the check button on this panel to continue.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:openphotoalbumheading"  >Open Photo Album</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:openphotoalbum"  >
      	You can view any of the photographs that you've taken by opening your Photo Album. Click on the Photo Album
      	button to open the Photo Album.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:openphotoalbumcompleted"  >
      	The photos that you've just taken are shown in the film strip along the top of the screen. You can click and drag them
      	into empty slots in your Photo Album. Click the check button on this panel to continue.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:closephotoalbumheading"  >Close Photo Album</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:closephotoalbum"  >
      	When you're finished viewing your pictures, click on the Return to Game button to close the Photo
      	Album.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:closephotoalbumcompleted"  />
      <LOC_STRING _locID="tutorial3:tutorial_3_complete"  >
      	Great job! This wraps up the tutorials for Zoo Tycoon 2. We've only brushed the surface of
      	all the great features available to you when creating your dream zoo. There's plenty for you to explore with
      	30 animals, 10 different biomes, hundreds of objects, and more. Be sure to refer to the Zoo Tycoon 2 manual for even more in-depth information.
			<p/>
			If you'd like to learn more about how to play Zoo Tycoon 2, try the other tutorials. Tutorials are marked with the book icon.
<img src="ui/shared/tutorial_icon.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="64" sh="64" width="16" height="16"/>
         <p/>
Press the X button to return to the Main Menu.
      	</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:textformat"  >
         <font name="arial" size="10" shadowx="-1" shadowy="1" shadowa="128">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255" a="255">
               <b>%text%</b>
            </color>
         </font>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:labelformat"  >
         <font name="arial" size="12">
            <color r="255" g="248" b="178" a="255">
               <b>%text%</b>
            </color>
         </font>
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:campaignname"  >Zoo Tycoon 2 Tutorials</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:T1"  >Tutorial 1: Control</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:T1short"  >Control Techniques</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:T1overviewshort"  >Start learning the basics of camera controls in Zoo Tycoon 2 with this guided tutorial. Then move on to construction techniques and more!      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:T2"  >Tutorial 2: Construction </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:T2short"  >Construction Techniques</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:T2overviewshort"  >Start learning the basics of construction in Zoo Tycoon 2 with this guided tutorial. Then move on to general information techniques and more! </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:T3"  >Tutorial 3: Getting Information</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:T3short"  >Getting Information</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="Tutoriallabels:T3overviewshort"  >Learn the basics of getting information about your zoo with this guided tutorial. After this, you'll be all set to create your own zoo in Freeform Mode, take on Challenge Mode, or start a Campaign
      	in Campaign Mode.
      </LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
