<ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AmericanAnimalsintro"  >North American Animals</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AmericanAnimalsoverview"  >
         
         
         
           A prominent zoo would like to open a new sister facility to display an exhibit area featuring three different species of   animals from North America. However, due to foreign content restrictions established by the ruling government, these   species must represent less than 30% of the species on exhibit.
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         To include three species from North America in your zoo and be within the regulations, you must have at least eight different species that are from regions other than North America.      
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AmericanAnimalsoverviewshort"  >  A prominent zoo would like to open a new sister facility to feature an exhibit area focused on North American species. However, due to   regulations, these species must represent less than 30% of the animals on exhibit. Create a new zoo so that you can display the required   species and fall within regulations. Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock the globe statue!      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AmericanAnimalsSuccessoverview"  >Your zoo has been a great success, and the new North American exhibit area is a hit!  The balance between species from North America and those from other regions of the world has ensured that you fall within regulations.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AmericanAnimalsresult"  >North American animals on exhibit!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AmericanAnimalsoverallgoal"  >Adopt three species from North America. However, to be permitted to display these animals, you must have at least eight species from outside North America.      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AmericanAnimalsoverallgoalOK"  >Congratulations! You have succeeded in balancing your display of animals from North America with other species.      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AsianAnimalsintro"  >Asian Animal Expansion</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AsianAnimalsoverview"  >
         
         
         
           The Board of Directors of your zoo has mandated that four Asian species be obtained within one   year. Unfortunately, animals from Asia are in short supply! Zoos around the world have had difficulty obtaining   these treasured endangered animals, and they are only being offered to zoos with the highest of reputations. 
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         You have one year to obtain the animals. Given their scarcity, you'll need to achieve zoo fame of  four stars to even hope to obtain enough of these rare creatures.     
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AsianAnimalsoverviewshort"  >  The Board of Directors of your zoo has mandated that the four Asian species be obtained within one year. Unfortunately, animals from Asia are in short supply! Do what it takes to increase your zoo's reputation so that you can acquire these rare creatures. Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock the globe statue!      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AsianAnimalsSuccessoverview"  >The addition of these rare Asian animals has had the expected positive impact on zoo attendance. Your zoo is thriving, and the Board is exceptionally pleased with your results. In recognition of your accomplishment, you have been given the globe statue, which you will be able to use in all of your future endeavors.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AsianAnimalsFailureoverview"  >Unfortunately, the mandated time allowed by your Board of Directors has expired. Regrettably they have had to find an alternate direction for the zoo.      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AsianAnimalsresult"  >Asian animals on exhibit!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AsianAnimalsoverallgoal"  >Add four species from Asia to your zoo within one year.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AsianAnimalsoverallgoalOK"  >Congratulations! You have succeeded in obtaining four Asian species within the required one year timeframe.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AsianAnimalsoverallgoalfailed"  >You have failed to obtain four Asian species within the required one year timeframe.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalsintro"  >African Animal Empire</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalsoverview"  >
         
         
         
           A wealthy landowner in Northern Europe wants to attempt the impossible. He has a vacant plot of land and would   like to create an animal park featuring animals only from Africa. He has provided enough funding to get started,   and will pay out some additional cash each time a new African animal species is added. The completed park must hold   12 different species of animals that originate in Africa.
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         In the interest of getting the park off the ground, he's willing to accept that it may be necessary to include animals from other regions of the world. Ultimately, however, for the park to meet his criteria, the park must be home to animals only from Africa. Any animals from other regions must be released to the wild for the park to be considered complete.     
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalsoverviewshort"  >A wealthy landowner would like to create an animal park featuring animals only from Africa. It must contain at least 12 different species. You can use any animal to get the zoo going, but animals from other regions must be   released to the wild for the park to be considered complete. Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock the globe statue!      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalsSuccessoverview"  >Congratulations! You have succeeded in creating an animal park dedicated to the animals of Africa. The new "African Animal Empire" has been written up as a tourist destination and is attracting guests from around the world.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalsresult"  >African Animal Empire completed!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalsoverallgoal"  >Build an animal park featuring 12 species of animals originating from Africa. Release to the wild any animals from other regions of the world that you may have used while building the park.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalsoverallgoalOK"  >Congratulations! You have succeeded in creating an animal park dedicated to the animals of Africa.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave1"  >You have your first species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave2"  >You have two species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave3"  >You have three species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave4"  >You have four species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave5"  >You have five species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave6"  >You have six species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave7"  >You have seven species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave8"  >You have eight species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave9"  >You have nine species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave10"  >You have ten species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave11"  >You have eleven species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalshave12"  >You have twelve species from Africa in your park!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:AfricanAnimalsgetridofothers"  >You have enough species from Africa, but you need to release to the wild animals from any other world region.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:HugeBiomeintro"  >Complete Ecosystem</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:HugeBiomeoverview"  >
         
         
         
           Guests particularly enjoy exhibits that resemble the natural habitat of the animals they house. They are even   more impressed when an entire ecosystem can be modeled within such an exhibit. Create a savannah exhibit   that contains both herbivores and carnivores. Ensure that their environment needs are met. As long as your   carnivores' food needs are being met by your zookeepers, your herbivores should be safe. To make the   exhibit a success, you will need at least six herbivores and four carnivores within the same area. 
         
      
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
           Continue to run this exhibit for four months. As long as you maintain this exhibit, you will   receive an additional $2,000 per month in grant funding to help pay the staff cost likely required to keep this running smoothly.     
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:HugeBiomeoverviewshort"  >  Create a savannah exhibit that contains both herbivores and carnivores but keep your carnivores well fed to avoid   any unfortunate accidents!       </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:HugeBiomeSuccessoverview"  >Your ecosystem has been successful over the four month trial period. Guests enjoyed the exhibit immensely in spite of the additional stress on zoo staff to keep the carnivores sated!      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:HugeBiomeFailureoverview"  >Your ecosystem exhibit has failed as you were unable to prevent your carnivores from attacking your herbivores. You have lost all funding for this program.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:HugeBiomeFailureWitnessedoverview"  >Your zoo has suffered a serious setback when one of your guests witnessed one of your animals become prey to another. Your biome exhibit is considered a failure and parents are outraged that their children were exposed to the brutality of a live animal becoming prey to another. Regrettably your zoo has had to put a significant sum of money into escrow to pay the legal fees expected as a result of the lawsuit filed on behalf of the Outraged Parents Coalition.       </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:HugeBiomeresult"  >A successful ecosystem demonstration!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:HugeBiomeoverallgoal"  >Create a savannah exhibit combining four carnivores and six herbivores within the same area. Run this exhibit for four months and ensure that no herbivores get injured.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:HugeBiomeoverallgoalOK"  >Congratulations! You have succeeded displaying an entire ecosystem without allowing any animals to be injured.     </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:HugeBiomeoverallgoalfailed"  >Your display of an ecosystem, unfortunately, has resulted in tragedy. Carnivores need to be well-fed!      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesintro"  >The World's Biomes</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesoverview"  >
         
         
         
           A biome is characterized by the plant and animal life and climate in a region. The Earth has many different   environments that vary in temperature, moisture, light, and the life that the various conditions support.
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         The geography department of a major university has funded a massive biome project to create a facility where the major biomes of the world are represented and can be used for study, research and education. By creating such an environment and opening it to the public, it is hoped that the benefits of education can be shared at the same time that some of the costs of the project are defrayed by public admission.
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         Create a single zoo that features each of the following biomes and ensure that you have at least one animal in each exhibit.
         
         
         
         <p/>
         
         
         
         Alpine, Boreal Forest, Desert, Savannah, Scrub, Temperate Forest, Tropical Rainforest, Tundra, and Wetlands.     
      
      
      
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesoverviewshort"  >  The geography department of a major university has funded a massive biome project to create a facility where the major biomes of the world are represented. You have the task to create such an environment. Complete all scenarios in this campaign to unlock the globe statue!      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesSuccessoverview"  >This facility has proven to be a great educational asset to the community. Learning about the nuances of the different biomes and the life forms that they support is the first step in understanding how animal and plant life can be protected through conservation.       </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesresult"  >Biome facility a success!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesAlpine"  >Create an alpine biome and adopt one animal suitable for this exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesAlpineOK"  >Great! You have an alpine biome with an animal suited for the exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesBorealForest"  >Create a boreal forest biome and adopt one animal suitable for this exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesBorealForestOK"  >Great! You have a boreal forest biome with an animal suited for the exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesDesert"  >Create a Desert biome and adopt one animal suitable for this exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesDesertOK"  >Great! You have a desert biome with an animal suited for the exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesSavannah"  >Create a savannah biome and adopt one animal suitable for this exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesSavannahOK"  >Great! You have a savannah biome with an animal suited for the exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesScrub"  >Create a scrub biome and adopt one animal suitable for this exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesScrubOK"  >Great! You have a scrub biome with an animal suited for the exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesTemperateForest"  >Create a temperate forest biome and adopt one animal suitable for this exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesTemperateForestOK"  >Great! You have a temperate forest biome with an animal suited for the exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesTropicalRainforest"  >Create a tropical rainforest biome and adopt one animal suitable for this exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesTropicalRainforestOK"  >Great! You have a tropical rainforest biome with an animal suited for the exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesTundra"  >Create a tundra biome and adopt one animal suitable for this exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesTundraOK"  >Great! You have a tundra biome with an animal suited for the exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesWetlands"  >Create a wetlands biome and adopt one animal suitable for this exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorld:TheWorldsBiomesWetlandsOK"  >Great! You have a wetlands biome with an animal suited for the exhibit.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignshort"  >The Globe</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignS1"  >North American Foreign Content</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignS1short"  >Foreign Content</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignS2"  >Scarce Asian Animals</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignS2short"  >Scarce Asian Animals</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignS3"  >African Animal Empire</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignS3short"  >African Animal Empire</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignS4"  >Complete Ecosystem</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignS4short"  >Complete Ecosystem</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignS5"  >The World's Biomes</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TheWorldLabels:WorldCampaignS5short"  >The World's Biomes</LOC_STRING>
</ZT2Strings>
