 <ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirIntro"  >Baird's Tapir</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirOverviewShort"  >
A local town has built a small zoo around a pair of endangered Baird's tapirs. Can you build a colony of tapirs while raising donations and protecting the tapirs' environment at the same time? Complete all the scenarios in this campaign to unlock the conservation breeding center.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirOverview"  >
A pair of rare Baird's tapirs has been discovered on land belonging to a nearby town. Rather than move the endangered creatures, the town council decided to build a small zoo near their protected habitat. 
         <p/>
The town has already begun work on the zoo and acquired a couple of additional animals to help get you started. Your job is to build a colony of healthy tapirs without disturbing their environment, while raising money for the zoo.
        <p/>
The first thing to do is make sure your tapirs are happy, healthy, and well-fed. Meet the basic needs of all the tapirs in your zoo.       
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirFailure"  >
One of your tapirs has died! Since caring for the tapirs was your primary responsibility, the town council has regretfully ended your employment at the zoo. You have failed to achieve your goals.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirDonations"  >
Your tapirs are doing great! All of their basic needs are being met.
      <p/>
Now that your tapirs are happy and healthy, the town council wants you to get your little zoo on firm financial footing. Raise $3,000 in guest donations to prove that you can attract visitors to your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirColony"  >
Good job! Your zoo has raised more than $3,000 in guest donations. The members of the town council are pleased with your progress.
      <p/>
They are so pleased, in fact, that they have asked you to expand your colony of Baird's tapirs. Make a tapir exhibit containing five or more tapirs to win the scenario!
      <p/>
You can get five tapirs either by breeding the tapirs you have or by adopting new ones. Adoption is fast but expensive. Breeding is extremely slow but free.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirSuccessOverview"  >
Your Baird's tapir colony is a big success. Now that you have five of them, you're sure this endangered species has a secure future in your area. And the town council is happy with your zoo as well. Congratulations!     
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirresult"  >Build a Baird's tapir colony containing five or more animals!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirOverallGoal"  >Create a zoo containing a successful colony of five or more Baird's tapirs.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirOverallGoalDone"  >Congratulations! You have built a successful colony containing five or more Baird's tapirs.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirWellBeingGoal"  >Meet the basic needs of the tapirs in your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirDonationsGoal"  >Raise $3,000 in guest donations.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirWellBeingGoalDone"  >Good work! You met the basic needs of the tapirs in your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BairdsTapirDonationsGoalDone"  >You raised more than $3,000 in guest donations and proved that you can attract visitors to your zoo.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramIntro"  >Endangered Species Breeding Program</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramOverviewShort"  >Help save endangered species by breeding three different endangered animals and then releasing them to the wild. Complete all the scenarios in this campaign to unlock the conservation breeding center.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramOverview"  >The board of directors of your zoo has come up with an ambitious breeding program designed to help save endangered species in zoos and in the wild. They want you to acquire and breed three different endangered species, then release one of each species to the wild.
      <p/>
      The endangered species that will be part of your breeding program are the Galapagos giant tortoise, the scimitar horned oryx, and the markhor. The first step is to acquire one of each of the animals and meet their basic needs. (Hint: build your zoo fame to at least 1 star first!)
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramBreed"  >Good work acquiring the required endangered animals! Now it's time to begin the breeding program. For each species, acquire a second animal of the opposite sex to create a breeding pair. Breed one of each of the following: the Galapagos giant tortoise, the scimitar horned oryx, and the markhor.
      <p/>
      To help you continue the breeding program, the zoo's board of directors has awarded you a $10,000 cash grant.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramRelease"  >Well done! You've bred each of the endangered species. Now it's time to help rebuild the populations of these species in their native habitats. Release one Galapagos giant tortoise, one scimitar horned oryx, and one markhor to the wild.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramSuccessOverview"  >
      Your breeding program is complete! In addition to breeding these endangered species, you've also helped rebuild their populations in the wild. The future of these species looks brighter thanks to you. Well done!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramOverallGoal"  >Acquire, breed, and release to the wild a Galapagos giant tortoise, a scimitar horned oryx, and a markhor.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramGetTortoiseGoal"  >Acquire a Galapagos giant tortoise and meet its basic needs.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramGetTortoiseGoalDone"  >You have obtained a Galapagos giant tortoise and met its basic needs!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramGetOryxGoal"  >Acquire a scimitar horned oryx and meet its basic needs.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramGetOryxGoalDone"  >You have obtained a scimitar horned oryx and met its basic needs!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramGetMarkhorGoal"  >Acquire a markhor and meet its basic needs.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramGetMarkhorGoalDone"  >You have obtained a markhor and met its basic needs!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramGetAll"  >Acquire a Galapagos giant tortoise, scimitar horned oryx, and markhor.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramGetAllDone"  >You have obtained all required animals!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramBreedTortoiseGoal"  >Breed the Galapagos giant tortoise.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramBreedTortoiseGoalDone"  >You have successfully bred the Galapagos giant tortoise!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramBreedOryxGoal"  >Breed the scimitar horned oryx.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramBreedOryxGoalDone"  >You have successfully bred the scimitar horned oryx!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramBreedMarkhorGoal"  >Breed the markhor.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramBreedMarkhorGoalDone"  >You have successfully bred the markhor!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramBreedAll"  >Breed your Galapagos giant tortoise, scimitar horned oryx, and markhor.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramBreedAllDone"  >You have bred your Galapagos giant tortoise, scimitar horned oryx, and markhor.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramReleaseTortoiseGoal"  >Meet the advanced needs of a Galapagos giant tortoise and release it to the wild.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramReleaseTortoiseGoalDone"  >You have released a Galapagos giant tortoise to the wild!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramReleaseOryxGoal"  >Meet the advanced needs of a scimitar horned oryx and release it to the wild.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramReleaseOryxGoalDone"  >You have released a scimitar horned oryx to the wild!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramReleaseMarkhorGoal"  >Meet the advanced needs of a markhor and release it to the wild.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramReleaseMarkhorGoalDone"  >You have released a markhor to the wild!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramReleaseAll"  >Release a Galapagos giant tortoise, scimitar horned oryx, and markhor to the wild.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:BreedingProgramReleaseAllDone"  >You have released a Galapagos giant tortoise, scimitar horned oryx, and markhor to the wild!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooIntro"  >The Endangered Species Zoo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooOverviewShort"  >Can you complete the ultimate endangered species challenge? Create a 5-star zoo containing nothing but endangered species! Complete this scenario to unlock the conservation breeding center.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooOverview"  >You've been hired to build a brand new zoo, and the board of directors wants to improve the public's awareness of endangered species. The board has an ambitious plan for you to create a 5-star zoo containing nothing but endangered or critically endangered species!
      <p/>
		The board of directors will allow you to display some non-endangered species as you build your zoo, but to accomplish your goal you must have a 5-star rating and no lower-risk or vulnerable animals in your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooCatchUp"  >Your zoo is doing well, but the board of directors is concerned that you do not have any endangered or critically endangered species. If you do not obtain at least two different species of endangered or critically endangered animals within the next month, the board will end your employment at the zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooCatchUpSuccess"  >You've managed to add two endangered or critically endangered species to your zoo before the board of directors' one-month deadline. The board is pleased with your progress and urges you to acquire more endangered species.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooCatchUpFailure"  >A month has passed and you have failed to acquire two endangered or critically endangered species. The board of directors has removed you from your position because you were not able to create a 5-star zoo that contains only endangered and critically endangered species. Better luck in your future endeavors!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooForcedAdoption"  >Your zoo's board of directors has unexpectedly acquired a new endangered species without consulting you! You will find the %s in a crate near the entrance to your zoo. The bad news is that the cost of the animal will be deducted from your funds. The good news is that if you can earn $300 in guest donations for the animal you will become eligible for a hefty grant!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooDonationSuccess"  >You've earned more than $300 in donations for your %s. In recognition of your efforts to expose the public to endangered animals you have received a significant cash grant!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooGrant"  >Your progress in obtaining endangered animals has impressed your zoo's board of directors so much that they have given you a grant!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooSuccessOverview"  >
      Congratulations! You have successfully built a 5-star zoo containing nothing but endangered and critically endangered animals. The board of directors is delighted! The popularity of your zoo has helped teach the public about the diversity of endangered species around the world.
      <p/>
      You have unlocked the conservation breeding center! The conservation breeding center will be available in all of your future Zoo Tycoon 2: Endangered Species games.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooOverallGoal"  >Create a 5-star zoo that contains only endangered or critically endangered species. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooOverallGoalDone"  >Wow! You have created a 5-star zoo with only endangered species!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooCatchUpGoalOne"  >Acquire one endangered or critically endangered species within one month.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooCatchUpGoalOneDone"  >You have obtained one endangered species!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooCatchUpGoalTwo"  >Acquire a second endangered or critically endangered species within one month.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooCatchUpGoalTwoDone"  >You have obtained a second endangered species!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooDonationGoal"  >Earn $300 in guest donations for the the %s.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimals:EndangeredAnimalsZooDonationGoalDone"  >You earned $300 in guest donations for the %s and received a cash grant!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimalsLabels:EndangeredAnimalsCampaignshort"  >Endangered Species</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimalsLabels:EndangeredAnimalsCampaignS1"  >Baird's Tapir</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimalsLabels:EndangeredAnimalsCampaignS1short"  >Baird's Tapir</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimalsLabels:EndangeredAnimalsCampaignS2"  >Endangered Species Breeding Program</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimalsLabels:EndangeredAnimalsCampaignS2short"  >Breeding Program</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimalsLabels:EndangeredAnimalsCampaignS3"  >The Endangered Species Zoo</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="EndangeredAnimalsLabels:EndangeredAnimalsCampaignS3short"  >Endangered Species Zoo</LOC_STRING>
   
</ZT2Strings>
