 <ZT2Strings>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahIntro"  >The Great Savannah</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahOverviewShort"  >
Use sky trams and elevated paths to showcase savannah wildlife! Build a successful zoo without disturbing a protected conservation area. Complete all of the scenarios in this campaign to unlock the decorated tour gate.  
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahOverview"  >
Decades of poaching have greatly reduced wildlife populations in the local savannah. To help stop the problem, the authorities have designated a large section of savannah as a protected conservation area. 
      <p/>
Your job is to build a successful zoo and wildlife park around the protected area. The conservation area itself is off limits to most forms of development. You may, however, build elevated paths and sky trams over the conservation area. You may also place animals inside the conservation area. Adopting savannah animals and placing them on exhibit in the conservation area helps rebuild the local animal populations while teaching the public about the savannah ecosystem at the same time.
      <p/>
The local authorities want the new zoo and wildlife park you're creating to be a state-of-art facility. They want you to build a working sky tram system in your zoo with at least two stations. In return they will give you a $8,000 grant. (Hint: Increase your zoo fame to 2 stars first.)    
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahFame"  >
Good work! Your park now contains a working sky tram system. You've been given a $8,000 grant to help with the costs.
      <p/>
The local authorities are eager for you to build the zoo into a world-class institution. If you can increase your zoo fame to 4 stars, you'll prove that it's possible to create a popular zoo around a protected conservation area. Get your zoo fame to 4 stars to win the scenario!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahGiantSableAntelope"  >
A survey of your guests reveals that they're extremely interested in seeing the critically endangered giant sable antelope in its native savannah habitat. If you can obtain two giant sable antelope and meet their basic needs within the next month, guest attendance at your zoo will increase! (Note: This is an optional goal. Failing to complete it will not cause you to fail the scenario.) 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahGiantSableAntelopeSuccess"  >
You've obtained two giant sable antelope and met their basic needs. Guests are eager to see these rare and fascinating creatures living in their native savannah environment. The animals have attracted a wave of new guests to your zoo! 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahGiantSableAntelopeFailureNoAntelope"  >
A month has gone by and you still haven't obtained a pair of giant sable antelope. Interest in seeing the animals has declined. You have missed your chance to attract extra guests to your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahGiantSableAntelopeFailureNeed"  >
Although you have obtained two giant sable antelope, you have failed to meet their basic needs. Guests aren't interested in seeing animals that are unhappy or poorly cared for. You have missed your chance to attract extra guests to your zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahSuccessOverview"  >
You have achieved a 4-star rating! You've proven that you can create a popular zoo around a protected conservation area without disturbing the local wildlife. Congratulations on your success!     
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahResult"  >Build a zoo around a protected conservation area!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahOverallGoal"  >Create a successful zoo around the protected conservation area.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahOverallGoalSuccess"  >Congratulations! You have achieved a 4-star rating without disturbing the protected conservation area.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahSkyTramGoal"  >Create a working sky tram system with at least two stations.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahFameGoal"  >Increase your zoo fame rating to 4 stars.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahFameGoalDone"  >Your zoo fame rating is 4 stars!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahGiantSableAntelopeGoal"  >(Optional) Obtain two giant sable antelope within the next month and meet their basic needs.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahSkyTramGoalDone"  >You have built a working sky tram system.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:GreatSavannahGiantSableAntelopeGoalDone"  >You obtained two giant sable antelope and met their basic needs.</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapIntro"  >Bridging the Gap</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapOverviewShort"  >Can you build a zoo that contains 16 different animal species? There's only one catch--there's a chasm in your way! Complete all of the scenarios in this campaign to unlock the decorated tour gate.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapOverview"  >The owners of the local zoo have ambitious plans to expand their small facility. The only problem is that the zoo is built next to a deep chasm, and local environmental laws prohibit any construction that might damage the chasm's delicate ecosystem. 
      <p/>
      You've been hired to solve the owner's expansion problem using modern tranportation technologies. Your first goal is to expand the zoo so that there are at least eight species of animal on display. When you achieve that goal, the owners will pay you a $4,000 bonus.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapTwelve"  >
      The owners are very happy to see eight different species on display in the zoo, so they have given you a $4,000 bonus as a reward. Now they want to expand even more. Increase the number of species on display to 12 and the owners will pay you a $10,000 bonus!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapSixteen"  >
      The owners are impressed that you've managed to display 12 different species. They've given you $10,000 in recognition of your efforts. However, they feel that one more expansion will really establish their zoo as a leading facility. Increase the number of different species on display to 16 to win the scenario!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapSuccessOverview"  >
      Congratulations! You've overcome geographical obstacles and transformed a small zoo into one that contains 16 different species. The owners are delighted!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapOverallGoal"  >Expand your zoo and span the chasm.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapEightGoal"  >Display eight or more different species in the zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapEightGoalDone"  >You have eight or more species on display!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapTwelveGoal"  >Display 12 or more different species in the zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapTwelveGoalDone"  >You have 12 or more different species on display!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapSixteenGoal"  >Display 16 or more different species in the zoo.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:BridgingGapSixteenGoalDone"  >You have 16 or more different species on display!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsIntro"  >Five-Star Sensation</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsOverviewShort"  >An old established zoo is having trouble maintaining its popularity. Use all of your transportation know-how to transform the zoo into a five-star sensation! Complete all the scenarios in this campaign to unlock the decorated tour gate.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsOverview"  >The renowned City Zoo has been around for over a hundred years. Lately the zoo has had trouble attracting guests, even though it's located in a beautiful and historic downtown park.
      <p/>
		The zoo's board of directors has hired you to turn the situation around. Although you won't have very much money to work with, the board is confident that you'll be able to use your knowledge of transportation and zoo design to update the zoo for the twenty-first century.
		<p/>
		The board has given you two goals. First, create a tour with a 4-star tour rating within one year. You may use either Jeep&#xAE; vehicles or sky trams for your tour. Second, build up your zoo fame to 5 stars within one year. Complete both of these goals by January first of year two to win the scenario!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsFailure"  >It's been a full year since you started, but you haven't managed to meet the board of directors' goals of creating a 4-star tour and a 5-star zoo. The board has decided you're not the right person for the job and has terminated your employment. Better luck next time! 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsSuccessOverview"  >
      You've managed to create both a 4-star tour and a 5-star zoo within one short year. The City Zoo is now a five-star sensation! The board of directors has voted you a special commendation for your achievement and you're now the toast of the town. Congratulations!
      <p/>
      Completing this campaign has unlocked the decorated tour gate object. You can use this object in all of your future Zoo Tycoon 2: Endangered Species games.
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsGrant"  >The board of directors is so pleased with your zoo improvements that they have awarded you a cash grant!</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsOverallGoal"  >Achieve both a 4-star tour rating and a 5-star fame rating by January first of year two. 
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsOverallGoalDone"  >You have achieved both a 4-star tour rating and a 5-star fame rating!
      </LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsTourGoal"  >Create a 4-star tour using either Jeep&#xAE; vehicles or sky trams by January first of year two. 
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsTourGoalDone"  >You have created a 4-star tour!
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsFameGoal"  >Achieve a 5-star fame rating by January first of year two. 
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaign:ReachForStarsFameGoalDone"  >You have achieved a 5-star fame rating!
		</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaignLabels:TransportationCampaignshort"  >Transportation</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaignLabels:TransportationCampaignS1"  >The Great Savannah</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaignLabels:TransportationCampaignS1short"  >The Great Savannah</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaignLabels:TransportationCampaignS2"  >Bridging the Gap</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaignLabels:TransportationCampaignS2short"  >Bridging the Gap</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaignLabels:TransportationCampaignS3"  >Five-Star Sensation</LOC_STRING>
      <LOC_STRING _locID="TransportationCampaignLabels:TransportationCampaignS3short"  >Five-Star Sensation</LOC_STRING>
   
</ZT2Strings>
